[
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/KVM",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is KVM and what type of hardware does it require?",
        "answer": "KVM (Kernel-based Virtual Machine) is a full virtualization solution for Linux on x86 hardware containing virtualization extensions (Intel VT or AMD-V)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the names of the kernel modules associated with KVM?",
        "answer": "The kernel consists of a loadable kernel module, kvm.ko, and a processor specific module, which can be either kvm-intel.ko or kvm-amd.ko."
      },
      {
        "question": "As of which Linux version is the KVM kernel component included in mainline Linux?",
        "answer": "The kernel component of KVM is included in mainline Linux as of version 2.6.20."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the recommended storage for the system image of a virtual machine using KVM?",
        "answer": "The system image for the virtual machine should be on local disk space."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can happen if a running virtual machine is placed on networked file space?",
        "answer": "Putting a running virtual machine on networked file space will result in poor performance for both the virtual machine and other users of the filespace."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should UMIACS Staff follow to start using KVM on a machine?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Staff will first need to install the requisite packages and set a baseline configuration, followed by contacting staff with a brief explanation of the goals for running a local virtual machine."
      },
      {
        "question": "What user group must Ubuntu users belong to in order to use KVM?",
        "answer": "Ubuntu requires users to be in the kvm group on the local host."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which program is used to initialize and manage virtual machines after the required packages are installed?",
        "answer": "'virt-manager' is the program used to initialize and manage virtual machines."
      },
      {
        "question": "What networking mode does KVM provide by default?",
        "answer": "The default networking mode provided by KVM is usermode networking, which offers a NAT connection to the outside world."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used in the terminal to bring up the graphical interface for managing virtual machines?",
        "answer": "The command is 'virt-manager -c qemu:///session'."
      },
      {
        "question": "Describe the process to forward ports during virtual machine configuration in KVM.",
        "answer": "The functionality to forward ports is achieved by editing the XML file for your domain directly. First, create your VM with virt-manager and shut it down, then run 'virsh -c qemu:///session' in a shell to access the virsh shell and edit the VM's XML."
      },
      {
        "question": "According to the text, how would you forward port 2222 to port 22?",
        "answer": "You need to replace the <domain> tag in the XML file with <domain type='kvm' xmlns:qemu='http://libvirt.org/schemas/domain/qemu/1.0'> and insert the lines '<qemu:commandline><qemu:arg value='-redir'/><qemu:arg value='tcp:2222::22'/></qemu:commandline>' just above the last </domain> tag."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to start a Windows installation in a more automated way?",
        "answer": "The command 'virt-install' can be used to start a Windows installation in an automated fashion."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens when virt-install is executed with a Windows 10 x64 ISO?",
        "answer": "Executing virt-install with a Windows 10 x64 ISO spawns virt-viewer automatically and shows the Windows installer screen."
      },
      {
        "question": "What resources are specified in the virt-install command for creating a Windows virtual machine?",
        "answer": "The resources specified include a 40G disk and 16GB of RAM."
      }
    ],
    "total": 15
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/WebSpace",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the preferred method for hosting websites in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Hosting websites in UMIACS Object Store is the preferred method."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can faculty members and authorized users modify their public profiles on the UMIACS homepage?",
        "answer": "Faculty members and authorized users can modify their own public profiles on the main UMIACS homepage by following the instructions in ContentManagement."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the URL format for a personal website at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The URL format for a personal website at UMIACS is http://www.umiacs.umd.edu/~username, where username is the UMIACS username."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must users set their directory Home Page to after creating a website in the UMIACS Object Store?",
        "answer": "Users must set their directory Home Page to the bucket's URL, which ends in umiacs.io."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to a personal webpage after a user departs from UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The personal webpage is not permanently continued upon the user's departure from UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be done if a user believes that their personal website needs to be hosted on the deprecated Nexus File Space?",
        "answer": "If a user believes that their personal website needs to be hosted on the deprecated Nexus File Space, they should contact the Help Desk."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to create a password-protected folder in UMIACS web space?",
        "answer": "The first step is to create the directory you want to password protect or cd into the directory you want to protect."
      },
      {
        "question": "What file must be created in a directory to enable password protection for that directory?",
        "answer": "A file called .htaccess must be created in the directory to enable password protection."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to create the .htpasswd file for password protection in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The command used is htpasswd -c .htpasswd username, where username is the name of the user."
      },
      {
        "question": "What directive is used to restrict content based on IP address in UMIACS web space?",
        "answer": "The SetEnvIF directive is used to restrict content based on IP address."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the address of the Iribe building?",
        "answer": "8125 Paint Branch Drive, College Park, MD 20742"
      },
      {
        "question": "What specific facilities are available in the Iribe building?",
        "answer": "Conference Rooms, Mail Room, Fax Machine, Office TVs"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of printers are mentioned in the miscellaneous section of the Iribe building information?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Public Printers"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of network does the Iribe building provide?",
        "answer": "Iribe Wired Network"
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Shell",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What web application can be used to change your default shell for new access?",
        "answer": "You can use the web application at https://intranet.umiacs.umd.edu/directory/info/ to change your default shell for new access."
      },
      {
        "question": "What warning is provided regarding changing your shell?",
        "answer": "Attempting to change your shell by starting a new shell in the initialization files for your current shell can result in issues in services such as sftp."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can you type in a terminal to see what shell you are using?",
        "answer": "You can type 'echo $SHELL' in a terminal to see what shell you are using."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of shells are mentioned in the section about adding paths?",
        "answer": "The types of shells mentioned are Bash, Tcsh, sh, csh, zsh, and ksh."
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Clear_Cache",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What action is recommended if a webpage is loading correctly for others but incorrectly for you?",
        "answer": "Cleaning your cache will most likely resolve this."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to take if you need to clear the cache on your browser?",
        "answer": "Follow the link below specific to the browser that you are using."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you find the instructions for clearing cache in Google Chrome?",
        "answer": "At the link: https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop&hl=en"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which browser has a support page linked for clearing cache at 'https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/how-clear-firefox-cache'?",
        "answer": "Firefox."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the link for the instructions on how to clear browsing history in Safari?",
        "answer": "https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/clear-your-browsing-history-sfri47acf5d6/mac"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which browser's cache clearing instructions can be found at 'https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/10607/microsoft-edge-view-delete-browser-history'?",
        "answer": "Microsoft Edge."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/OnSite",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What current offerings are listed in the Services/OnSite section?",
        "answer": "Printing and Scanning, Wired Network Access, Wireless Network Access"
      }
    ],
    "total": 1
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SecureCopy",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What does SCP stand for in the context of copying data?",
        "answer": "Secure Copy"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of SCP?",
        "answer": "To securely copy files and directories between two locations using SSH."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which operating systems support the SCP command mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "Red Hat Enterprise Linux, Ubuntu Linux, macOS, and Windows."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to copy 'source_file0.txt' to 'target_file0.txt' on hostname.umiacs.umd.edu?",
        "answer": "[username@hostname ~]$ scp source_file0.txt username@hostname.umiacs.umd.edu:~/target_file0.txt"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command would you use to copy 'source_file1.txt' from hostname.umiacs.umd.edu to the local machine?",
        "answer": "[username@hostname ~]$ scp username@hostname.umiacs.umd.edu:~/source_file1.txt target_file1.txt"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is noted about the syntax of the scp command?",
        "answer": "The syntax of scp is very similar to that of the UNIX command cp with the addition of a hostname and username."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the utility available for Windows hosts mentioned in connection with SCP?",
        "answer": "WinSCP"
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/AlternativePickup",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "As of which semester must you have a rationale other than COVID-19 precautions to use the Alternative Pickup service?",
        "answer": "Fall 2021"
      },
      {
        "question": "What information must you provide in your initial request for picking up or dropping off an item?",
        "answer": "Your name, what you are looking to pick up or drop off, the color, make, and model of the vehicle (if applicable), and the rough 15-minute window that you are planning on stopping by in."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you ensure to have during pickup to verify your identity?",
        "answer": "A photo ID"
      },
      {
        "question": "What phone number should you call when you are at the loop in parking lot GG1?",
        "answer": "(301) 405-1775"
      },
      {
        "question": "What may happen if you arrive on campus without notifying the staff beforehand?",
        "answer": "You will not be able to be serviced."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required for the pickup of large or heavy items?",
        "answer": "They may only be picked up using car transportation instead of allowing on foot pickup to prevent accidental damage."
      },
      {
        "question": "From which entrance should you turn onto Paint Branch Drive to follow the directions provided for reaching the loop behind the A.V. Williams building?",
        "answer": "The main entrance to campus (off US Rt. 1)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you do immediately after making a right at the stop sign past A.V. Williams?",
        "answer": "Enter lot GG1."
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you pass straight at the stop sign after the Xfinity Center when following directions from the Paint Branch Drive entrance?",
        "answer": "The Biomolecular Sciences and A. James Clark Hall buildings."
      },
      {
        "question": "What online resource is mentioned for viewing a full campus map?",
        "answer": "https://maps.umd.edu/map/"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Phishing",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is a common method that phishing attacks use to disguise themselves?",
        "answer": "Phishing attacks may be hard to distinguish from legitimate administrative messages, especially those in which the supposed UMIACS staff advise or require users to take administrative actions related to their account."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do to verify the legitimacy of administrative actions suggested by the UMIACS staff?",
        "answer": "Users should check the UMIACS intranet site, which will always have a posted announcement of any administrative actions intended for all UMIACS users."
      },
      {
        "question": "What URL should always be SSL-secured and reported as a secure connection when visited?",
        "answer": "Any URL in the *.umiacs.umd.edu domain should always be SSL-secured and reported as a secure connection."
      },
      {
        "question": "What tool does UMIACS provide to confirm the legitimacy of messages from staff?",
        "answer": "UMIACS provides a tool called Verify Staff GPG Messages from the UMIACS intranet site, which allows users to paste the text of the message and confirm that the sender is legitimate."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which communications will not be signed with a staff member's GPG key?",
        "answer": "Communications that are initiated by users through the Jira ticket system or in response to these tickets will not be signed."
      },
      {
        "question": "List two signs that may indicate a phishing attempt.",
        "answer": "Bogus to and from addresses (not within the UMIACS or UMD domains) and messages that do not directly reference you by name (e.g., 'Hello user' or 'Hello researcher')."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do before clicking on links or opening attachments in a suspicious message?",
        "answer": "Users should hover over links to check where they really point to instead of clicking on them."
      },
      {
        "question": "What immediate action should you take if you believe you've fallen victim to a phishing attack?",
        "answer": "You should contact the Help Desk immediately."
      },
      {
        "question": "What preventive measures may be taken by UMIACS if you report a potential account compromise?",
        "answer": "This typically will involve a password change as well as possibly locking out access to your account for some period of time while ensuring your account is secure."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/UMIACS:Privacy_policy",
    "Q/A": [],
    "total": 0
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/EMail",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What service is provided for @umiacs.umd.edu email addresses?",
        "answer": "E-mail forwarding, which forwards an @umiacs.umd.edu email address to another address of your choice."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of email services are indicated under Mailing Lists?",
        "answer": "Mail reflectors and aliases."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who should be contacted to set up local mail resources?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Staff."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Caffe",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command is used to verify that the NVIDIA driver is installed and can see the GPUs?",
        "answer": "Run nvidia-smi -L to verify the NVIDIA driver is installed and can see your GPUs."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the version of CUDA mentioned to build Caffe?",
        "answer": "CUDA version 8.0.44 is mentioned to build Caffe."
      },
      {
        "question": "What repository command is used to clone Caffe?",
        "answer": "$ git clone https://github.com/BVLC/caffe.git."
      },
      {
        "question": "What commands are needed to build Caffe with CPU-only capability?",
        "answer": "The commands needed are: git clone https://github.com/BVLC/caffe.git, cd caffe, cp Makefile.config.example Makefile.config, set CPUONLY := 1 in Makefile.config, make, make test, make runtest."
      },
      {
        "question": "What specific MATLAB version is required to use Caffe and which GCC version is required for compiling mex files?",
        "answer": "Matlab 2015a is required and it supports GCC 4.7.x for compiling mex files."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be set in the Makefile.config to enable cuDNN?",
        "answer": "# USE_CUDNN := 1 should be uncommented in Makefile.config to enable cuDNN."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/WebCrawling",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the general activity referred to as 'crawling' in the context of this text?",
        "answer": "Web crawling, scraping, or otherwise downloading large sets of publicly available information on the Internet."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should one understand before crawling publicly accessible data?",
        "answer": "One should understand if any publicly accessible data is encumbered or not, and what the restrictions are on any data that is crawled."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the potential consequences of bad behavior from a single user on UMIACS systems?",
        "answer": "Bad behavior on the part of a single user from UMIACS systems can result in all access to a service being banned from UMIACS' public IP addresses."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of organizations might have restrictions on crawling despite providing access to academic institutions?",
        "answer": "There are a number of different organizations that give access through IP based filtering but have restrictions on crawling."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is advised against when dealing with limitations or restrictions of publicly available services?",
        "answer": "You should never try to evade limitations or restrictions imposed by the site or owner for publicly available services that you are looking to crawl."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which two examples of databases or sites with restrictions on crawling are mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "University of Maryland Library Resources and NCBI."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SSHFileTransferProtocol",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What does SFTP stand for?",
        "answer": "SSH File Transfer Protocol"
      },
      {
        "question": "On which protocol is SFTP layered?",
        "answer": "SSH protocol"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why is SFTP preferred over FTP?",
        "answer": "It is used to securely transfer and manage files on remote systems."
      },
      {
        "question": "What issue can occur if interactive programs are run in shell initialization files when using SFTP?",
        "answer": "It causes SFTP to fail."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to connect to an SFTP server from a terminal under Red Hat Enterprise Linux, Ubuntu Linux, or macOS?",
        "answer": "sftp bkirz@$HOSTNAME.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be replaced in the SFTP command to connect to the desired host?",
        "answer": "$HOSTNAME with the name of the host you are trying to connect."
      },
      {
        "question": "What SFTP client is already installed for UMIACS supported Windows hosts?",
        "answer": "A SFTP client is already installed."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which software can be downloaded to enable SSH and SFTP access on hosts other than UMIACS supported Windows hosts?",
        "answer": "winSCP"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can more information about SFTP be found?",
        "answer": "http://www.openssh.org/"
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/LaTeX",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is LaTeX primarily used for?",
        "answer": "LaTeX is a high-quality typesetting system designed for the production of technical and scientific documentation."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is recommended for LaTeX installation on Windows?",
        "answer": "A full-featured suite such as TeX Live or MiKTeX is recommended for LaTeX installation on Windows."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command is used to list installed packages in TeX Live?",
        "answer": "$ tlmgr list --only-installed"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to compile a LaTeX file into a DVI file?",
        "answer": "$ latex example.tex"
      },
      {
        "question": "What tool is suggested to convert a DVI file into a PDF?",
        "answer": "dvipdfmx is suggested to convert a DVI file into a PDF."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which version of TeX Live comes preinstalled on supported RHEL7 workstations?",
        "answer": "TeX Live 2013 comes preinstalled on supported RHEL7 workstations."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if your output PDF does not look right?",
        "answer": "You may need to use different conversion tools, and your workflow may necessarily vary depending on the contents of your document."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the de facto standard for the communication and publication of scientific documents?",
        "answer": "LaTeX is the de facto standard for the communication and publication of scientific documents."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you find more LaTeX project documentation?",
        "answer": "You can find more LaTeX project documentation on the LaTeX project documentation page."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the output of compiling example.tex in the provided example?",
        "answer": "The output is an example.dvi file."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Branding",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary objective of UMIACS regarding branding?",
        "answer": "UMIACS seeks to have a strong, easily-recognizable brand both on Campus and among peer institutions."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of resources are mentioned as potentially useful for branding?",
        "answer": "Branding resources."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is indicated as the preferred logo for visual presentations?",
        "answer": "The UMIACS Logo."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two horizontal alternatives mentioned in relation to the UMIACS logo?",
        "answer": "Horizontal Alternative 1 and Horizontal Alternative 2."
      },
      {
        "question": "What alternative option is available besides the UMIACS logo?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Logo Without Tagline."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe_Wired_Network",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of network does UMIACS provide in Iribe for transient devices?",
        "answer": "A wired network."
      },
      {
        "question": "What authentication is required for accessing the Iribe wired network?",
        "answer": "Authentication using UMIACS credentials."
      },
      {
        "question": "How long is the access valid after the initial authentication on the Iribe wired network?",
        "answer": "24 hours."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the URL to check the status of your registration on the Iribe wired network?",
        "answer": "https://packetfence00.iribe.umd.edu/status"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where should requests be sent to make the wired network available at a desk?",
        "answer": "Email the request to staff@umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you include in the email request to connect to the wired network at your desk?",
        "answer": "The label of the yellow network jack you are trying to connect."
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you need to do the first time you navigate to a webpage on the Iribe wired network?",
        "answer": "Authenticate using your UMIACS credentials."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you disconnect from the Iribe wired network?",
        "answer": "By visiting https://packetfence00.iribe.umd.edu/networklogoff."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Nexus/CBCB",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "As of when have the compute nodes from CBCB's previous standalone cluster folded into Nexus?",
        "answer": "mid 2023"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two submission hosts you can SSH into for accessing Nexus?",
        "answer": "nexuscbcb00.umiacs.umd.edu and nexuscbcb01.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many nodes were purchased in October 2022 with center-wide funding, and what is the naming convention for these nodes?",
        "answer": "22 nodes named cbcb[00-21]"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the total number of GPU nodes listed in the summary of nodes, and what types of GPUs do they include?",
        "answer": "33 GPUs of various types"
      },
      {
        "question": "What specific configurations are available for the cbcb partition and cbcb-interactive partition?",
        "answer": "The cbcb partition is the default for job allocations on all nodes except those in the cbcb-heng partition. The cbcb-interactive partition only allows interactive jobs."
      },
      {
        "question": "What resource limitations exist for jobs submitted in the cbcb and cbcb-heng partitions regarding core and RAM usage?",
        "answer": "The partition has a GrpTRES limit of 100% of the available cores/RAM on the partition-specific nodes plus 50% of the available cores/RAM on legacy nodes in aggregate."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command must be used to submit a job to the CBCB partition and what parameters should be specified?",
        "answer": "--partition=cbcb and --account=cbcb"
      },
      {
        "question": "What requires CBCB users to possibly recompile software after migrating to Nexus?",
        "answer": "The CBCB's standalone cluster submission and compute nodes were running RHEL7, and Nexus is exclusively running RHEL8."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the highest allocated memory allowed for jobs in the highmem QoS in the cbcb partition?",
        "answer": "significantly increased memory allocation"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of storage does CBCB still have available from its standalone cluster after migration to Nexus?",
        "answer": "All data filesystems that were available in the standalone CBCB cluster are also available in Nexus."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the specified maximum job length for interactive jobs in the cbcb-interactive partition?",
        "answer": "up to 12 hours"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SSH_Jumphosts",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of using jumphosting in SSH?",
        "answer": "To SSH through a host in order to access another host."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command format is used for jumphosting when the ports for different hosts are the same?",
        "answer": "ssh -J user1@host1 user2@host2"
      },
      {
        "question": "In the setup for static jumphosts, what must be edited to create a shortcut for SSH commands?",
        "answer": "The ~/.ssh/config file."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the basic command format for dynamic jumphosts when multiple hosts are involved?",
        "answer": "ssh -J user1@host1:port1,user2@host2:port2 user3@host3"
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you specify the final jump host in the ~/.ssh/config file setup?",
        "answer": "By adding Host finalJump with HostName myfinaljump.example.org and ProxyJump secondJump."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the significance of static jumphosts compared to dynamic jumphosts?",
        "answer": "Static jumphosts are used for times when you will often need to make the jump, allowing a shorter command."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What types of computational resources does UMIACS provide?",
        "answer": "Workstations, Laptops, HPC, Virtualization"
      },
      {
        "question": "What service is included under the category of common-pool resources?",
        "answer": "Nexus Cluster"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of electronic mail services does UMIACS offer?",
        "answer": "Locally hosted E-Mail services."
      },
      {
        "question": "What items can be borrowed through UMIACS's equipment loans?",
        "answer": "Laptops, Projectors, Data Storage"
      },
      {
        "question": "What logistics services are mentioned in the UMIACS service categories?",
        "answer": "Ordering, Procurement, Receiving"
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of support does UMIACS provide under technical support?",
        "answer": "Hardware and OS support"
      },
      {
        "question": "What web-based collaborative tools are mentioned in the UMIACS services?",
        "answer": "Revision Control, Data Sharing"
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of web hosting services are available through UMIACS?",
        "answer": "User Webspace, Lab Webspace, Project Pages"
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Data_Transfer",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command should you use to transfer a single file to another directory?",
        "answer": "cp"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the format for the cp command when transferring a file?",
        "answer": "cp Source Destination"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the recommended command for transferring large amounts of data?",
        "answer": "gtar"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should be used to return a file from a remote host to your current directory?",
        "answer": "scp USERNAME@example1.umiacs.umd.edu:~/Documents/foo.txt ~/Videos"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is an important note regarding the cp command?",
        "answer": "The cp command should only be used for small file transfers."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to create an archive of two files in the current directory?",
        "answer": "gtar -cpvf archive.tar file1 file2"
      },
      {
        "question": "In the command 'gtar -C ~/Documents/ -xpvf archive.tar', what is the purpose of the '-C' flag?",
        "answer": "It specifies the target directory where the data will be re-archived."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the dash '-' represent in the gtar command format for data transfer?",
        "answer": "The dash '-' stands for standard output."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command transfers files from the tmp directory on example1.umiacs.umd.edu to the foo directory on your current host?",
        "answer": "ssh USERNAME@example1.umiacs.umd.edu gtar -cpf - /tmp | gtar -C /foo -xpvf -"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the rsync command do in the context of verifying file transfers?",
        "answer": "It compares the two directories' contents and updates the files in which it sees differences."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command should be used to ensure that files are the same in two directories?",
        "answer": "rsync -aH ~/Documents/ ~/foo"
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be included after the source directory name when using the rsync command?",
        "answer": "A slash after the name of the source directory."
      }
    ],
    "total": 12
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/EmailMigration",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What date did UMIACS wind down its Exchange and IMAP mailbox email services?",
        "answer": "June 30th 2020"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can users access their email through a browser?",
        "answer": "https://mail.google.com/a/umd.edu/"
      },
      {
        "question": "What action should users take if they already have a personal Gmail/Google account logged in?",
        "answer": "They may need to add a new Google account for their @umd.edu account."
      },
      {
        "question": "On what date did UMIACS notify everyone about the timeline for the email migrations?",
        "answer": "May 1st 2020"
      },
      {
        "question": "What must users do before May 26th 2020 at 9am to have their mailbox migrated to the UMD Gmail system?",
        "answer": "Notify UMIACS Technical Staff that they wanted their mailbox migrated."
      },
      {
        "question": "What email address was set to forward to the user's @g.umd.edu address starting May 26th 2020 at 9am?",
        "answer": "@umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of folders were not migrated but were stored in the archives?",
        "answer": "Deleted Items and Junk E-Mail from Exchange, Deleted Messages, Junk, and Trash from IMAP"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary email support provided by the Division of IT?",
        "answer": "The web-based offering."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the formats provided for archived email for Exchange and IMAP users?",
        "answer": "PST format for Exchange users and MBOX format for IMAP users."
      },
      {
        "question": "What requirement is placed on users with an appointment at the University of Maryland regarding email forwarding?",
        "answer": "Their UMIACS email must forward to their @umd.edu email address."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/FileTransferProtocol",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the current status of UMIACS's FTP service?",
        "answer": "The FTP service is deprecated in favor of the UMIACS Object Store."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of users access the FTP service, and how do they log in?",
        "answer": "External users log in as anonymous, while internal users access the file directories internally."
      },
      {
        "question": "Will users authenticate over FTP with their UMIACS account?",
        "answer": "Users will never authenticate over FTP with their UMIACS account."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can users find more information about a secure file transfer protocol?",
        "answer": "Users can see SFTP for more information on a secure file transfer protocol."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action can users take to make data externally accessible?",
        "answer": "Users can place data in their public FTP space to make it externally accessible."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the path format for accessing a user's public FTP space?",
        "answer": "The public FTP space can be accessed at the path: asftp://ftp.umiacs.umd.edu/pub/<username>/."
      },
      {
        "question": "From which locations can users upload data to their public FTP site?",
        "answer": "Data can be uploaded from supported UNIX machines to /fs/ftp/pub/<username> and from supported Windows machines to \\umiacs-webftp\\ftp-umiacs\\pub\\<username>."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Data_Compression_/_Archival",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of compressing files before archiving them?",
        "answer": "The purpose of compressing files before archiving them is to allow the computer to store the same information and data on less disk space, as well as reduce transmission time of the file."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command is used in Linux to create a compressed archive file?",
        "answer": "The command used in Linux to create a compressed archive file is: tar czvf <FILENAME>.tar.gz <DIRECTORY>."
      },
      {
        "question": "In the context of creating a compressed archive in Linux, what does the '-c' command indicate?",
        "answer": "The '-c' command indicates the creation of a file."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can one list the contents of a gzip tar file in Linux without extracting the data?",
        "answer": "To list the contents of a gzip tar file without extracting the data in Linux, enter: tar tzvf <FILENAME>.tar.gz."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to expand the contents of a gzip tar file in Linux?",
        "answer": "The command used to expand the contents of a gzip tar file in Linux is: tar xzvf <FILENAME>.tar.gz."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the command to create a compressed archive file from a folder in Windows?",
        "answer": "To create a compressed archive file from a folder in Windows, the command is: Compress-Archive -Path <FOLDER PATH> -DestinationPath <PATH OF COMPRESSED / ARCHIVED FILE>."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should not be included at the end of the file name when creating a compressed archive file from a folder in Windows?",
        "answer": "When creating a compressed archive file from a folder in Windows, do not write .zip at the end of the file."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command is used in Windows to expand the contents of a compressed archive file?",
        "answer": "The command used in Windows to expand the contents of a compressed archive file is: Expand-Archive -Path <FILE PATH>.zip -DestinationPath <FILE PATH OF UNZIPPED FILE>."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Adobe",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is Adobe primarily known for?",
        "answer": "Adobe is primarily known for their multimedia software products and Flash Player."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the commonly deployed Adobe product at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The commonly deployed Adobe product at UMIACS is the Creative Cloud Suite."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which products are included in the Creative Cloud Suite mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "The Creative Cloud Suite includes products such as Acrobat and Photoshop."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many concurrent logons does UMD's license allow for Creative Cloud products?",
        "answer": "UMD's license allows for two concurrent logons on two computing devices."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens when you try to log on to a third device if you are already logged onto two devices?",
        "answer": "If you try to log on to a third device, it will prompt you to confirm that you are OK with being signed out of one or more of the other devices."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who should be contacted to install Creative Cloud products on supported desktop machines?",
        "answer": "Staff should be contacted to install Creative Cloud products on supported Windows or macOS desktop machines."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must users do to use the apps installed on supported desktop machines?",
        "answer": "Users will still need to sign in with their UMD account to use the apps."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can instructions for installing Creative Cloud products on laptops or personal machines be found?",
        "answer": "Instructions for installing Creative Cloud products on laptops or personal machines can be found on Terpware."
      },
      {
        "question": "What option should faculty and staff choose when installing Creative Cloud products?",
        "answer": "Faculty and staff should choose the Faculty and Staff Enterprise for Individuals option."
      },
      {
        "question": "What handles the licensing for Creative Cloud products installed on personal machines?",
        "answer": "Licensing is handled through the user's UMD account."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/ConferenceRooms/AutoAccept",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "How many hours in advance can users schedule auto-accept conference rooms?",
        "answer": "12 hours in advance"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum duration for which users can reserve an auto-accept conference room?",
        "answer": "up to 2 hours at a time"
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to a room reservation made through the UMD's Google Calendar interface if there is no conflict on the calendar?",
        "answer": "The room will auto-accept the reservation"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which rooms mentioned in the text have a single display (LCD) setup and are used for large conference room capabilities?",
        "answer": "Rooms 5107 and 5161"
      },
      {
        "question": "What presentation methods are available in rooms 5107 and 5161?",
        "answer": "Laptop presentation via HDMI or Mersive Solstice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of conferencing is available in every other room on this page apart from rooms 5107 and 5161?",
        "answer": "Software Conferencing via room PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the prefix users must dial to make an external call from the Crestron pads in auto-accept conference rooms?",
        "answer": "91"
      },
      {
        "question": "If a user wants to answer a call using the Crestron system, what steps should they follow?",
        "answer": "Start the system, select phone, and hit the 'dial/answer' button"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the phone numbers associated with the auto-accept conference rooms IRB-5107 and IRB-5161?",
        "answer": "IRB-5107: 301-314-9974, IRB-5161: 301-314-9983"
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/LinuxFAQ",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What topic is covered in the LinuxFAQ section regarding file permissions in UNIX?",
        "answer": "How do I use umasks and SetGID bits for group control under UNIX?"
      },
      {
        "question": "What question addressed in the LinuxFAQ pertains to modifying environment settings for users?",
        "answer": "How do I add a path to my Shell in UNIX?"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one of the primary functions described in the LinuxFAQ related to file management?",
        "answer": "How do I transfer a file or data?"
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Google_Drive/Migrating_from_Backup_and_Sync_to_Drive_for_Desktop",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What two existing Drive sync clients were unified into Drive for Desktop?",
        "answer": "Backup and Sync and Drive File Stream."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to migrate from Backup and Sync to Drive for Desktop on Windows?",
        "answer": "Click on the Backup and Sync cloud icon in the lower right-hand corner of your desktop."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Google account should be selected when signing in during the migration process?",
        "answer": "The account with <DIRECTORYID>@umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does Drive for Desktop check after signing in?",
        "answer": "It checks your folders to make sure all of your files are up to date."
      },
      {
        "question": "What options does Drive for Desktop give regarding storing photos and videos?",
        "answer": "You can choose to store your photos and videos on your Google Drive or your Google Photos."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must you do if you select the Google Photos option?",
        "answer": "You will need to sign into Google Photos using your <DIRECTORYID>@umd.edu Google account to access them."
      },
      {
        "question": "What prompt appears after setting up Drive for Desktop regarding Backup and Sync?",
        "answer": "You will be prompted to remove Backup and Sync from your system."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to the files and folders backed up by Backup and Sync after the migration?",
        "answer": "They will now be backed up by Drive for Desktop as will any files saved to the Google Drive directory in your filesystem."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SecGroups",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are Security Groups used for in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Security Groups are authentication groups that control access to various applications in UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What kind of access control do Security Groups provide?",
        "answer": "They provide fine-grained access control to wikis, source code repositories, and certain web applications."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user view and edit the secgroups they belong to?",
        "answer": "A user can view and edit the secgroups they belong to using the SecGroups section of the directory app."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the URL for the SecGroups section of the directory app?",
        "answer": "The URL for the SecGroups section of the directory app is https://intranet.umiacs.umd.edu/directory/secgroup/."
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SLURM/ClusterStatus",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command is used to display the status of partitions in the cluster?",
        "answer": "The sinfo command."
      },
      {
        "question": "What flag can be added to the sinfo command to show the status of each node individually?",
        "answer": "-N flag."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many nodes are in the 'gamma' partition and what is their state?",
        "answer": "There are 3 nodes in the 'gamma' partition and their state is 'idle'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command allows viewing the status and configuration of specific nodes in the cluster?",
        "answer": "The scontrol command."
      },
      {
        "question": "What two features are active on the node 'tron05'?",
        "answer": "rhel8 and AMD, EPYC-7302."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the total number of CPUs allocated and the total CPUs available for the node 'tron13'?",
        "answer": "1 CPU allocated and 16 CPUs total."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the sacctmgr command display?",
        "answer": "Cluster accounting information."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the priority level of the 'normal' QoS according to the sacctmgr command?",
        "answer": "0."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum wall time for the 'gpu' QoS as listed by the sacctmgr command?",
        "answer": "08:00:00."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the node state of 'tron02' and how many cores does it have?",
        "answer": "The state of 'tron02' is 'idle' and it has 16 cores."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/NASProjects",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What protocols are used by UMIACS labs to distribute shared data to workgroups?",
        "answer": "UMIACS labs distribute shared data to workgroups using a wide variety of protocols including FTP, SFTP, SCP, NFS, and SMB."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can on-site clients access project directories?",
        "answer": "On-site clients can access project directories through the Network File System (NFS) and Server Message Block (SMB) protocols."
      },
      {
        "question": "What mapping does supported UNIX workstations use for project directories?",
        "answer": "Supported UNIX workstations map project directories to /fs/."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the directory path structure for Windows workstations accessing project directories?",
        "answer": "Windows workstations map project directories as \\*.umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the directory path for accessing directories on the Isilon?",
        "answer": "For directories on the Isilon, the path would be \\isilondata.umiacs.umd.edu\\."
      },
      {
        "question": "Is project data storage shared by default with every host?",
        "answer": "No, project data storage may not be shared by default with every host."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action should one take to configure a new share for project data?",
        "answer": "Please send mail to staff to configure a new share."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the guidelines regarding the storage of personal data in project storage allocations?",
        "answer": "The guidelines advise avoiding storing personal data in project storage allocations."
      },
      {
        "question": "Why is it recommended to separate project data from personal data?",
        "answer": "Separating project data from personal data will simplify administration and data management for both researchers and staff."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Network/Troubleshooting",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command should be used on Windows to check the IP address configuration?",
        "answer": "type ipconfig /all into the command prompt."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the PING utility?",
        "answer": "PING is a network utility that sends ICMP packets to a specified host to test network connectivity."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you specify the number of times to ping a destination host on Linux/UNIX?",
        "answer": "You may want to add the -c flag followed by a number to specify how many times to ping the destination host."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used on Windows to perform a traceroute?",
        "answer": "In a command prompt type 'tracert' followed by the hostname or IP address of the host."
      },
      {
        "question": "What might be a reason for networking issues if your IP address is manually set?",
        "answer": "If your machine happens to have a manually set IP address that conflicts with that of another host, networking issues may arise."
      },
      {
        "question": "What option could help if you are behind a firewall and having trouble accessing a service?",
        "answer": "You can connect to the VPN, or use SSH tunneling."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which two publicly accessible Nexus hosts are suggested for testing connectivity when experiencing trouble connecting to UMIACS services?",
        "answer": "nexuscml00.umiacs.umd.edu or nexuscfar00.umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What utility performs DNS lookups and displays the answers from the name server(s)?",
        "answer": "dig."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command shows network status on macOS/Linux/UNIX?",
        "answer": "netstat."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command shows network routing tables on Windows?",
        "answer": "route print."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Lamsub.sh",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What kind of script is Lamsub.sh based on?",
        "answer": "Bash script"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum wall time set in the script?",
        "answer": "0:10:0"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many nodes are specified for use in the script?",
        "answer": "8"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to modify the PATH in the script?",
        "answer": "export PATH=/usr/local/stow/lam-7.1.4/bin:$PATH"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which executable is called within the script for running a parallel job?",
        "answer": "/usr/local/stow/lam-7.1.4/bin/mpiexec"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is the machinefile referenced in the script located?",
        "answer": "${PBS_NODEFILE}"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is echoed at the start of the script?",
        "answer": "starting"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is echoed at the end of the script?",
        "answer": "ending"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which directory contains the executable being run by mpiexec?",
        "answer": "/nfshomes/xhe/torquejobs/lamtest/"
      },
      {
        "question": "What specific version of LAM is being referenced in the script?",
        "answer": "7.1.4"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/URL",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What does the acronym URL stand for?",
        "answer": "Uniform Resource Locator"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is an example of a common protocol used in a URL?",
        "answer": "http://, https:// or ftp://"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does 'dns.address' in a URL represent?",
        "answer": "Either a fully qualified domain name (FQDN) or a short domain name if the local name service resolver is configured to try certain subdomains."
      },
      {
        "question": "Is the ':port' section of a URL optional, and what type of value is it?",
        "answer": "Yes, ':port' is optional and is always a numeric value."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does 'file:/' indicate when used in a URL?",
        "answer": "It refers to the root of the local file system."
      },
      {
        "question": "Is it common to see path information appended to a URL?",
        "answer": "Yes, most of the time you will see some path information appended to a URL."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Ubuntu/SoftwareCenter",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary function of the Ubuntu Software Center?",
        "answer": "The Ubuntu Software Center provides a mechanism to install many different applications and libraries to your Ubuntu desktop without requiring 'su' or 'sudo' (administrative) access."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a primary user of a UMIACS-supported Ubuntu machine do if they do not have adequate permissions to install software?",
        "answer": "They should contact staff and provide both their hostname and username."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user launch the Ubuntu Software Center using the Dashboard?",
        "answer": "By typing the meta key (commonly referred to as the Windows key) to open the dashboard and then typing 'Software Center' in the search box."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used in the terminal to launch the Ubuntu Software Center?",
        "answer": "'software-center' should be typed in the terminal to launch the Ubuntu Software Center."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is a limitation of using the Ubuntu Software Center via X11 Forwarding?",
        "answer": "The Ubuntu Software Center cannot be used via X11 Forwarding due to limitations, and updates must be done on the physical machine."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/OptLocal",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the preferred method of providing locally-built software to the Institute?",
        "answer": "Modules is now the preferred method of providing locally-built software to the Institute."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to manage the /opt/local directory?",
        "answer": "The Stow system is used to manage the /opt/local directory."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you list a specific piece of software under /opt/local?",
        "answer": "You can list the directory /opt/local/stow for a specific piece of software."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which directories are linked with the stow command for software?",
        "answer": "The stow command links software directly into the bin, lib, man, and sbin directories in /opt/local."
      },
      {
        "question": "For which versions of the operating system does this information pertain?",
        "answer": "This information pertains to RHEL7 and above."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where was software previously found before it was managed in /opt/local?",
        "answer": "Software was previously found in /usr/local."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Network/VPN/Linux",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the prerequisites for accessing the UMIACS VPN?",
        "answer": "A full UMIACS account, a device enrolled with UMIACS Duo for multi-factor authentication, and an established network connection (wired or wireless)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Pulse Secure Client versions are available for different Linux distributions?",
        "answer": "64 bit Pulse Secure Client .deb for Debian-based Linux (e.g. Ubuntu) and 64 bit Pulse Secure Client .rpm for Fedora-based Linux (e.g. Red Hat)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do upon starting the Pulse Secure Client for the first time?",
        "answer": "It may ask to upgrade the client, which will pull an up-to-date version of the client with the most recent configuration."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to install the Pulse Secure Client on a Debian-based OS?",
        "answer": "sudo dpkg -i <insert_filename_here>.deb"
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional packages must be installed before proceeding with the installation on a Debian-based OS?",
        "answer": "libnss3-tools and net-tools."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the server URL that needs to be entered when creating a new VPN connection?",
        "answer": "vpn.umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What options are provided for the secondary password when connecting to the VPN?",
        "answer": "push, phone, or <press YubiKey>."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if they want to register a YubiKey for use with the VPN?",
        "answer": "Contact UMIACS Tech Staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user select on the secondary authentication prompt to use their preferred method automatically?",
        "answer": "'Save Settings'."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user check the VPN connection status?",
        "answer": "Launch the Pulse Client GUI and select the down arrow to show connection status."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/BitLocker/PersonalUse",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What types of hard drives can BitLocker be used on?",
        "answer": "BitLocker can be used on fixed hard drives (i.e. internal to your computer) as well as on portable hard drives (i.e. USB)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the preferred file system format for a portable hard drive needed for BitLocker?",
        "answer": "The preferred file system format for a portable hard drive needed for BitLocker is NTFS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be installed on the machine before initializing the YubiKey for encryption?",
        "answer": "The YubiKey personalization tool must be downloaded and installed on the machine before initializing the YubiKey for encryption."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the recovery key in BitLocker?",
        "answer": "The recovery key is the only way to get into the encrypted drive if you lose the YubiKey."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be done with the recovery key text file after adding it to the database in KeePassXC?",
        "answer": "The recovery key text file should be deleted permanently after adding it to the database in KeePassXC."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the auto-unlock feature do in BitLocker?",
        "answer": "The auto-unlock feature allows an encrypted drive to auto-unlock for specific user(s) when plugged into specific computer(s)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is a strongly recommended practice regarding the management of USB flash drives containing the recovery key?",
        "answer": "It is strongly recommended to copy the contents of the first USB flash drive onto one or more additional USB flash drives to safeguard against loss of both the YubiKey and any single USB flash drive."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does a user unlock the drive using the YubiKey?",
        "answer": "To unlock the drive using the YubiKey, the user should physically plug the drive and YubiKey in, then touch the YubiKey's sensor for 3 seconds to emit the password, which will automatically unlock the drive."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does BitLocker recommend doing before disconnecting the portable hard drive from the machine?",
        "answer": "BitLocker recommends waiting for encryption to complete before disconnecting the portable hard drive from the machine."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if a user loses their YubiKey according to the instructions provided?",
        "answer": "If a user loses their YubiKey, it is strongly recommended to buy a new YubiKey, decrypt BitLocker on the drive, and then repeat the initial procedure to re-encrypt it with the new YubiKey."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/InputMethodEditors",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of input method editors (IMEs)?",
        "answer": "IMEs make it easier to type in languages that are made up of thousands of characters that can't fit on a standard keyboard."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is indicated about the nature of IMEs in relation to user privileges?",
        "answer": "IMEs are a per user setting and can be added/removed/customized without any need for administrative privileges."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step in adding an IME to your account according to the instructions?",
        "answer": "Click the Windows button and open the control panel."
      },
      {
        "question": "After opening the control panel, which option should be selected to change input methods?",
        "answer": "Click 'Clock, Language, and Region'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action should you take after clicking 'Change keyboards or other input methods'?",
        "answer": "Click the 'Change Keyboards' button."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you identify which IMEs are currently installed on your system?",
        "answer": "A dialogue box will open with a list of your currently installed input methods (aka keyboards)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do after clicking the 'Add' button in the input methods dialogue box?",
        "answer": "Another dialogue box will open with a list of languages; scroll through these until you find the language you want to add."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional step is required to enable an IME for a specific language?",
        "answer": "Check any of the IMEs that you want to enable and then click the 'Ok' button."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the significance of clicking 'Apply' after making changes to the IMEs?",
        "answer": "Click 'Apply' to close the dialogue box and apply your changes."
      },
      {
        "question": "What new feature appears if this is the first time an IME has been added?",
        "answer": "A new icon should appear in the bottom right corner of your screen near the taskbar that allows you to switch between IMEs and configure them."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can users access help pages or configure their IMEs?",
        "answer": "Click the Options Menu icon on the right side of the language bar."
      }
    ],
    "total": 11
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Lamsub.sh.o127",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the error message received at the beginning of the text?",
        "answer": "Warning: no access to tty (Bad file descriptor)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What rank is responsible for sending the message '0' to rank 1?",
        "answer": "Rank 0."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many total ranks are involved in sending and receiving messages as per the text?",
        "answer": "Eight ranks (from rank 0 to rank 7)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which rank finishes its operations last according to the provided information?",
        "answer": "Rank 7."
      },
      {
        "question": "During the messaging process, what does Rank 2 do when it receives message '4' from rank 4?",
        "answer": "Rank 2 sends message '2' to rank 4."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does Rank 5 do upon receiving message '2' from rank 2?",
        "answer": "Rank 5 sends message '5' to rank 2."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ranks do not send messages to themselves according to the messaging operations described?",
        "answer": "Ranks 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, and 7 all do not send messages to themselves."
      },
      {
        "question": "In the context of the message-passing operation, what does Rank 3 do when it receives message '6' from rank 6?",
        "answer": "Rank 3 sends message '3' to rank 6."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Modules",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command is used to check the availability of software in the module system?",
        "answer": "module avail"
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens when a user runs the module add command without specifying a version for a piece of software that has no default version?",
        "answer": "They will load the most recent version of it."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command would you use to list the currently loaded modules in your environment?",
        "answer": "module list"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the show command do in relation to a specific module?",
        "answer": "It shows what the module is going to add to your environment and the dependencies that will be added."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command can be used to remove a module from your environment?",
        "answer": "module rm <module>"
      },
      {
        "question": "In non-interactive shell sessions, why might the Modules configuration environment not load automatically?",
        "answer": "Because the OS version of the compute node scheduled differs from the OS version of the submission node."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are users advised to do to get the module command to work in RHEL9 desktop sessions?",
        "answer": "Source the modules init script."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which shell family does the Modules system automatically customize the environment for?",
        "answer": "bash/sh (default shell) and tcsh/csh."
      },
      {
        "question": "If a piece of software has a default version, how is it indicated in the output of module avail?",
        "answer": "By (default) coming after their name/version."
      },
      {
        "question": "What paths are prepended to the environment variables when loading the cuda/12.1.1 module?",
        "answer": "PATH, LD_LIBRARY_PATH, LD_RUN_PATH, LIBRARY_PATH, CPATH, PKG_CONFIG_PATH."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Compute/DataLocality",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is recommended for storing data that is actively being worked on in the context of a cluster job?",
        "answer": "It is recommended to store data that is actively being worked on as close to the processing source as possible, specifically on a disk physically installed in the compute node itself."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step in the suggested workflow for a computational job?",
        "answer": "The first step is to copy the data to be processed to local disk space of the compute node(s) your job is assigned."
      },
      {
        "question": "Why is it important to utilize local disks on compute nodes during cluster jobs?",
        "answer": "Utilizing the local disks on the compute nodes helps distribute the data access load and reduce the load on the file server, improving performance."
      },
      {
        "question": "List two benefits of storing data in an archive file when not actively being processed.",
        "answer": "Two benefits are faster data transfers and reduced data size."
      },
      {
        "question": "What common utilities can be used to create archive files?",
        "answer": "Common utilities for creating archive files are tar and zip."
      },
      {
        "question": "What naming convention does local disk space at UMIACS typically follow?",
        "answer": "Local disk space typically conforms to the guideline where the directory name starts with /scratch."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if they have questions about the available local disk space on a given cluster?",
        "answer": "The user should refer to the documentation specific for that cluster or contact the UMIACS Help Desk."
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are local disk spaces considered transitory in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Local disk space is considered transitory and is not backed up, making it not intended for long-term storage of critical/sensitive data."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/NAS",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What does NAS stand for in the context of this document?",
        "answer": "Network Attached Storage"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two categories of Network Attached Storage mentioned?",
        "answer": "Network Attached Storage for Users and Network Attached Storage for Projects"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the NAS as described in the text?",
        "answer": "To provide storage solutions for users and projects."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Accounts/Collaborator",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of account is a Collaborator account?",
        "answer": "A Collaborator account is a sponsored provisional account for non-UMIACS members."
      },
      {
        "question": "What access do Collaborator accounts provide?",
        "answer": "Collaborator accounts provide access to UMIACS applications such as GitLab, Object Storage, and MediaWiki instances."
      },
      {
        "question": "Do Collaborator accounts provide login access to UMIACS computers?",
        "answer": "No, Collaborator accounts do not provide login access to UMIACS computers."
      },
      {
        "question": "How is access to a group's resources managed for Collaborator accounts?",
        "answer": "Access to a group's resources is mediated through Security Groups, which can be managed in the UMIACS Directory Application."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required for a Collaborator account to be created?",
        "answer": "A UMIACS Account holder has to sponsor the Collaborator Account."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where do you go to sponsor a Collaborator account?",
        "answer": "Sponsorship is done in the UMIACS Requests Application."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens once a Collaborator has created their account?",
        "answer": "An email will be sent to both the account sponsor and the Collaborator that the account is ready to use."
      },
      {
        "question": "What management actions are available for a sponsor regarding their Collaborators?",
        "answer": "The following management actions are available: Send Password Reset and Remove Sponsorship."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'Take Over Sponsorship' action do?",
        "answer": "It notifies staff to transfer sponsorship to the requester, and the original sponsor of the Collaborator will be notified."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Network/VPN/Windows",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary client used to access the UMIACS VPN?",
        "answer": "Ivanti Connect Secure Client."
      },
      {
        "question": "What alternative method can be used to establish a UMIACS VPN connection if the primary client is unavailable?",
        "answer": "A web browser at the URL https://vpn.umiacs.umd.edu/"
      },
      {
        "question": "What specific requirement is mentioned for computers with ARM-based processors?",
        "answer": "They require a different installer than the standard Windows one."
      },
      {
        "question": "List the prerequisites needed to connect to the UMIACS VPN.",
        "answer": "A full UMIACS account, device enrolled with UMIACS Duo for multi-factor authentication, and an established network connection (wired or wireless)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do if prompted to upgrade the Ivanti Secure client upon starting it for the first time?",
        "answer": "They should allow it to pull an up-to-date version of the client with the most recent configuration."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be entered in the server URL field when creating a new VPN connection?",
        "answer": "vpn.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "How does the multi-factor authentication system for the Pulse VPN work?",
        "answer": "It prompts for credentials twice, requiring a secondary password for MFA, which could be a push notification, a call verification, or a one-time password from a YubiKey."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do to register a YubiKey for use with the VPN?",
        "answer": "They should contact UMIACS Tech Staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "What icon indicates a successful connection to the UMIACS VPN in the status bar?",
        "answer": "An S icon with a green arrow."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if there is no icon or a different icon in the status bar?",
        "answer": "It means the user is not connected."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is stated about the support for 32-bit clients?",
        "answer": "32-bit clients are no longer supported by Ivanti."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users select on the secondary authentication prompt to save time for future logins?",
        "answer": "Select ‘Save Settings’."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which version of the Pulse Secure client needs to be downloaded for ARM processors?",
        "answer": "Windows 64 bit ARM Pulse Secure Client."
      }
    ],
    "total": 13
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/NAGWareCompiler",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "Where can the NAGWare Fortran compiler be found on supported RHEL7/Ubuntu hosts?",
        "answer": "/opt/common/NAGWare_f95*"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the suggested method for loading the NAGWare compiler binaries into the environment?",
        "answer": "Using GNU Modules"
      },
      {
        "question": "What file must be created to perform the Hello World example using the NAGWare Fortran compiler?",
        "answer": "hello.f95"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to load the NAGWare modules into the environment?",
        "answer": "module load nagware"
      },
      {
        "question": "What output is expected when the Hello World program is run after compilation?",
        "answer": "Hello World!"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command compiles the Hello World program using the NAGWare Fortran compiler?",
        "answer": "f95 -o hello hello.f95"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to verify that the compiler is in the path after loading the NAGWare modules?",
        "answer": "which f95"
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/OSSupport",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "List the versions of Red Hat Enterprise Linux supported by UMIACS.",
        "answer": "Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7, Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8, Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Windows operating systems are supported by UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Windows 10 / Windows Server 2022, Windows 11"
      },
      {
        "question": "Identify the macOS versions that UMIACS supports.",
        "answer": "macOS 13.x, macOS 14.x, macOS 15.x"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many versions of Red Hat Enterprise Linux does UMIACS support?",
        "answer": "Three versions: Red Hat Enterprise Linux 7, Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8, and Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the highest version of macOS supported by UMIACS as per the document?",
        "answer": "macOS 15.x"
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Accounts",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the two main components of a full UMIACS account?",
        "answer": "Active Directory Account and Jira Account."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required to fill out the UMIACS account request form?",
        "answer": "You need to enter your PI/Professor/Sponsor's account name and indicate any labs you are a member of in the notes field."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the minimum password length required for Active Directory passwords at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The minimum password length is 8 characters."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does one change their Jira password?",
        "answer": "Changing your Jira password does not change your Active Directory Account password, and it can be set separately."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if you forget your UMIACS password?",
        "answer": "You must reset it using the UMIACS Password Web Application."
      },
      {
        "question": "What conditions must be met to reset your password if you do not know your current password?",
        "answer": "You must know your username and have already registered a mobile phone number and alternate E-mail address in the Directory Application."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the procedure if a UMIACS Collaborator Account password needs to be reset?",
        "answer": "The password can be reset by your sponsor via the Requests Application."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one of the password security policies regarding previously used passwords?",
        "answer": "The password cannot be one that was previously used in your last 10 passwords."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can a sponsor do regarding the accounts they sponsor?",
        "answer": "They can view a list of the accounts they sponsor and manage details such as installation date or email forward."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action is required to secure a password according to UMIACS policy?",
        "answer": "It is your responsibility to secure your password, not to use your UMIACS password for any other service, and to connect using secure protocols."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ClassAccounts",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of UMIACS Class Accounts?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Class Accounts support classes for all of UMIACS/CSD via the Nexus cluster."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must students do if they do not receive an account notification email after their TA or instructor requests an account?",
        "answer": "They must contact their TA or instructor."
      },
      {
        "question": "How long do students have to redeem their account before the redemption token expires?",
        "answer": "Students must redeem the account within 7 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required for logging onto the class submission host after account installation?",
        "answer": "Students must register for MFA (multi-factor authentication) under UMIACS's Duo instance."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the location of a student’s home directory in UMIACS Class Accounts?",
        "answer": "/fs/classhomes/<semester><year>/<coursecode>/<username>"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum quota for a student's home directory?",
        "answer": "The maximum quota for a student's home directory is 30GB."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a student request additional personal storage beyond the 30GB quota?",
        "answer": "A student can request up to another 100GB of personal storage by having their TA or instructor contact staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the method of job scheduling that UMIACS Class Accounts must use for computational jobs?",
        "answer": "Students must schedule their jobs with the SLURM workload manager."
      },
      {
        "question": "What submission parameters can Class accounts access in SLURM?",
        "answer": "--partition - class, --account - class, --qos - default, medium, and high."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the correct command to view the available nodes in the class partition using SLURM?",
        "answer": "The correct command is 'show_nodes -p class'."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Bash",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the two main configuration files used by Bash?",
        "answer": "~/.bash_profile and ~/.bashrc"
      },
      {
        "question": "In which type of shell is ~/.bash_profile used?",
        "answer": "Login shells (ssh, console)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which configuration file is used by interactive shells in X?",
        "answer": "~/.bashrc"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you access a complete explanation of Bash features?",
        "answer": "By typing man bash"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can you type in the terminal to view your current paths?",
        "answer": "echo $PATH"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you add an additional path to your current PATH in Bash?",
        "answer": "By using the command export PATH=${PATH}:/the/new/path"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the order of paths in the PATH variable affect?",
        "answer": "It controls the order that programs are found in your path."
      },
      {
        "question": "What format is the list of current paths displayed in when using echo $PATH?",
        "answer": "Colon separated list"
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MediaSanitization",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What types of data storage devices does UMIACS Staff securely destroy?",
        "answer": "Hard drives, USB sticks, CD/DVDs."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which service is used by UMIACS to securely destroy data storage devices?",
        "answer": "The Storage Device Destruction Service."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can one find more information about the Storage Device Destruction Service?",
        "answer": "At the link provided, https://umd.service-now.com/itsupport?id=kb_article&article=KB0011509&sys_kb_id=94b4f34a37275200a90963d2b3990eaf."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if you want a device securely destroyed at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Stop by the help desk to have the device placed in the pile for mass destruction dropoff."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the University's Data Retention Guidelines related to?",
        "answer": "They are related to the destruction of university-owned data storage devices."
      },
      {
        "question": "What method of destruction is always recommended when destroying a data storage device?",
        "answer": "Physical destruction."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which organization's guidelines are recommended for data storage device destruction?",
        "answer": "NIST (National Institute of Standards and Technology)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should one adhere to when physically destroying a university-owned data storage device?",
        "answer": "Guidelines published by NIST."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can the guidelines published by NIST for media sanitization be found?",
        "answer": "At the link provided, https://nvlpubs.nist.gov/nistpubs/specialpublications/nist.sp.800-88r1.pdf."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Nexus/GPUs",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the architecture of the H100 NVLink GPU?",
        "answer": "Hopper"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many CUDA cores does the RTX 6000 Ada Generation have?",
        "answer": "1817"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of memory does the A100 PCIe 80GB use?",
        "answer": "HBM2e"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the memory bandwidth of the Tesla P100 GPU?",
        "answer": "732 GB/s"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which GPU has the highest memory bandwidth listed?",
        "answer": "H100 NVLink"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much FP32 performance does the RTX A6000 provide?",
        "answer": "38.7 TFLOPS"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the GRES string for the GeForce RTX 3090?",
        "answer": "rtx3090"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which architecture does the GeForce RTX 2080 Ti belong to?",
        "answer": "Turing"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the number of GB of memory for the RTX A5000?",
        "answer": "24 GB"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many physical cards are connected over NVLink for the H100 NVLink GPU?",
        "answer": "Two"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/BarracudaSpamFirewall",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "How many Barracuda Networks spam firewalls has UMIACS deployed?",
        "answer": "UMIACS has deployed a system with 2 Barracuda Networks spam firewalls."
      },
      {
        "question": "What email format should users use to log in to the Barracuda spam firewalls?",
        "answer": "Users should log in using their UMIACS email address in the format username@umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will users receive daily at approximately 3:30 PM EST from the Barracuda?",
        "answer": "Users will receive a mail with their quarantine summary."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to the quarantine mail after 21 days?",
        "answer": "Mail held in quarantine for longer than 21 days will be purged."
      },
      {
        "question": "What do Barracuda spam firewalls do with messages that pass through them?",
        "answer": "The Barracudas will score every message that passes through them and inject varying message headers based on that score."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can users find the guide to enable quarantine passthrough?",
        "answer": "Users can find the guide to enable quarantine passthrough at BarracudaSpamFirewall/QuarantinePassthrough."
      },
      {
        "question": "What filtering options can be set up through the Preferences tab in the Barracuda web portal?",
        "answer": "Users can set up whitelists, blacklists, and Bayesian filtering options through the Preferences tab."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action must users take if they receive a security warning in their browser after clicking the Barracuda link?",
        "answer": "Users may need to add the UMIACS Certificate Authority."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can users search their spam quarantine?",
        "answer": "Users can search their spam quarantine by following the steps at BarracudaSpamFirewall/SearchingQuarantine."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do to log in if the auto log-in through the daily summary link is not working?",
        "answer": "Users should use the links provided above to log in."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/LabFacilities",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the full name of the CBCB lab?",
        "answer": "Center for Bioinformatics and Computational Biology"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which lab focuses on health-related informatics and bioimaging?",
        "answer": "Center for Health-related Informatics and Bioimaging"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the abbreviation CfAR stand for?",
        "answer": "Center for Automation Research"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which laboratory is associated with machine learning?",
        "answer": "Center for Machine Learning"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Distributed Systems Software Laboratory (DSSL)?",
        "answer": "The text does not specify the purpose, but it is inferred to be focused on distributed systems software."
      },
      {
        "question": "Name one laboratory that deals with human-computer interaction.",
        "answer": "Human Computer Interaction Laboratory (HCIL)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which lab has a focus on computational linguistics?",
        "answer": "Computational Linguistics and Information Processing (CLIP)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the link to the Maryland Cybersecurity Center?",
        "answer": "http://cyber.umd.edu/"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which lab is affiliated with quantum information and computer science?",
        "answer": "Joint Center for Quantum Information and Computer Science (QUICS)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which laboratory corresponds to the abbreviation MAXWell?",
        "answer": "Lab for Broadband Mobile Communications"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Nexus",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary function of the Nexus in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The Nexus is the combined scheduler of resources in UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which resource manager is used for Nexus?",
        "answer": "The resource manager for Nexus is SLURM."
      },
      {
        "question": "What determines access to submission nodes for Nexus computational resources?",
        "answer": "Your access to submission nodes for Nexus computational resources is determined by your account sponsor's department, center, or lab affiliation."
      },
      {
        "question": "How are SLURM jobs submitted for both interactive and batch jobs?",
        "answer": "SLURM jobs are submitted by either srun for interactive jobs or sbatch for batch jobs."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum wall time per job for the default job QoS in Nexus?",
        "answer": "The maximum wall time per job for the default job QoS is 3 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "What limitations do jobs in the scavenger partition have?",
        "answer": "Jobs in the scavenger partition have no resource limits per job, only a maximum wall time per job of 3 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "What kind of storage do users have available in their home directories in Nexus?",
        "answer": "Users have 30GB of home directory storage available at /nfshomes/<username>."
      },
      {
        "question": "How much scratch space is allocated to users via NFS from /fs/nexus-scratch/<USERNAME>?",
        "answer": "Users are allocated 200GB of scratch space via NFS from /fs/nexus-scratch/<USERNAME>."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of backups and snapshots are available for project allocations in Nexus?",
        "answer": "Project storage is fully protected, has snapshots enabled, and is backed up nightly."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to check the quota usage of your scratch space?",
        "answer": "You can view your quota usage by running df -h /fs/nexus-scratch/<USERNAME>."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Network/VPN/MFA",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the mandatory requirement for using the Pulse Secure VPN as of May 10th, 2019?",
        "answer": "Enabling Multi Factor Authentication (MFA) is mandatory as of May 10th, 2019."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two credentials you need to provide when using the Pulse VPN multi-factor authentication?",
        "answer": "The first credential is the UMIACS password, and the second credential is your preferred MFA verification option."
      },
      {
        "question": "What verification option do you use if you have a physical YubiKey token?",
        "answer": "You would press the YubiKey for the one time password."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must you do to register a YubiKey for use with the VPN?",
        "answer": "You must contact the UMIACS Tech Staff to program the YubiKey for you."
      },
      {
        "question": "Can you register hardware tokens other than YubiKeys for MFA with the VPN?",
        "answer": "No, UMIACS only supports registering YubiKey tokens for this purpose; no other hardware token is supported."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should be followed to configure MFA with the Pulse VPN?",
        "answer": "Connect with your existing Pulse VPN profile, enter your UMIACS credentials for the first authentication box, tick 'Save settings', type 'push' into the password field on the second authentication box, tick 'Save settings', and then click Connect."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will happen after you complete the MFA setup with the Pulse VPN in terms of future connections?",
        "answer": "You should receive a push to your mobile device to complete authentication every time you connect to the VPN going forward."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SSH/Keys",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are SSH keys primarily used for in the context of authentication and authorization?",
        "answer": "SSH can utilize public key encryption to authenticate and authorize users."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the recommended action to secure a private key when using SSH?",
        "answer": "The private key should be secured with a pass-phrase."
      },
      {
        "question": "In what scenario are SSH keys more secure than normal passwords?",
        "answer": "SSH keys are considered more secure than normal passwords over SSH."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of an SSH Agent according to the text?",
        "answer": "SSH Agents allow you to temporarily use your SSH key without a password for a set period of time."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be done to the permissions of the .ssh directory and the private key file?",
        "answer": "The permissions of the .ssh directory should be set to 700, and the private key file should be set to 600."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to generate a new SSH key pair without a pass-phrase?",
        "answer": "The command ssh-keygen -t rsa -N \"\" can be used to generate a new key without a pass-phrase."
      },
      {
        "question": "What information must be provided when using ssh-keygen to create a key pair?",
        "answer": "It will prompt you for a file to create the private key and then for the public key append .pub extension."
      },
      {
        "question": "What warning is given regarding the private key after its creation?",
        "answer": "Allowing anyone to read this private key will compromise the security of the key and could allow someone to access any resources secured by this key without your consent."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can the public key be copied to a remote host according to the provided information?",
        "answer": "The public key can be copied to a remote host using the ssh-copy-id command."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must you do before creating a new key if you are using batch clusters?",
        "answer": "If using batch clusters, please read the Batch clusters section prior to creating a new key."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SetUID",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of SetUID in UNIX?",
        "answer": "SetUID is useful for programs that need root level privileges in UNIX."
      }
    ],
    "total": 1
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/UMobj/Example",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command is used to export the object store credentials?",
        "answer": "export OBJ_ACCESS_KEY_ID=\"<ACCESS_KEY>\" export OBJ_SECRET_ACCESS_KEY=\"<SECRET_KEY>\" export OBJ_SERVER=\"obj.umiacs.umd.edu\""
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the size of the file 'CASIA-WebFace.tar.gz'?",
        "answer": "4.4GB"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to create a new bucket named 'janus_datasets'?",
        "answer": "# mkobj janus_datasets:"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to copy 'CASIA-WebFace.tar.gz' to the bucket 'janus_datasets'?",
        "answer": "# cpobj CASIA-WebFace.tar.gz janus_datasets:"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to calculate the md5sum of 'CASIA-WebFace.tar.gz' locally?",
        "answer": "# md5sum CASIA-WebFace.tar.gz"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to compare the checksums between the local file and the object store?",
        "answer": "# cmpobj janus_datasets:CASIA-WebFace.tar.gz"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should the local md5sum and the md5sum from the object store do?",
        "answer": "They should match."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Quota",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command is used to find out the current quota of a user in an Isilon NAS file system?",
        "answer": "quota"
      },
      {
        "question": "What percentage of the file system was used in the example output of the df command?",
        "answer": "1%"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the Use% represent in the df command output?",
        "answer": "The Use% here is for the entire file system and not your user-specific home directory."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if they encounter an error like 'Error while getting quota from ...'?",
        "answer": "They may safely ignore these errors as some of the file systems do not report quotas correctly."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of errors may occur if a user hits their RPC quota?",
        "answer": "Some applications like vi may throw 'FSync' errors, and commands like wget may succeed but produce zero-length files."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command can be used to diagnose how much space is being used in the directories?",
        "answer": "du"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user show their home directory quota?",
        "answer": "By using the df command with the argument ~."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which operating systems use the concept of .. for the previous directory in the context of calculating space usage?",
        "answer": "*NIX operating systems"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command example shows how to identify all files and directories from the current directory while considering hidden files?",
        "answer": "du -hs .[^.]* *."
      },
      {
        "question": "In the example of the du command output, how much storage is used by the Downloads directory?",
        "answer": "57M"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/CompromisedPasswordFiltering",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What organization’s best practices does UMIACS follow regarding password usage?",
        "answer": "UMIACS follows the best practices recommended by NIST."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does UMIACS prohibit with respect to passwords?",
        "answer": "UMIACS prohibits the use of passwords that have been included in a known data breach."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does UMIACS verify the validity of a new password?",
        "answer": "UMIACS checks that a new password is not among hundreds of millions of compromised passwords."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the data source used by UMIACS for checking compromised passwords?",
        "answer": "UMIACS uses the Have I Been Pwned (HIBP) corpus of passwords as the data source."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many compromised passwords does UMIACS check against?",
        "answer": "UMIACS checks against hundreds of millions of compromised passwords."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/UpdatingMozillaSoftware",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the recommended action to take regarding browser and email client updates to combat security flaws?",
        "answer": "It is important to keep your browser and email clients up-to-date."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you find installers and documentation for the latest versions of Firefox and Thunderbird?",
        "answer": "At the URLs: Firefox: http://www.getfirefox.com and Thunderbird: http://www.getthunderbird.com."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you determine what version of Firefox or Thunderbird is installed on your computer?",
        "answer": "By opening the application and choosing 'Help > About Mozilla [application]' on Windows or 'Firefox > About [application]' on macOS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should you follow to enable automatic updates for Mozilla Firefox if it is currently disabled?",
        "answer": "Navigate to options (Windows) or preferences (Mac), go to the Firefox Updates section, and enable the option to 'Automatically install updates'."
      },
      {
        "question": "If you want to check for updates manually in Mozilla Firefox, what is the first step?",
        "answer": "Navigate to options (Windows) or preferences (Mac)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What button must be clicked to update Firefox manually after confirming an available update?",
        "answer": "'Restart to Update' button (Windows and Mac)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps are required to enable automatic updates for Mozilla Thunderbird?",
        "answer": "Navigate to options (Windows) or preferences (Mac), go to the advanced tab, then navigate to updates, and enable 'Automatically install updates'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must you do if Thunderbird refuses to update using the described methods?",
        "answer": "Visit the HelpDesk for assistance from a technician."
      },
      {
        "question": "What alternative actions can be taken if auto-update is not desired in Thunderbird?",
        "answer": "Navigate to help->about Thunderbird and click the check for updates button."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Nexus/Vulcan",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "When did the compute nodes from Vulcan's previous standalone cluster fold into Nexus?",
        "answer": "The compute nodes from Vulcan's previous standalone cluster have folded into Nexus as of the scheduled maintenance window for August 2023, specifically on Thursday 08/17/2023, 5-8pm."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the actual submission host names for logging into the Nexus cluster?",
        "answer": "The actual submission hosts are nexusvulcan00.umiacs.umd.edu and nexusvulcan01.umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What prefix is prepended to all job parameters that were present in the standalone Vulcan cluster when moved to Nexus?",
        "answer": "The prefix 'vulcan-' is prepended to all of the values that were present in the standalone Vulcan cluster."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum number of jobs a user can submit simultaneously in the Vulcan partition?",
        "answer": "The max submission limit is 500 jobs per user simultaneously."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many GPU nodes are available in the Vulcan compute infrastructure, and what types of graphics cards do they run?",
        "answer": "There are currently 46 GPU nodes available running a mixture of NVIDIA RTX A6000, A5000, A4000, Quadro P6000, GeForce GTX 1080 Ti, RTX 2080 Ti, and Tesla P100 cards."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the roles of the 'vulcan-dpart' and 'vulcan-scavenger' partitions?",
        "answer": "The 'vulcan-dpart' partition is the default partition where job allocations are guaranteed, while the 'vulcan-scavenger' partition allows jobs longer run times and more resources but is preemptable when jobs in other vulcan- partitions are ready to be scheduled."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the storage limit for home directories, and what type of data should be stored there?",
        "answer": "You have 30GB of home directory storage available at /nfshomes/<username>, which is intended to store personal or configuration files only."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command would you use to view your account associations in the SLURM system?",
        "answer": "$ show_assoc"
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens after you request a temporary increase of scratch storage space beyond 300GB?",
        "answer": "You will be contacted and given a one-week window of opportunity to clean and secure your data before staff will forcibly remove data to get your space back under 300GB."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required for faculty to manage user access in the Vulcan infrastructure?",
        "answer": "Faculty can manage this list of users via the Directory application in the Security Groups section, with the security group having the prefix 'vulcan_' followed by the faculty username."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Perl/Environment",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of using local::lib in the Perl environment?",
        "answer": "It creates an isolated collection of packages that will not affect the system version of Perl."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to creating a Perl environment as mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "You will first need to download a copy of local::lib."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to decompress and extract the local-lib package?",
        "answer": "The command is 'gunzip local-lib-2.000019.tar.gz' followed by 'tar xvf local-lib-2.000019.tar'."
      },
      {
        "question": "After configuring local::lib, which command should be run to install the environment?",
        "answer": "The command is 'make test && make install'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should be added to the .bashrc file to initialize the new Perl environment?",
        "answer": "The command to add is 'echo 'eval $(perl -I$HOME/perl5/lib/perl5 -Mlocal::lib)' >>~/.bashrc'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional file may require the initialization line for the Perl environment aside from .bashrc?",
        "answer": ".bash_profile may also require the initialization line."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command installs a package once the environment is created and properly sourced?",
        "answer": "'cpan -i Date::Tolkien::Shire' is the command used to install a package."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command lists all the Perl Modules installed in the currently sourced environment?",
        "answer": "'perldoc perllocal' is the command that lists all installed Perl Modules."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is the default directory for creating the Perl environment?",
        "answer": "By default, the environment is created in the ~/perl5 directory."
      },
      {
        "question": "What modification is needed to create additional environments in a different directory?",
        "answer": "You need to specify a directory while building the environment using the command 'perl Makefile.PL --bootstrap=/Path/to/Second/Environment'."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/UsrLocal",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the preferred method for providing locally-built software to the Institute according to the text?",
        "answer": "Modules"
      },
      {
        "question": "How is /usr/local managed as mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "Via a Stow system"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to link some software directly into the bin, lib, man, and sbin directories in /usr/local?",
        "answer": "stow command"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where will the software be moving from and to for RHEL hosts?",
        "answer": "From /usr/local to /opt/local"
      },
      {
        "question": "What issues are being worked around by moving the software for RHEL hosts?",
        "answer": "Issues with the root user and problems with NFS"
      },
      {
        "question": "If someone is looking for a specific piece of software, which directory can they list?",
        "answer": "/usr/local/stow"
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/PerlLocalLib",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the default directory where everything will be installed when using PerlLocalLib?",
        "answer": "~/perl5"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to install a module using a specific version of Perl?",
        "answer": "/opt/local/stow/perl-5.14.2/bin/perl -MCPAN -Mlocal::lib -e 'CPAN::install(LWP)'"
      },
      {
        "question": "After installing a module, what command must be run to make Perl aware of the alternate location for Perl modules?",
        "answer": "/usr/local/stow/perl-5.14.2/bin/perl -Mlocal::lib"
      },
      {
        "question": "What files need to be updated with the output from the command that makes Perl aware of the alternate module location?",
        "answer": ".cshrc/.tcshrc, .bash_profile, etc."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do after modifying your shell initialization files to apply the changes?",
        "answer": "Log out/log in or source your dot files."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Mpich1sub.sh.o167",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What warning is displayed at the beginning of the content?",
        "answer": "Warning: no access to tty (Bad file descriptor). Thus no job control in this shell."
      },
      {
        "question": "What rank is sending the message '1' to rank 0?",
        "answer": "Rank 1 is sending message '1' to rank 0."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which rank sends the message '6' to rank 7?",
        "answer": "Rank 6 is sending message '6' to rank 7."
      },
      {
        "question": "What message does rank 0 receive from rank 1?",
        "answer": "Rank 0 receives message '1' from rank 1."
      },
      {
        "question": "List the ranks that rank 1 receives a message from during its operations.",
        "answer": "Rank 1 receives messages from rank 0, rank 2, rank 3, rank 4, rank 5, rank 6, and rank 7."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many ranks are there in total that are involved in the messaging displayed?",
        "answer": "There are 8 ranks (0 through 7) involved in the messaging."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does rank 1 do after it finishes its operations?",
        "answer": "Rank 1 finished."
      },
      {
        "question": "What message does rank 2 send to rank 1?",
        "answer": "Rank 2 sends message '2' to rank 1."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which rank does not send messages to itself according to the output?",
        "answer": "Rank 0, rank 1, rank 2, rank 3, rank 4, rank 5, rank 6, and rank 7 all do not send messages to themselves."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action does rank 5 take after it receives message '7' from rank 7?",
        "answer": "Rank 5 sends message '5' to rank 7."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the last message that rank 4 sends before finishing its operations?",
        "answer": "Rank 4 sends message '4' to rank 7 before finishing."
      }
    ],
    "total": 11
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/CCompilers",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the version of gcc located at the path /opt/local/stow/gcc-6.2.0?",
        "answer": "gcc-6.2.0"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many different versions of gcc are mentioned for the RHEL7 platform?",
        "answer": "Eight different versions of gcc are mentioned."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the path for gcc version 5.4.0?",
        "answer": "/opt/local/stow/gcc-5.4.0"
      },
      {
        "question": "What tool is suggested for loading different versions of gcc into the environment?",
        "answer": "Modules"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which version of gcc is the latest one listed for RHEL7 in the provided information?",
        "answer": "gcc-9.3.0"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of compilers, aside from gcc, are mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "Intel Compilers and Portland Group Compilers."
      },
      {
        "question": "What functionality do Modules provide regarding gcc versions?",
        "answer": "Modules provide a way to add and later remove environmental variables that provide access to different versions of gcc."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Main_Page",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'Announcements' section on the UMIACS Main Page?",
        "answer": "The purpose of the 'Announcements' section is to direct users to the intranet page for announcements."
      },
      {
        "question": "What introductory information is provided in the 'Getting Started' section?",
        "answer": "The 'Getting Started' section provides a broad introduction to UMIACS Accounts and services."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which services are included in the 'Core Services' section?",
        "answer": "The 'Core Services' section includes information about Email, Data Storage, Backups, and the VPN."
      },
      {
        "question": "What information is available in the 'Ordering Equipment' section?",
        "answer": "The 'Ordering Equipment' section provides information on equipment requests and best practices."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'Lab Facilities' section cover?",
        "answer": "The 'Lab Facilities' section covers information on the various labs and centers within UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What best practices are shared in the 'Publishing Data' section?",
        "answer": "The 'Publishing Data' section shares best practices when publishing data at UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can individuals get support according to the 'Getting help (UMIACS Help Desk)' section?",
        "answer": "The 'Getting help (UMIACS Help Desk)' section provides information on UMIACS Support and how to contact them."
      },
      {
        "question": "What restriction is mentioned regarding editing privileges on the wiki?",
        "answer": "The editing privileges on the wiki are restricted to members of UMIACS Technical Staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "If someone believes editing is needed on the wiki, what should they do?",
        "answer": "If someone believes editing is needed on the wiki, they should contact staff."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MalwareRecovery",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "Who fully handles malware removal for UMIACS-supported systems?",
        "answer": "UMIACS staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "What may have been collected by a third party during the infection of the machine?",
        "answer": "Private information."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the relationship between the duration of malware propagation and the risk to private information?",
        "answer": "The longer the malware had time to propagate, the greater the risk is that private information may have been collected."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action is recommended for users whose machines have been infected with malware?",
        "answer": "Change all passwords for applications and websites visited while the machine was infected."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do if they made online purchases using an infected machine?",
        "answer": "Keep a close eye on their credit card transactions for the next several weeks after the machine has been cleansed."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of links are provided below the malware removal information?",
        "answer": "Links for changing passwords on commonly-used websites."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do if they notice odd behavior from the previously infected machine?",
        "answer": "Email staff or contact the HelpDesk for further investigation."
      },
      {
        "question": "What email address should users contact if they suspect the system was not fully cleansed?",
        "answer": "staff@umiacs.umd.edu."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/Compute/HPC",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What operating system is used for the High Performance Computational systems at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "RHEL 7"
      },
      {
        "question": "What scheduling system is mentioned as being used with the HPC clusters at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "SLURM"
      },
      {
        "question": "How does UMIACS ensure that the HPC systems meet the needs of different groups?",
        "answer": "The individual configuration and scheduler are suited to the needs of each individual group."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of systems does UMIACS provide integration and maintenance for?",
        "answer": "High Performance Computational (HPC) clusters."
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Umask",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What permissions do files have by default when no umask is set?",
        "answer": "Files have permissions 666."
      },
      {
        "question": "What binary representation corresponds to the default permission for directories when no umask is set?",
        "answer": "Directories have permissions 777, which is 111111111 in binary."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does the umask affect the permissions of files and directories created?",
        "answer": "For each bit that is set to 1 in the umask, the corresponding bit of any files or directories that are created is set to 0."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the result of applying umask 022 to the default directory permissions?",
        "answer": "The result is 755."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does umask 002 allow for user and group permissions?",
        "answer": "It gives full rwx for the user and full rwx for the group, and r-x for others."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the risk associated with using umask 000?",
        "answer": "It gives full control to user, group, and others, making the directory or file world read, write, and executable, which can be a large security risk."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command is used to set or check the current umask in a shell?",
        "answer": "The command used is umask."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you set your umask to be applied by default each time you start a new shell session?",
        "answer": "In your shell initialization file, such as .profile or .bash_profile for bash, and .cshrc or .tcshrc for tcsh."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be added to .bash_profile to set the umask to 002?",
        "answer": "The command to add is 'echo 'umask 002' >> ~/.bash_profile'."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/UMIACS:About",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What does UMIACS stand for?",
        "answer": "University of Maryland Institute for Advanced Computer Studies"
      },
      {
        "question": "Is there a link provided for more information about UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Yes, the link provided is https://www.umiacs.umd.edu"
      }
    ],
    "total": 2
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/EnvironmentalVariables",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the most common variable mentioned that affects commands run in UNIX and Windows?",
        "answer": "The most common variable is the PATH variable."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you view your PATH variable in the shell?",
        "answer": "You can see your PATH variable by using the built-in echo command in the shell."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the correct syntax to append a path to the PATH variable in tcsh or csh?",
        "answer": "setenv PATH ${PATH}:/opt/UMtorque/bin"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the command to set the PATH variable in bash?",
        "answer": "export PATH=${PATH}:/opt/UMtorque/bin"
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should be taken to modify the Windows PATH Environmental Variable?",
        "answer": "Go to Control Panel, click on User Accounts, then on Change my environment variables, select the PATH variable, and append the new path."
      },
      {
        "question": "How are different paths separated when modifying the Windows PATH variable?",
        "answer": "Different paths are separated by semicolons."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command do you use to verify that the PATH variable has been modified in Windows?",
        "answer": "Type in PATH in a new Command Prompt."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if you replace instead of append to the PATH variable?",
        "answer": "Replacing the PATH variable fully will most likely decrease the functionality of your shell."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/CommonPool",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are Common-Pool resources?",
        "answer": "Common-Pool resources consist of various."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of service is the Nexus Cluster categorized under?",
        "answer": "Infrastructure as a service."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the term 'Supported Shared Storage' refer to in the context of UMIACS services?",
        "answer": "Supported Shared Storage."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Windows",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of operating system is Windows?",
        "answer": "Windows is a desktop and server operating system made by Microsoft."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you refer to for information on supported Windows versions?",
        "answer": "For a list of what Windows versions are currently supported, you should see the relevant page."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you find information about activating Windows on UMIACS supported devices?",
        "answer": "You can see Windows Activation for activation information."
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you need to reference for activating Microsoft Office on UMIACS supported devices?",
        "answer": "You should see Microsoft Office Activation for that purpose."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is covered in the section titled 'Windows Servicing'?",
        "answer": "Windows Servicing provides an overview of how Windows feature updates are run at UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "List the programming environments mentioned in the document.",
        "answer": "The mentioned programming environments are Python, R, RStudio, and Visual Studio."
      },
      {
        "question": "What topics are included in the 'Other Resources' section?",
        "answer": "The topics included are Windows Accounts, Remote Desktop, Setting File Permissions in Windows, and BitLocker Input Method Editors."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/IntelCompilers",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What two versions of compilers are supported on RedHat hosts according to the document?",
        "answer": "Intel® C/C++ Composer XE for Linux and Intel® Fortran Composer XE for Linux."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is suggested to prepare the environment for C/C++ or Fortran compilation on RHEL7+/Ubuntu hosts?",
        "answer": "module load intel/2020.1"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the path for the Intel C/C++ compiler version 11.1 on RHEL7+/Ubuntu?",
        "answer": "/opt/common/intel/Compiler/11.1/current"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should tcsh/csh users execute to use the Intel C Compiler with the version 13.1.1 on a 64bit architecture?",
        "answer": "source /opt/common/intel/composer_xe_2013_sp1.1.106/bin/iccvars.csh intel64"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the paths for the Intel Fortran compiler version 11.1 on RHEL7+/Ubuntu?",
        "answer": "/opt/common/intel/Compiler/11.1/current"
      },
      {
        "question": "For a tcsh/csh user using the Intel Fortran Compiler version 13.1.1 on a 64bit architecture, what command should be used?",
        "answer": "source /opt/common/intel/composer_xe_2013_sp1.1.106/bin/ifortvars.csh intel64"
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be specified on the command line when sourcing the environment for either the Intel C/C++ or Fortran compilers?",
        "answer": "the architecture, either ia32 for 32bit or intel64 for 64bit."
      },
      {
        "question": "What tool can be used to compile with the Intel C++ Compiler after setting up the environment?",
        "answer": "icpc"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to compile with the Intel Fortran Compiler after the environment is set up?",
        "answer": "ifort"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the initial command executed on any RedHat host to obtain support for Intel compilers?",
        "answer": "load a GNU Module file or source some config files depending on your shell and architecture."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SLURM/ArrayJobs",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the code saved in the file called test.py?",
        "answer": "The code prints the start time, sleeps for 10 seconds, and then prints the stop time."
      },
      {
        "question": "What job name is assigned in the submission script array.sh?",
        "answer": "The job name assigned is 'example'."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many jobs will the SLURM array run simultaneously as indicated in the submission script?",
        "answer": "The SLURM array will run 16 jobs at the same time."
      },
      {
        "question": "What amount of memory is allocated per CPU in the SLURM submission script?",
        "answer": "500MB of memory is allocated per CPU."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the total runtime specified for the jobs in the submission script?",
        "answer": "The total runtime specified is 5 minutes."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is the unique scratch directory created for the job?",
        "answer": "The unique scratch directory is created at /scratch0/${USER}/job-array-example/${SLURM_JOBID}."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used in the submission script to execute the Python code with the unique task ID?",
        "answer": "The command used is 'python test.py > output_${SLURM_ARRAY_TASK_ID}.txt'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to the output files after the jobs are completed?",
        "answer": "The output files are copied back to ${SLURM_SUBMIT_DIR}."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command is used to remove the scratch directory after the job is done?",
        "answer": "The command used is 'rm -rf ${SCRATCH_DIRECTORY}'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the line 'echo \"now processing task id:: \" ${SLURM_ARRAY_TASK_ID}' do in the script?",
        "answer": "It outputs a message indicating the current task ID being processed."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/ConferenceRooms/Moderated",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is required for making reservations in the moderated conference rooms?",
        "answer": "All reservations need to go through the moderation process."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the primary moderator for room IRB-4105?",
        "answer": "Sharron McElroy is the primary moderator for room IRB-4105."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many occupants can room IRB-3137 accommodate?",
        "answer": "Room IRB-3137 can accommodate 24 occupants."
      },
      {
        "question": "What specific feature does room IRB-4107 have?",
        "answer": "Room IRB-4107 is designated as a seminar room."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the setup configuration for rooms 3137 and 4105?",
        "answer": "Rooms 3137 and 4105 have dual display (projector and LCD), dual camera conferencing via room PC, laptop presentation via HDMI or Mersive Solstice, Blu-ray playback, and a TV tuner."
      },
      {
        "question": "What prefix do you use to dial external numbers from the conference rooms?",
        "answer": "Use prefix 91 for external numbers."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which room is associated with the phone number 301-314-9963?",
        "answer": "Room IRB-2137 is associated with the phone number 301-314-9963."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of display is available in every other room besides 3137 and 4105?",
        "answer": "Every other room has a single display (LCD)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the backup moderator for the Adobe Conference Room (IRB-4237)?",
        "answer": "Elizabeth Hontz is the backup moderator for the Adobe Conference Room (IRB-4237)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be done to answer a call in the moderated IRB conference rooms?",
        "answer": "Start the system, select phone, and hit the 'dial/answer' button."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/Faxing",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What model of printer is located in room 4208 of the Iribe Center?",
        "answer": "HP LaserJet Enterprise Flow MFP M633"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the fax number associated with the fax machine in room 4208?",
        "answer": "301-314-9115 (x49115)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional capability does the HP LaserJet Enterprise Flow MFP M633 have besides black and white printing?",
        "answer": "Faxing capability (send/receive)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can HP's guide for using the HP LaserJet Enterprise Flow MFP M633 model of fax be found?",
        "answer": "On page 15 of the guide found at http://h10032.www1.hp.com/ctg/Manual/c05791986"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the dialing requirement when faxing to numbers external to the university using the HP LaserJet Enterprise Flow MFP M633?",
        "answer": "You will need to dial 9 and then 1 before faxing to any number external to the university."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Microsoft_Office_Activation",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of this article?",
        "answer": "The article is about how to manually force Microsoft Office to activate and obtain a license from the university KMS server."
      },
      {
        "question": "Under what circumstances will a user need to manually activate Microsoft Office?",
        "answer": "A user will need to manually activate Microsoft Office if it is installed on a host that goes an extended length of time (180 days or more) without connecting to the campus network (either physically or through a VPN) and needs to be activated in a hurry."
      },
      {
        "question": "What network connections are necessary to activate Microsoft Office?",
        "answer": "To activate Microsoft Office, you need to be connected to either the wired campus network, campus WiFi, the campus VPN, or the UMIACS VPN."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be correct for the activation process to work?",
        "answer": "Your time must be correct (i.e. set via the Internet) and set to the US Eastern timezone for this to work."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can you run to resync your time if the activation commands fail?",
        "answer": "You can run the command 'w32tm /resync' on the command line to resync your time."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step in the Simple Activation Method?",
        "answer": "The first step in the Simple Activation Method is to open any Office product (Word, PowerPoint, etc.)."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you determine the bitness of your operating system?",
        "answer": "You determine the bitness of your operating system by running the command 'wmic os get osarchitecture'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command do you need to run to set the KMS server for 64-bit Office on 64-bit Windows?",
        "answer": "The command to set the KMS server for 64-bit Office on 64-bit Windows is 'cscript \"C:\\Program Files\\Microsoft Office\\Office16\\OSPP.VBS\" /sethst:kms.umd.edu'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the command used to check the licensing status of Microsoft Office?",
        "answer": "The command used to check the licensing status is 'cscript \"C:\\Program Files\\Microsoft Office\\Office16\\OSPP.VBS\" /dstatus'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the command 'cscript \"C:\\Program Files\\Microsoft Office\\Office16\\OSPP.VBS\" /act' do?",
        "answer": "The command 'cscript \"C:\\Program Files\\Microsoft Office\\Office16\\OSPP.VBS\" /act' forces an activation against the KMS server."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/CloudDataStorage",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What does cloud storage refer to?",
        "answer": "Cloud storage refers to all data that is stored on third-party providers' data hosting platforms."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the opposite of cloud storage?",
        "answer": "The opposite of cloud storage is local storage."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is local storage physically located?",
        "answer": "Local storage is stored physically at UMIACS on hard drives either in a datacenter managed by UMIACS staff or on UMIACS-supported workstations."
      },
      {
        "question": "Do UMIACS accounts provide access to cloud storage options?",
        "answer": "UMIACS accounts do not provide access to any cloud storage options."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which accounts provide access to cloud storage options?",
        "answer": "UMD accounts provide access to cloud storage options."
      },
      {
        "question": "Name one cloud storage service listed for UMD accounts.",
        "answer": "Google Drive is one of the cloud storage services listed for UMD accounts."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the three cloud storage options mentioned for UMD accounts?",
        "answer": "The three cloud storage options mentioned are Google Drive, Box, and OneDrive."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Malware/virus_removal",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the two types of malware/virus removal tools mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "Online and offline scanners."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do offline scans differ from online scans according to the text?",
        "answer": "Offline scans work outside of your computer's operating system, providing an alternate means for detecting and mitigating threats that may use various tactics to hide, while online scanners can detect most problems and are easier to use."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is recommended as the first step to remove malware or a virus?",
        "answer": "To first try an online scanner."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be done if the online scanner does not fix the problem?",
        "answer": "Try an offline scanner."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which offline scan tool is mentioned that only works with Windows 10 or 11 machines?",
        "answer": "Microsoft Defender Offline."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the F-Secure Client Security on UMIACS-supported machines?",
        "answer": "It is used to run a manual scan on UMIACS-supported machines."
      },
      {
        "question": "What issue does the F-Secure suite's Browsing Protection optional feature cause?",
        "answer": "It can cause website accessibility issues."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two options available for manual scanning using F-Secure?",
        "answer": "Malware scan and Full computer scan."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the Malware scan option search for?",
        "answer": "It searches common places where malware can be found."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the Full computer scan do?",
        "answer": "It scans all internal/external hard drives for malware."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Network/VPN/Ivanti",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the new name for the Pulse Secure Client as of August 14th, 2022?",
        "answer": "Ivanti Secure Access Client."
      },
      {
        "question": "How has the icon for the Pulse Secure Client changed?",
        "answer": "The Pulse Secure Desktop Client icon is replaced with the Ivanti Secure Access Icon."
      },
      {
        "question": "What options do users have regarding the user interface of the Ivanti Secure Access Client?",
        "answer": "Users have an option to switch between the Classic UI and New-UX to maintain user experience per individual preference."
      },
      {
        "question": "What prompts will users receive after the VPN maintenance?",
        "answer": "Users will automatically be prompted to upgrade the client, pulling an up to date version of the client with the most recent configuration."
      },
      {
        "question": "List the available installers for the Ivanti Secure Access Client for different operating systems.",
        "answer": "1. Windows 64 bit Ivanti Secure Access Client (/umiacs/images/b/bb/PulseSecure22.2R1.x64.msi) 2. Windows 32 bit Ivanti Secure Access Client (/umiacs/images/1/12/PulseSecure22.2.R1.x86.msi) 3. Ubuntu 64 bit Ivanti Secure Access Client (/umiacs/images/9/92/Pulsesecure_22.2.R1_amd64.deb) 4. MacOS Ivanti Secure Access Client (/umiacs/images/3/31/PulseSecure_22.2.R1.dmg)"
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/GettingStarted",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What types of facilities and services are included in the basic UMIACS Account?",
        "answer": "The basic UMIACS Account includes access to facilities such as a UMIACS E-mail address, several login machines (Nexus), basic home directory space, object storage space, the Nexus HPC cluster, VPN, and printing access."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary goal of the Nexus system used in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The goal of the Nexus is to provide a basic computing environment for communications, authoring, file sharing, and general administrative computing."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps must be taken to request a UMIACS account if one does not already exist?",
        "answer": "To request a UMIACS account, you must fill out the account request form, enter your PI/Professor/Sponsor's account name, indicate any labs you are a member of, confirm your email address, and wait for your PI to approve the request."
      },
      {
        "question": "How long does it take to have a UMIACS account installed after approval from a PI?",
        "answer": "Once the PI approves the account, staff will install it within two business days."
      },
      {
        "question": "What application should users log into to see which hosts they have access to?",
        "answer": "Users should log into the UMIACS Directory CR application to see which hosts they have access to."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can be managed through the Directory Profile web application?",
        "answer": "Through the Directory Profile web application, users can change their listed full name, office location, office phone number, home page, PGP key, mail delivery/forward options, mobile phone number for password recovery, and default shells."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the recommended method for accessing remote data at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The recommended method for accessing remote data is using SCP."
      },
      {
        "question": "What different home directory setups may users experience while using specific labs' machines?",
        "answer": "Users may have different home directories in different locations depending on the specific labs' machines they are using."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Perl",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are some of the tasks Perl is used for?",
        "answer": "Perl is used for a wide range of tasks including system administration, web development, network programming, GUI development, and more."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary design intention of the Perl language?",
        "answer": "The language is intended to be practical (easy to use, efficient, complete) rather than beautiful (tiny, elegant, minimal)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What programming paradigms does Perl support?",
        "answer": "Perl supports both procedural and object-oriented (OO) programming."
      },
      {
        "question": "What built-in capability does Perl have that is noteworthy?",
        "answer": "Perl has powerful built-in support for text processing."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is mentioned regarding the availability of different versions of Perl for RHEL?",
        "answer": "For RHEL, different versions of Perl can be found via GNU Modules."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which version of Perl is indicated as available for Ubuntu Trusty 14.04?",
        "answer": "The version of Perl indicated for Ubuntu Trusty 14.04 is 5.18.2."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can ActiveState Perl be obtained for Windows?",
        "answer": "ActiveState Perl can be installed on your PC upon request by contacting staff at UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is preferred regarding user installations of Perl modules?",
        "answer": "Users are preferred to create their own installations of Perl modules to ensure backwards compatibility and functionality."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can full documentation for Perl be found?",
        "answer": "Full documentation for any version of Perl can be found at http://www.cpan.org/modules/INSTALL.html."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the suggested way to install Perl modules according to the text?",
        "answer": "The text suggests that users create their own installations of Perl modules to keep the central versions of Perl as vanilla as possible."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/Compute/LabSpecific",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is a Lab Specific resource in the context of UMIACS?",
        "answer": "A Lab Specific resource is any UMIACS maintained system acquired for the exclusive use of a given Lab or group."
      }
    ],
    "total": 1
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Mpich1sub.sh",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command is used to specify the number of nodes and walltime in the script?",
        "answer": "#PBS -l nodes=8,walltime=60"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which directory is the script changing to before executing the program?",
        "answer": "~/mpich1test/"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to set up the path for the MPICH installation?",
        "answer": "PATH=/usr/local/stow/mpichgm-1.2.7p1-20/bin:$PATH"
      },
      {
        "question": "How is the number of processes for the mpirun command determined in the script?",
        "answer": "mpirun -np $( wc -l < $PBS_NODEFILE )"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the echo command output in the script?",
        "answer": "The command outputs the content of $PBS_NODEFILE."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/CDebuggers",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What version of gdb is available on the RHEL7 platform?",
        "answer": "gdb 7.6.1-120.el7"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the file path for gdb on the RHEL7 platform?",
        "answer": "/usr/bin/gdb"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which version of valgrind is available on the RHEL7 platform?",
        "answer": "valgrind 3.15.0"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the file path for valgrind on the RHEL7 platform?",
        "answer": "/usr/bin/valgrind"
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/RStudio",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is required to use RStudio?",
        "answer": "An R environment set up."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can the installation files for RStudio be retrieved?",
        "answer": "From http://www.rstudio.com/products/rstudio/download/"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two methods available for installing RStudio?",
        "answer": "The installer and the archive."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the recommended installation method for RStudio?",
        "answer": "The archive method, as it allows you to skip directly to Running RStudio."
      },
      {
        "question": "When using the installer, what location is recommended for installation?",
        "answer": "A location within your home directory."
      },
      {
        "question": "What recommendation is given regarding the creation of shortcuts during installation?",
        "answer": "It is recommended to check 'Do not create shortcuts' because the RStudio folder it creates will likely just be empty."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do after navigating to the directory where RStudio was installed?",
        "answer": "Open the 'bin' directory and find the 'rstudio.exe' file."
      },
      {
        "question": "What option should you choose when RStudio prompts for an R execution environment?",
        "answer": "Choose the third option: 'Choose a specific version of R.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "What folders must be directly contained within the selected folder when configuring RStudio?",
        "answer": "Folders such as 'bin' and 'include'."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/NASUsers",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is being deprecated in favor of the UMIACS Object Store?",
        "answer": "These services are currently being deprecated in favor of the UMIACS Object Store."
      },
      {
        "question": "What might vary depending on when the user's account was installed?",
        "answer": "Users may or may not have web space or personal FTP access depending on when their account was installed."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the online address for accessing the FTP site?",
        "answer": "The FTP site is online at ftp://ftp.umiacs.umd.edu/pub/username."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can Windows users access their FTP site?",
        "answer": "Windows users can map it as a network drive from \\umiacs-webftp\\ftp-umiacs\\pub."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should not be stored on the FTP site according to the guidelines?",
        "answer": "Confidential data should not be stored on the FTP site."
      },
      {
        "question": "What services provide regular backups for the file system?",
        "answer": "This file system has regular backups with the TSM service."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the configuration of personal NAS in terms of availability and usage?",
        "answer": "Personal NAS is configured to be highly available and modest in both size and usage."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is recommended for storing large or heavily accessed datasets?",
        "answer": "It is recommended to store large or heavily accessed datasets in a dedicated project storage directory that is tuned for your application."
      },
      {
        "question": "Why is it suggested to separate project data from personal data?",
        "answer": "Separating project data from personal data will simplify administration and data management for both researchers and staff."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Matlab",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What operating systems are covered by the UMIACS institutional Matlab licenses?",
        "answer": "Linux, Windows, and macOS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What versions of Matlab are supported by the University's license server?",
        "answer": "Only Matlab versions R2020a and newer are supported."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can one install the institutional version of Matlab on a self-supported machine?",
        "answer": "By contacting staff to provide install media."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the preferred way to interact with Matlab on UMIACS-supported Linux machines?",
        "answer": "Modules are the preferred way."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if you need a later version of Matlab on a UMIACS-supported Windows machine?",
        "answer": "Contact staff if you would like a later version installed."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required to use the University's Matlab licenses?",
        "answer": "You must have network connectivity."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens when calling functions in a toolbox in Matlab?",
        "answer": "Matlab will automatically check out a license for that toolbox, making it temporarily unavailable to other users."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is indicated by a license manager error stating that the maximum number of users for Matlab has been reached?",
        "answer": "This likely indicates that all of campus' available licenses are in use."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are some examples of toolbox shortnames used in Matlab?",
        "answer": "Examples include Aerospace_Blockset, Bioinformatics_Toolbox, Communication_Toolbox, Optimization_Toolbox, and Statistics_Toolbox."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can you customize in Matlab using the 'startup.m' file?",
        "answer": "You can customize the window environment, set variables for later use, and enable the use of 3rd party toolboxes."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you specify a path other than the current working directory for startup and 3rd party toolbox locations in Matlab?",
        "answer": "By using the userpath environment variable."
      }
    ],
    "total": 11
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Intranet",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What feature does the UMIACS Account Management section provide?",
        "answer": "New accounts, approve requests, etc."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can users do in the Search the Directory section?",
        "answer": "Search for e-mail addresses, telephone numbers, and room numbers of UMIACS employees."
      },
      {
        "question": "What options are available in the Directory Update section?",
        "answer": "Update your UMIACS directory info and change e-mail forwarding options."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of information is available in the Technical Reference section?",
        "answer": "How-to's and FAQ's regarding UMIACS's computing facilities."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Equipment Reservation section?",
        "answer": "Reserve laptops and other equipment ahead of time."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/AddingUMIACSCertificateAuthority",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the main purpose of the UMIACS Certificate Authority?",
        "answer": "The main purpose of the UMIACS Certificate Authority is to enable web browsers to trust UMIACS's secure webpages."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps must be followed in Windows to accept the UMIACS certificate after downloading it?",
        "answer": "After downloading the UMIACS Certificate Authority file, open it, click 'Install Certificate', then 'Next', choose 'Place all certificates in the following store', click 'Browse', select 'Trusted Root Certification Authorities', click 'Ok', then 'Next', and 'Finish'. If a Security Warning appears, click 'Yes'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if they do not have administrator access on a UMIACS-supported Mac?",
        "answer": "If a user does not have administrator access on a UMIACS-supported Mac, they should contact Staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "In macOS, where is the Keychain Access located?",
        "answer": "Keychain Access is located in the Others group in Launchpad."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be done after right-clicking the added certificate in macOS?",
        "answer": "After right-clicking the added certificate, the user must select the 'Get Info' section and then select 'Always Trust' in the 'When using this certificate' dropdown."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is a prerequisite for accepting the UMIACS Certificate Authority in macOS?",
        "answer": "Administrator access is required to accept the UMIACS Certificate Authority in macOS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What may a Unix user need assistance with regarding the UMIACS Certificate Authority?",
        "answer": "A Unix user may need assistance with the more complicated process of accepting the UMIACS Certificate Authority, which may depend on their particular Unix distribution."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step for accepting the UMIACS certificate in most Windows browsers?",
        "answer": "The first step is to click the UMIACS Certificate Authority link to download the file."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action do you need to perform after entering administrator credentials in macOS?",
        "answer": "After entering administrator credentials, the user should close the certificate and Keychain Access window."
      },
      {
        "question": "What browser is mentioned as being an exception in the macOS instructions for accepting the UMIACS certificate?",
        "answer": "Firefox is mentioned as the exception in the macOS instructions."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MFA/Duo_Recovery",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What should a user do first if they haven't already when attempting to recover Duo authentication?",
        "answer": "Download the Duo app on your device."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where should a user navigate to in order to log in with their UMIACS credentials?",
        "answer": "Navigate to https://intranet.umiacs.umd.edu/directory."
      },
      {
        "question": "What button should a user click on the Duo prompt after logging in?",
        "answer": "Click the 'My Settings & Devices' button on the left."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two options a user can select to authenticate without the Duo app?",
        "answer": "The Call Me or Passcode option."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user click on their registered device to reactivate Duo Mobile?",
        "answer": "Click Device Options."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action must a user follow after clicking Reactivate Duo Mobile?",
        "answer": "Follow the on-screen prompts."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MailmanFAQ",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What email address do members of a Mailman list use to post messages?",
        "answer": "list-name@lists.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps are involved in adding users to a mailing list using the Mass Subscription feature?",
        "answer": "Log in to the mailing list's administration page with the admin password, click 'Membership Management...' -> Choose 'Mass Subscription'. Enter one address per line of users you would like to subscribe. Click 'Submit Your Changes' button and verify by choosing 'Membership List' under 'Membership Management...'"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can someone subscribe to a mailing list without the administrator's assistance?",
        "answer": "They just need to go to http://lists.umiacs.umd.edu/mailman/listinfo/LISTNAME and fill in the form or send an email to LISTNAME-subscribe."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should an administrator do to automatically delete all mail from non-members?",
        "answer": "Go to the privacy page followed by the sender-filter sub-page and set to 'discard' the value for 'Action to take for postings from non-members for which no explicit action is defined.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user post from multiple addresses to a 'members-only' mailing list without their message being rejected?",
        "answer": "The solution is to subscribe both addresses to the list but to disable delivery from all but one of the addresses."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can an administrator change a member's password or send it to them?",
        "answer": "Go to the Membership Management page, click the address in question, and use the option 'Email my password to me'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the moderation flag in a mailing list?",
        "answer": "The moderation flag is used to manage posts from users, allowing the list administrator to set users as moderated or to reject their posts by default."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action must an administrator take to unsubscribe users without them receiving an unsubscribe message?",
        "answer": "They need to click the 'unsub' button next to each user's name or go to the Mass Removal subpage and add all addresses before clicking 'submit'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What feature is used to edit a held message before approving it for a mailing list?",
        "answer": "Use the 'forward this message' feature in the admindb page to forward the message to yourself, edit it, and resend it to the list with the appropriate headers."
      },
      {
        "question": "What common spam filter restriction is mentioned for mailing lists?",
        "answer": "One common spam filter restriction is to restrict posts with [QUAR] in the subject."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Service/Compute/Virtualization",
    "Q/A": [],
    "total": 0
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/DigitalLoanerForm",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What software is needed to complete the loaner form digitally?",
        "answer": "Adobe Acrobat DC or Adobe Acrobat Reader DC."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can Adobe Acrobat DC be accessed for free?",
        "answer": "From Terpware."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be clicked on the top menu to begin filling out the loaner form?",
        "answer": "Tools."
      },
      {
        "question": "What minimum field must be filled out for each item on the loaner form?",
        "answer": "Description of Equipment."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must users do with the signature field before saving the form?",
        "answer": "Leave the signature field blank."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens after saving the PDF with the signature placed in the signature field?",
        "answer": "Users will not be able to edit the form further."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should the file be renamed to include before saving it?",
        "answer": "The word 'signed'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of attaching the signed form?",
        "answer": "To attach it to the originating request that prompted staff to direct you to this page."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SLURM/Priority",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the reason a job remains in the Pending state if it has a lower priority than another pending job?",
        "answer": "Your job gets assigned a lower priority value than that pending job; your job will instead remain in the Pending state with reason (Priority)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to provide a time estimate for when a job will start?",
        "answer": "The command squeue -j <jobid> --start can be used to provide a time estimate for when your job will start."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the priority factors in use at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The priority factors include: Age of job, Association (SLURM account), Partition job was submitted to, Fair-share of resources, and 'Nice' value that job was submitted with."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does the Age factor affect a job's priority?",
        "answer": "The longer a job is eligible to run but cannot due to resources being unavailable, the higher the job's priority becomes as it continues to wait in the queue. The priority modifier for this factor reaches its limit after 7 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the general priority order for partitions at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "In decreasing order of priority, the priority tiers for partitions are: Account-specific non-preemptable partitions, Lab/center-specific non-'scavenger' named partitions, Lab/center-specific 'scavenger' named partitions, Institute-wide scavenger partition."
      },
      {
        "question": "What impact does Fair-share have on job priority within the same account?",
        "answer": "The more resources your jobs have already consumed within an account, the lower priority factor your future jobs will have when compared to other users' jobs in the same account who have used fewer resources."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the weighting value of memory in CPU-only partition billing?",
        "answer": "The weighting value for memory is 1.0 per GB, resulting in roughly 90.9% of the billing weight being for memory and 9.1% being for CPU."
      },
      {
        "question": "How is the 'Nice' value used when submitting jobs, and how does it affect their priority?",
        "answer": "'Nice' is a submission argument included to deprioritize jobs; larger values will deprioritize jobs more."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the baseline GPU type currently used for weighting in GPU partitions at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The current baseline GPU is the NVIDIA RTX A4000."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to jobs submitted to the scavenger partition at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Jobs submitted to the scavenger partition always have a lower priority factor for their jobs than all other partitions on that cluster and are also preemptable."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to view Fair-share statistics?",
        "answer": "The command sshare -l can be used to view the various fair-share statistics."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/Compute/UserSupported",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What defines a User-Supported system according to the document?",
        "answer": "A User-Supported system is any University owned hardware that is administered by the system's primary user."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of services may UMIACS Technical Staff provide on User-Supported systems?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Technical Staff may provide In-Warranty hardware diagnostics and support, operating system and software licensing and media."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is responsible for the maintenance, security, and backups of a User-Supported system?",
        "answer": "The maintenance, security, and backups of the system will be the responsibility of its primary user."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MongoDB",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the reason given for no longer supporting MongoDB?",
        "answer": "Changes in their licensing a few years ago."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of file should be downloaded from the MongoDB Community download page for installation?",
        "answer": "The right Community Server file, which for most people will be: Version: Current, Platform: RedHat / CentOS 7.0, Package: tgz."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be created as part of the MongoDB installation steps?",
        "answer": "A custom mongod.conf configuration file."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the specific directories that need to be set in the custom mongod.conf file?",
        "answer": "systemPath and dbPath, which must be directories that you own."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to start the mongo server with the custom configuration file?",
        "answer": "\"/path/to/bin/mongod --config /path/to/mongod.conf\"."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you stop the mongo server after you are done using it?",
        "answer": "\"/path/to/bin/mongod --config /path/to/mongod.conf --shutdown\"."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MailmanListAdmin",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if they wish to subscribe to a private list?",
        "answer": "They need to go to http://lists.umiacs.umd.edu/mailman/listinfo/LISTNAME, even if the list is private, and they can also subscribe/unsubscribe by email."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the password provided by UMIACS staff?",
        "answer": "The password is needed for managing the list, including adding/removing users, approving user subscriptions, and tailoring the list."
      },
      {
        "question": "What capability does the 'Membership Management' section provide?",
        "answer": "This section allows you to subscribe and unsubscribe users, hide their email addresses, and more."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a list administrator set the list to be moderated?",
        "answer": "A list can be set to be moderated at the bottom of the 'Membership Management' --> 'Membership List' page."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens when a user forgets their password in the Membership Management section?",
        "answer": "Clicking on the user's email address will allow the administrator to send them an email message containing their password."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default visibility setting for list membership email addresses?",
        "answer": "By default, only list members can see the email addresses of other list members."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the significance of the 'Archiving Options' section?",
        "answer": "This section allows the administrator to choose whether or not to archive messages sent to the list and who can access those archives."
      },
      {
        "question": "What confirmation process is required when a new user tries to subscribe to the list?",
        "answer": "Mailman sends a confirm email message to the user asking if they are sure they want to subscribe."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can a list administrator do in the event of messages pending moderation?",
        "answer": "They can view the queue of messages and choose actions such as Defer, Accept, Reject, or Discard for messages."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'nomail' option do for a user who goes on vacation?",
        "answer": "The 'nomail' option turns off mailing to that individual until they return."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Unix_groups",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the default group membership for a UMIACS account?",
        "answer": "Each UMIACS account is by default a member of its own group, defined by that username."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many UNIX groups can a user create via the Directory tool?",
        "answer": "A user may create up to 5 UNIX groups via the Directory tool."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must a user do to add a valid UMIACS user to a newly created UNIX group?",
        "answer": "Click on the link of the newly created group, add a valid UMIACS user into the available text box, and click add user."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command is used to grant group ownership of a file to a specific UNIX group?",
        "answer": "The command to use is chgrp group-name file-name."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user verify the permissions that a group has for a specific file or directory?",
        "answer": "To see the permissions that the group has, a user can use the command ls -l, and the group permissions will be the 5, 6, 7th characters of the permissions listing."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should be used to change the permissions of a group on a file or directory?",
        "answer": "To change the permissions of the group, use chmod g+r/w/x file-name if you own the group."
      },
      {
        "question": "How are group deletions managed at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Deleting groups will be managed by UMIACS staff, and a ticket must be submitted through JIRA to delete a group."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Tensorflow",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is Tensorflow and which company developed it?",
        "answer": "Tensorflow is a Python deep learning package developed by Google."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the preferred way to install Tensorflow according to the text?",
        "answer": "The easiest way to install Tensorflow is to build a Python virtualenv with it in it."
      },
      {
        "question": "What specific Tensorflow version is mentioned as the latest release as of April 29, 2024?",
        "answer": "The latest Tensorflow release mentioned is tensorflow-2.16.1."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should be used to create a Python virtualenv for Tensorflow?",
        "answer": "$ python3 -m venv env"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command upgrades pip within the virtualenv?",
        "answer": "(env) $ pip install --upgrade pip"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to install Tensorflow via pip?",
        "answer": "(env) $ pip install --upgrade tensorflow"
      },
      {
        "question": "What environment variable can be set to turn off oneDNN custom operations?",
        "answer": "Set the environment variable `TF_ENABLE_ONEDNN_OPTS=0`."
      },
      {
        "question": "What warning message may appear related to TensorRT according to the output?",
        "answer": "TF-TRT Warning: Could not find TensorRT."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the command 'export XLA_FLAGS' mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "It is needed to export specific flags in the shell for using XLA with Tensorflow."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which dataset is used in the Tensorflow example provided in the text?",
        "answer": "The MNIST dataset is used in the Tensorflow example."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the activation function used for the second Dense layer in the model definition?",
        "answer": "The activation function used is tf.nn.softmax."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many epochs is the model trained for in the example?",
        "answer": "The model is trained for 5 epochs."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command must be run after closing the shell to use the Tensorflow installation?",
        "answer": "You will need to both add the correct CUDA/cuDNN modules, export the XLA_FLAGS variable (if needed), and activate the virtualenv by the source command."
      }
    ],
    "total": 12
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/PGICompilers",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What compilers are available under /opt/common/pgi*?",
        "answer": "The Portland Group C and Fortran compilers."
      },
      {
        "question": "On which operating systems are the PGI compilers supported?",
        "answer": "RHEL and Ubuntu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should the LM_LICENSE_FILE environment variable be set to?",
        "answer": "/etc/license.pgi."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you set the LM_LICENSE_FILE variable in tcsh?",
        "answer": "You can use the command: setenv LM_LICENSE_FILE $LM_LICENSE_FILE:/etc/license.dat:/etc/license.pgi."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to set the LM_LICENSE_FILE variable in bash?",
        "answer": "export LM_LICENSE_FILE=\"$LM_LICENSE_FILE:/etc/license.dat:/etc/license.pgi\"."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/ConferenceRooms/Moderation",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What action should be taken to approve a reservation for an event?",
        "answer": "Select 'I'm going on the event.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be selected to deny a reservation for an event?",
        "answer": "Select 'I'm not going on the event.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can notifications for a calendar be enabled?",
        "answer": "Open the calendar's settings in Google Calendar, scroll down to the Other notifications section, and enable what you want."
      },
      {
        "question": "Is enabling notifications for calendars a global setting or a room-specific setting?",
        "answer": "It is done on a room by room basis."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is recommended regarding notifications for the rooms you moderate?",
        "answer": "It is recommended that you at least have notifications enabled for the rooms you moderate."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/HPC",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What documentation is mentioned in relation to the Slurm Scheduler?",
        "answer": "Slurm Scheduler Documentation"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the names of the Nexus resources listed in the text?",
        "answer": "Nexus/CBCB, Nexus/CLIP, Nexus/CML, Nexus/GAMMA, Nexus/MBRC, Nexus/MC2, Nexus/Vulcan"
      }
    ],
    "total": 2
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/OBJ/WebHosting",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What happens to the visibility of your bucket when you set up a website configuration?",
        "answer": "Setting up a website configuration will automatically set the visibility of your bucket to public and remove the bucket level ACLs."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of content does the Object Store support for hosted websites?",
        "answer": "The Object Store only has the capability to support static content and client-side scripting in bucket websites."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step in hosting a website using the web interface method?",
        "answer": "Log into OBJ and create a bucket."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command do you use in the CLI to create a new bucket?",
        "answer": "The command is mkobj <bucket_name>."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which file must be uploaded as part of the website configuration when using the web interface?",
        "answer": "You must upload your index.html file and optionally error.html file."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you access the website after it has been hosted?",
        "answer": "You can access the website by using the default URL which has the form https://<Bucket_name>.umiacs.io."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action must be taken to remove a website configuration using the web interface?",
        "answer": "Click on Remove Website Configuration on the settings page."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be done to update your personal UMIACS webpage to point to the hosted site?",
        "answer": "Log into your UMIACS Directory page and update the Home Page attribute to https://<Bucket_name>.umiacs.io."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the command chobj -m public <bucket_name> in the CLI?",
        "answer": "This command is used to make your bucket public."
      },
      {
        "question": "In Cyberduck, what should you check under the Distribution tab to enable website configuration?",
        "answer": "Make sure to leave a checkmark next to Enable Website Configuration (HTTP) Distribution."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Archives",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "For how long does UMIACS archive data?",
        "answer": "UMIACS archives data for a period of 5 years."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of data does UMIACS generally archive?",
        "answer": "UMIACS generally archives persistent local data from primary drives on UMIACS-supported machines (Windows/macOS only) and data from accounts that are closed (metadata, network home directories, GitLab repositories, etc.)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the types of data that UMIACS does not archive?",
        "answer": "UMIACS does not archive /tmp and /scratch directories, temporary project directories, external drives attached to a UMIACS-supported machine, data migrated from one UMIACS-supported machine to another, data handed off to the end-user or PI via external drive, data from drives that failed and were not under backup protection, and any data from self-supported machines."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which operating systems are supported for archiving persistent local data?",
        "answer": "UMIACS supports Windows and macOS for archiving persistent local data."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to data from accounts that are closed at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Data from accounts that are closed, such as metadata, network home directories, and GitLab repositories, is archived."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Visual_Studio",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What edition of Visual Studio is being installed on a UMIACS-supported Windows desktop?",
        "answer": "Community Edition"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of account is required to license the Community Edition of Visual Studio?",
        "answer": "A free Microsoft account"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if they already have a Microsoft account when launching Visual Studio for the first time?",
        "answer": "Go to step 6"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which types of email addresses will not work when signing up for a new Microsoft account?",
        "answer": "University emails"
      },
      {
        "question": "What must a user do after entering their personal email and password during the Microsoft account creation process?",
        "answer": "Check their email for the indicated code and enter it to activate their account"
      },
      {
        "question": "What action must be completed to finish creating a Microsoft account?",
        "answer": "Complete the provided captcha"
      },
      {
        "question": "What information must be filled in after signing in with the Microsoft account?",
        "answer": "Full Name"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of clicking the drop-down arrow next to the user's name in Visual Studio?",
        "answer": "To select 'Account Settings...' and check that the license has been activated under the account"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does Visual Studio do after the user completes their preferences?",
        "answer": "It prepares for first use and then launches"
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ATL/ConferenceRooms",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What control device is used to manage the video and audio sources in conference room ATL 3100A?",
        "answer": "A touch panel."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of sources can be projected in conference room ATL 3100A?",
        "answer": "Room PC, Solstice Pod, and an HDMI cable to use a laptop or external device."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'Audio Override' output device in conference room ATL 3100A?",
        "answer": "It decouples the source audio from the source video, allowing audio from one source to be sent to the audio output while maintaining video from a different source."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do with the Conference account on the room PC once they are finished using it?",
        "answer": "Log off to ensure the account is fully wiped and that the next group does not have access to anything signed into."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action should be taken to shut down the audio/visual system in conference room ATL 3100A after use?",
        "answer": "Touch the 'Shutdown A/V System' button."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must users connect to in order to display their device in conference room ATL 3100A using a wired connection?",
        "answer": "The HDMI cable coming out of the middle of the desk."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can users find instructions for displaying their devices wirelessly via the Solstice Pod in conference room ATL 3100A?",
        "answer": "On the display in the room."
      },
      {
        "question": "What do the conference rooms provide for controlling the video source and adjusting audio levels?",
        "answer": "A simplified touch panel."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users select to turn off the display and raise the projector screen when shutting down the room?",
        "answer": "The 'Shutdown A/V System' button."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do users connect their devices to the HDMI cable in the conference rooms?",
        "answer": "By connecting their device to the HDMI cable coming out of the middle of the desk."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Apptainer",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command do you use to find out the current version of Apptainer on a UMIACS-supported host?",
        "answer": "apptainer --version"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the previous branding of Apptainer?",
        "answer": "Singularity"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two types of images that Apptainer can run?",
        "answer": "Apptainer's own format and Docker images"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if the command 'apptainer --version' returns 'command not found'?",
        "answer": "Contact staff to ensure that the software is available on the host you are looking for it on."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you set the APPTAINER_CACHEDIR and APPTAINER_TMPDIR to in a local scratch directory setup?",
        "answer": "${WORKDIR}/.cache and ${WORKDIR}/.tmp"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the command to pull a Docker image into a SIF file using Apptainer?",
        "answer": "$ apptainer pull cuda12.2.2.sif docker://nvidia/cuda:12.2.2-base-ubi8"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command needs to be specified to access GPUs inside an Apptainer container?",
        "answer": "--nv"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the location of the shared containers maintained in Nexus?",
        "answer": "/fs/nexus-containers"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command do you use to execute an interactive session with GPUs while binding your Nexus scratch directory?",
        "answer": "apptainer exec --nv --bind /fs/nexus-scratch/username:/fs/nexus-scratch/username /fs/nexus-containers/pytorch/pytorch_1.13.0+cu117.sif bash"
      },
      {
        "question": "What file format is used for portable images in Apptainer?",
        "answer": "Singularity Image Format or .sif files"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the recommended method to create images if you do not have administrative rights on a UMIACS-supported host?",
        "answer": "Use Podman on a UMIACS-supported host or create images on a laptop or personal desktop where you have full administrative access."
      },
      {
        "question": "In the context of the Docker workflow example, where can you clone the example repository for pytorch_docker?",
        "answer": "https://gitlab.umiacs.umd.edu/derek/pytorch_docker"
      }
    ],
    "total": 12
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Network/VPN",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What was the previous name of the Pulse Secure Client before it was rebranded?",
        "answer": "Pulse Secure Client"
      },
      {
        "question": "As of what date was the Pulse Secure Client rebranded as Ivanti Secure Access Client?",
        "answer": "August 14th 2022"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of VPN does UMIACS currently provide access through?",
        "answer": "Ivanti Connect Secure SSL VPN"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is excluded from VPN access provided by UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Class accounts"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is mandatory for users to connect using the UMIACS VPN?",
        "answer": "Enrollment in MFA (Multi-Factor Authentication)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one purpose of using the VPN once connected?",
        "answer": "To access a Windows machine via Remote Desktop client and other non-public UMIACS resources."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which operating systems are mentioned for VPN client setup?",
        "answer": "Windows, macOS, and Linux"
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of mobile devices are specified for VPN configuration?",
        "answer": "iOS and Android devices"
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/CIFS",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is CIFS an enhanced version of?",
        "answer": "CIFS is an enhanced version of SMB."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does CIFS stand for?",
        "answer": "CIFS stands for Common Internet File System."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which protocol is referenced in context with CIFS for more information?",
        "answer": "The protocol referenced is SMB, specifically through its Wikipedia page."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Tcsh",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the two main configuration files for Tcsh?",
        "answer": "~/.tcshrc and ~/.cshrc"
      },
      {
        "question": "In what order does Tcsh source its configuration files?",
        "answer": "It sources ~/.tcshrc first if it is found; if not, it sources ~/.cshrc."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should be typed to get a complete explanation of Tcsh features?",
        "answer": "man tcsh"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can users see their current paths in Tcsh?",
        "answer": "By typing 'echo $PATH' in the terminal."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to add additional paths to the PATH variable in Tcsh?",
        "answer": "setenv PATH ${PATH}:/my/new/path"
      },
      {
        "question": "How does the order of paths in the PATH variable affect program lookup in Tcsh?",
        "answer": "Programs are looked up left to right in the path."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/NFS",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What protocols of Network File System (NFS) are utilized by UMIACS?",
        "answer": "UMIACS utilizes both NFSv2 and NFSv3 protocols."
      },
      {
        "question": "Is there support for NFSv4 at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "No, UMIACS does not provide support for NFSv4."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of authentication do NFSv2 and NFSv3 protocols have at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "NFSv2 and NFSv3 protocols do not have any authentication other than IP based host authentication."
      },
      {
        "question": "How are NFS volumes managed for almost all users at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "NFS volumes will be automatically mounted via the Automounter."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which types of file systems are included in the automatically mounted NFS volumes for users?",
        "answer": "Almost all home directories, web, and ftp file systems are included."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is a restriction placed on core file systems accessed via NFS at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Core file systems are very restricted to who they can be mounted by."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/ConferenceRooms/Reserve",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What must a user ensure before attempting to reserve a room through Google Calendar?",
        "answer": "The user must ensure that they are logged into their UMD account."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which type of email account is required to schedule rooms?",
        "answer": "Only @umd.edu email address accounts can schedule rooms."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if a user tries to log in with a Terpmail account?",
        "answer": "Terpmail accounts will not work for scheduling rooms."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the specific format for the room names that can be reserved?",
        "answer": "Rooms are of the form 'IRB XXXX'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What indicates that a room is not available for reservation?",
        "answer": "Rooms that appear with strikethrough text are not available to reserve at the times chosen."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the final step in the reservation process for a moderated room?",
        "answer": "An email for approval will be sent to the moderator(s) at this point."
      },
      {
        "question": "What distinguishes the validity of reservations in moderated rooms versus auto-accept rooms?",
        "answer": "In moderated rooms, the reservation is not valid until one of the moderators approves it, while in auto-accept rooms, the reservation is valid immediately."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/PythonVirtualEnv",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is a virtual environment in Python?",
        "answer": "A virtual environment is an isolated working copy of Python, which allows you to work on specific projects without affecting others."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to create a virtual environment on Python 3?",
        "answer": "$ python3 -m venv env"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you activate the VirtualEnv after creating it?",
        "answer": "$ source env/bin/activate"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should users of tcsh/csh run to activate their virtual environment?",
        "answer": "source env/bin/activate.csh"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do first after activating a virtual environment?",
        "answer": "Ensure you have an updated version of pip, setuptools and wheel installed in your environment."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command is used to install additional Python modules in the virtual environment?",
        "answer": "$ pip install nose"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you list the installed Python modules in the virtual environment?",
        "answer": "$ pip freeze"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to uninstall a module from the virtual environment?",
        "answer": "$ pip uninstall nose"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the process to switch between different virtual environments?",
        "answer": "Deactivate your current virtual environment, then source another."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you create a virtual environment using a different version of Python?",
        "answer": "Create the virtualenv with your target version of Python using the '--python' flag."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is an essential step to ensure when creating a vanilla environment in a virtualenv?",
        "answer": "It might be a good idea to verify your PYTHONPATH is empty."
      }
    ],
    "total": 11
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/ConferenceRooms/HuddleRoom",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the intended purpose of huddle rooms?",
        "answer": "Huddle rooms are intended for small, short-duration meetings on a first-come, first-serve basis."
      },
      {
        "question": "How are huddle rooms scheduled?",
        "answer": "They are scheduled by walking up to the room and using the Crestron room scheduler panel."
      },
      {
        "question": "How far in advance can huddle rooms be scheduled?",
        "answer": "The panel allows up to 12 hours in advance to be scheduled."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum duration for a single reservation in a huddle room?",
        "answer": "The maximum duration for a single reservation is 2 hours."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of display is available in the huddle rooms?",
        "answer": "Single LCD Display."
      },
      {
        "question": "What technology is available for connecting laptops in the huddle rooms?",
        "answer": "Mersive Solstice, Laptop via HDMI or Mersive Solstice Pod."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ClassAccounts/Manage",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What must all students in a class do to raise issues or questions?",
        "answer": "All students within the class will need to raise issues or questions through the faculty member or TA(s) as the point of contacts."
      },
      {
        "question": "What email should faculty members use to request the creation of a class?",
        "answer": "Faculty members should send an email to staff@umiacs.umd.edu to create a ticket for class resources."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does UMIACS staff confirm the course before creating a class?",
        "answer": "UMIACS staff will confirm the course through UMD Testudo."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of email addresses does the system support for creating student accounts?",
        "answer": "We only support creating accounts for @umd.edu and @terpmail.umd.edu addresses."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if a student does not redeem their account within the specified time?",
        "answer": "If the student does not redeem their account, Faculty/TAs can go into the student's class account request in the app and renew their token."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required for students to access the class account login nodes?",
        "answer": "Class accounts also need to setup Duo multi-factor authentication in order to access the cluster."
      },
      {
        "question": "When will UMIACS Technical Staff install redeemed class accounts?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Technical Staff will install class accounts that have been redeemed once per business day."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a student do if they did not provide a phone number when redeeming their account?",
        "answer": "If a student does not provide a phone number when they redeem their account, the TA will need to contact staff for assistance with password reset."
      },
      {
        "question": "When are class accounts typically deleted after the completion of a semester?",
        "answer": "Class accounts are liable to be archived and deleted as early as February 1st for Winter semesters, June 1st for Spring semesters, September 1st for Summer semesters, and January 1st of the next year for Fall semesters."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/QuICS",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What does QuICS stand for?",
        "answer": "QuICS stands for the Joint Center for Quantum Information and Computer Science."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which two institutions are partners in QuICS?",
        "answer": "The partners in QuICS are the University of Maryland (UMD) and the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is QuICS located?",
        "answer": "QuICS is located at the University of Maryland just outside of Washington, D.C."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the main focuses of QuICS?",
        "answer": "QuICS advances research and education in quantum computer science and quantum information theory."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is necessary to access the QuICS Private Wiki?",
        "answer": "You need to be on the UMIACS network to access the QuICS Private Wiki."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the acronym NIST stand for?",
        "answer": "NIST stands for the National Institute of Standards and Technology."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ConferenceRooms/Solstice",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is Solstice and what does it enable users to do?",
        "answer": "Solstice is a wireless and content sharing solution that enables multiple users to connect simultaneously to a shared display using laptops and mobile devices over an existing wireless network without the need for cables or additional hardware."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which buildings are equipped with Solstice Mersive Pods?",
        "answer": "All conference rooms in the Brendan Iribe Center and some in the Atlantic Building are equipped with Solstice Mersive Pods."
      },
      {
        "question": "What information can be found on the Welcome Screen of a Solstice display?",
        "answer": "The Welcome Screen contains the Solstice display name, a screen key, network information, user connection instructions, and the Solstice display menu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should be followed to connect to a Solstice display using the Solstice user app?",
        "answer": "To connect to a Solstice display using the Solstice user app, ensure you are connected to either the UMD wireless or wired network, search for a specific display by name/IP in the search bar, and when prompted, enter the screen key listed on the Solstice display."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user mirror their iOS device screen to a Solstice display using AirPlay?",
        "answer": "To mirror an iOS device screen to a Solstice display using AirPlay, ensure the iOS device is on the WiFi network used to connect to the display, open the iOS Control Center, tap the Screen Mirroring button, and select the desired Solstice display."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if the desired Solstice display does not appear in the AirPlay menu?",
        "answer": "If the desired display does not appear in the AirPlay menu, the user should open the Solstice App and connect to the desired display, then repeat the steps to access the AirPlay menu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What capability does Miracast provide for Windows devices in relation to Solstice displays?",
        "answer": "Miracast allows users without the Solstice user app to connect and share their screen to the display using Miracast capabilities on their Windows device."
      },
      {
        "question": "What key combination should a user press to connect their Windows laptop to a wireless display?",
        "answer": "A user should hit the Windows key + P to connect their Windows laptop to a wireless display."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the Mersive recommendation for the setting to use when streaming with Miracast?",
        "answer": "Mersive recommends using the Duplicate setting when streaming with Miracast."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user stop Miracast streaming to a Solstice display?",
        "answer": "To stop Miracast streaming to the display, the user should hit the Windows key + P, click Connect to a wireless display, then click Disconnect."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Network",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What service administrates the wireless network on the campus?",
        "answer": "The wireless network on campus is a service administrated by the University of Maryland Department of Information Technology."
      },
      {
        "question": "What network should UMD Directory ID holders use to connect with their email and password?",
        "answer": "UDM Directory ID holders should use the eduroam network with their @umd.edu email address and directory password."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can an individual access the umd-guest network?",
        "answer": "An individual can sign up for and connect to the umd-guest network."
      },
      {
        "question": "What do UMIACS staff do regarding bulk access to the network?",
        "answer": "For bulk access, contact UMIACS Staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "What colors are used to identify wired ports in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Wired ports are typically identified by having a yellow port (Iribe) or orange port (AVW)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do to enable a wired port for their personal laptop or desktop?",
        "answer": "To get a wired port enabled for a personal laptop or desktop, a user should send mail to staff@umiacs.umd.edu noting the room number and identification number of the port."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of issues does the Network Troubleshooting section address?",
        "answer": "The Network Troubleshooting section addresses basic network issues."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SecureShellTunneling",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to forward local port 9999 to the remote port 8000 on the host webserver.umiacs.umd.edu through nexusclip00.umiacs.umd.edu?",
        "answer": "ssh -NfL 9999:webserver.umiacs.umd.edu:8000 nexusclip00.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command allows users to print to the UMIACS CUPS server through an SSH tunnel, specifying their username?",
        "answer": "ssh $<USERNAME>@nexusclip00.umiacs.umd.edu -T -N -L 3631:print.umiacs.umd.edu:631"
      },
      {
        "question": "In PuTTY, where can users find the port forwarding configuration settings?",
        "answer": "Under 'Connection>SSH>Tunnels'"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the command 'ssh -ND 7777 nexusclip00.umiacs.umd.edu' achieve?",
        "answer": "It tunnels all traffic coming into a certain port through a SOCKS v5 proxy."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be entered into the proxy settings of a browser when configuring it to use a SOCKS v5 proxy through an SSH tunnel?",
        "answer": "Enter 127.0.0.1 for the proxy and the port number chosen for dynamic forwarding (7777 in the example)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the function of the 'FoxyProxy' plugin for Firefox mentioned in the passage?",
        "answer": "It allows conditional proxies to be set up, adding intelligence/complexity to the proxy configuration."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the effect of configuring proxy settings for a browser or the whole operating system to use a SOCKS v5 proxy?",
        "answer": "All the traffic for that browser or OS will be sent through the proxy, which can have performance implications."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command would create a local port 13389 that forwards to a remote host running an RDP client on port 3389?",
        "answer": "ssh -L 13389:my-desktop.ad.umiacs.umd.edu:3389 nexusclip00.umiacs.umd.edu"
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/JavaDisableBrowser",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What should you enter in the address bar to disable the Java plugin in Chrome/Chromium?",
        "answer": "about:plugins"
      },
      {
        "question": "In Firefox, which tab must be clicked after entering about:addons to disable the Java plugin?",
        "answer": "the Plugins tab"
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be unchecked in the Security tab under Safari Preferences to disable Java?",
        "answer": "the Enable Java checkbox"
      },
      {
        "question": "In Internet Explorer, which menu path leads to the option for disabling Java applets?",
        "answer": "Tools Menu > Internet Options > Security tab > Custom Level button"
      },
      {
        "question": "In the Security Settings box of Internet Explorer, what option can you select to disable Java applets?",
        "answer": "Disable or Prompt radio button under 'Scripting of Java Applets'"
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Web",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary focus of the section titled 'Web'?",
        "answer": "The section focuses on Web Space, File Transfer Protocol, and Collecting Sensitive Information Online."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which protocols or topics are mentioned in the section related to the Web?",
        "answer": "The topics mentioned include Web Space, File Transfer Protocol, and Collecting Sensitive Information Online."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of information is indicated as being collected online according to the text?",
        "answer": "The text indicates that sensitive information is collected online."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/CBCB",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What does CBCB stand for?",
        "answer": "UMD Center for Bioinformatics and Computational Biology"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary focus of research at CBCB?",
        "answer": "Research on questions arising from the genome revolution"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of center is CBCB described as?",
        "answer": "A multidisciplinary center"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can one find related documentation for CBCB?",
        "answer": "In the CBCB Private Wiki"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required to access the CBCB Private Wiki?",
        "answer": "You need to be on the UMIACS network"
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Mpich1sub.sh.e167",
    "Q/A": [],
    "total": 0
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Nexus/GAMMA",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "Who is allowed to run non-interruptible jobs on the GAMMA lab GPU nodes?",
        "answer": "Only GAMMA lab members are able to run non-interruptible jobs on these nodes."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of additional job Quality of Service (QoS) does the GAMMA partition offer?",
        "answer": "The additional job QoS for the GAMMA partition is 'huge-long', which allows for longer jobs using higher overall resources."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the GrpTRES limit for jobs running in the GAMMA partition?",
        "answer": "The GrpTRES limit is 100% of the available cores/RAM on the partition-specific nodes in aggregate plus 50% of the available cores/RAM on legacy nodes in aggregate."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum home directory storage allocated to each user in GAMMA?",
        "answer": "Each user has 30GB of home directory storage available."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must a user include when requesting a project-based allocation?",
        "answer": "A user must include the Project Name, Description, Size, Length in days, and other users that need to access the allocation, if any."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of scratch directories are available in GAMMA?",
        "answer": "There are two types of scratch directories: Network scratch directories and Local scratch directories."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should be used to run an interactive job while specifying the necessary parameters?",
        "answer": "$ srun --pty --gres=gpu:8 --account=gamma --partition=gamma --qos=huge-long bash"
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to the scratch data after 90 days in the local scratch directories?",
        "answer": "A tmpwatch job will delete unaccessed data after 90 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "How much scratch space can be requested permanently without faculty approval?",
        "answer": "Up to 200GB total space can be requested permanently without faculty approval."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is the read-only dataset storage available in GAMMA?",
        "answer": "The read-only dataset storage is available at /fs/gamma-datasets."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/EquipmentLoans",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum duration for which general equipment loans are available?",
        "answer": "General equipment loans are available for a maximum of 2-weeks."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do to request a loaner laptop or projector?",
        "answer": "To request a loaner laptop or projector, a user should visit the specified request link."
      },
      {
        "question": "What items does UMIACS commonly stock for equipment loans?",
        "answer": "Common items UMIACS stocks include external hard drives, mice, keyboards, tool sets, and more."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who should be contacted for the availability of equipment requests not listed?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Staff should be contacted for the availability of other equipment requests."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is UMIACS's policy regarding data on loaner devices?",
        "answer": "UMIACS staff is not responsible for backing up any data stored on loaner devices and will wipe the device upon its return."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must users do with any data they wish to keep before returning a loaner device?",
        "answer": "Users must copy any data they wish to keep elsewhere before returning the device."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action is required to digitally sign a loaner form?",
        "answer": "To digitally sign a loaner form, users need to see the specified page."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Nexus/MBRC",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the submission host where users can SSH to log in?",
        "answer": "nexusmbrc.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which nodes were brought over from the previous standalone MBRC Slurm scheduler?",
        "answer": "The compute nodes are named mbrc##."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional job QoS allows for longer jobs using higher overall resources?",
        "answer": "huge-long"
      },
      {
        "question": "What must users specify to submit jobs to the MBRC partition?",
        "answer": "--partition=mbrc and --account=mbrc"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the point of contact for allocating requested storage for projects in the MBRC Cluster?",
        "answer": "Jonathan Heagerty"
      },
      {
        "question": "What information must be provided when making a request for storage?",
        "answer": "Name of user requesting storage, Name of project, Collaborators working on the project, Storage size, Length of time for storage."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default maximum runtime for jobs submitted to the MBRC partition?",
        "answer": "1-00:00:00 (1 day)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two actual submission hosts mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "nexusmbrc00.umiacs.umd.edu and nexusmbrc01.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should happen if the requested storage size is significantly large relative to the total allotted amount?",
        "answer": "The request will be relayed from Jonathan Heagerty to the MBRC Cluster faculty for approval."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the GrpTRES limit for jobs in the MBRC partition?",
        "answer": "100% of the available cores/RAM on the partition-specific nodes in aggregate plus 50% of the available cores/RAM on legacy## nodes in aggregate."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/ConferenceRooms/Solstice/Solstice_App",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the two options available for first-time users to download the Solstice user app?",
        "answer": "First-time users can either download the user app from the Solstice App Downloads page or download the app directly from the host."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does a user download the Solstice User App directly from the host?",
        "answer": "A user must open a browser on their device, enter the IP address visible on the Solstice display, and then the Solstice Quick Connect page will open."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens when a user clicks 'Get the App & Join' on the Solstice Quick Connect page?",
        "answer": "If the user is on a laptop, the user app will download and launch automatically. If the user is on an Android or iOS device, the appropriate app marketplace will open and display the user app available for download."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to the Solstice user app once it is installed on a device?",
        "answer": "Once installed, the app will remain on the device for future use and will not need to be installed again."
      },
      {
        "question": "What tab should a user visit to manually enter the IP address on the Solstice user app interface?",
        "answer": "The user should go to the 'Enter IP' tab to manually enter the IP address shown on the display’s Welcome Screen."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Nexus/MC2",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "When did the compute nodes from the previous standalone MC2 cluster fold into Nexus?",
        "answer": "As of mid 2022."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the names of the actual submission hosts for the MC2 partition?",
        "answer": "nexusmc200.umiacs.umd.edu and nexusmc201.umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What standard job QoSes are available to MC2 users using the mc2 account?",
        "answer": "All of the standard job QoSes in the MC2 partition."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the command that needs to be specified to submit jobs to the MC2 partition?",
        "answer": "--partition=mc2 and --account=mc2."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional job QoS options are specifically available for the MC2 partition?",
        "answer": "highmem and huge-long."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the GrpTRES limit for the MC2 partition?",
        "answer": "100% of the available cores/RAM on the partition-specific nodes in aggregate plus 50% of the available cores/RAM on legacy## nodes in aggregate."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command was issued to run a job in the MC2 partition in the example provided?",
        "answer": "srun --pty --ntasks=4 --mem=8G --qos=default --partition=mc2 --account=mc2 --time 1-00:00:00 bash."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the time limit set for the job with JobId 218874 in the provided example?",
        "answer": "1-00:00:00."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the node names in the MC2 partition?",
        "answer": "twist##."
      },
      {
        "question": "What resources are listed for job 218874 based on the provided job details?",
        "answer": "cpu=4, mem=8G, node=1."
      },
      {
        "question": "What file systems are available to MC2 users in Nexus?",
        "answer": "All data filesystems that were available in the standalone MC2 cluster."
      }
    ],
    "total": 11
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Lamsub2.sh",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the shebang line present in the script?",
        "answer": "#!/bin/bash"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many nodes are specified in the PBS resource request?",
        "answer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum wall time allocated for the job in the PBS settings?",
        "answer": "5:00"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which directory does the script change to before executing any commands?",
        "answer": "~/torquejobs/lamtest"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to boot the LAM (Local Area Multicomputer) environment?",
        "answer": "lamboot $PBS_NODEFILE"
      },
      {
        "question": "What MPI command is executed to perform the alltoall operation?",
        "answer": "mpirun C alltoall-lam"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is called at the end of the script to halt the LAM environment?",
        "answer": "lamhalt"
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/CUPS",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What printing system has UMIACS replaced with CUPS?",
        "answer": "LPRng printing system"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of CUPS in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "It provides better support for printers and their specific options."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should be used to specify duplex printing with CUPS?",
        "answer": "-o sides=two-sided-long-edge"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command is the main supported command for printing in CUPS?",
        "answer": "lp command"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a list of printers be accessed on UMIACS Networks?",
        "answer": "By using the command lpstat -p or visiting http://print.umiacs.umd.edu/printers"
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if jobs in the queue from the other print system misbehave?",
        "answer": "They can cause the other print system queue to stall."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default behavior regarding banner pages for print queues in CUPS?",
        "answer": "All queues are no banner queues by default."
      },
      {
        "question": "If a user wants to change the banner page behavior for their account, what command should they use?",
        "answer": "lpoptions -o job-sheets=standard PRINTER_QUEUE"
      },
      {
        "question": "What documentation should be referenced for command-line printing from RHEL/Ubuntu hosts?",
        "answer": "http://www.cups.org/doc/options.html"
      },
      {
        "question": "What can a user do if they encounter a problem with the print system queues?",
        "answer": "Contact staff for assistance."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/HelpDesk",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What types of support does the UMIACS Help Desk provide?",
        "answer": "Technical Support and Equipment Procurement."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is the UMIACS Help Desk located?",
        "answer": "Brendan Iribe Center for Computer Science and Engineering Room 310, 98125 Paint Branch Drive, College Park, MD 20742."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the operation hours of the UMIACS Help Desk?",
        "answer": "9:00am - 5:00pm Monday - Friday (excluding University Holidays)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which email address should be used for technical support inquiries at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "staff@umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the phone number for the UMIACS Help Desk?",
        "answer": "(301) 405-1775."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which email should be used for equipment procurement requests?",
        "answer": "orders@umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "For room access requests and building-related inquiries, which email address should be contacted?",
        "answer": "facilities@umiacs.umd.edu."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Windows_Personal_Backups",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What built-in backup tool does the article focus on for creating personal backups on Windows devices?",
        "answer": "File History"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of drive is required for creating personal backups according to the prerequisites section?",
        "answer": "A portable hard drive formatted with the NTFS file system."
      },
      {
        "question": "What edition of Windows is necessary to use the backup procedure mentioned in the article?",
        "answer": "Any desktop edition of Windows 10/11."
      },
      {
        "question": "How frequently does File History back up files by default?",
        "answer": "Every one hour."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if the portable hard drive is disconnected for 5 days or more?",
        "answer": "You will receive a Windows notification, and backups will automatically resume upon reconnecting the drive."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action must be taken to include or exclude folders in the backup process?",
        "answer": "Click on More options."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the recommendation regarding the security of backups mentioned in the overview section?",
        "answer": "We strongly encourage encrypting your backups."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you find instructions on how to prepare an encrypted portable hard drive for backups?",
        "answer": "BitLocker/PersonalUse"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command must be executed to start a manual backup?",
        "answer": "Click Back up now."
      },
      {
        "question": "What default folders does File History backup when it is enabled?",
        "answer": "All folders in C:\\Users\\<yourusername>."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/LocalDataStorage",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of storage refers to data physically stored at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Local (data) storage."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum quota allocated to each user for the network home directory local storage?",
        "answer": "30GB, non-expandable Quota."
      },
      {
        "question": "How is user data backed up in UNIX local storage?",
        "answer": "User directories use redundant, backed-up network file shares."
      },
      {
        "question": "What directories in UNIX local storage may not be used for permanent storage of unique, important data?",
        "answer": "/tmp, /scratch0, /scratch1, and any directory named in whole or in part 'tmp', 'temp', or 'scratch'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to user directories when a host is decommissioned in the Windows and macOS local storage section?",
        "answer": "User directories go into the Archives."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which local storage option does UMIACS discourage due to high vulnerability to data loss or theft?",
        "answer": "Direct-attached local storage."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the naming convention for network-attached local storage shares dedicated for datasets and project storage?",
        "answer": "/fs/<lab>-<purpose> (i.e., /fs/cml-models or /fs/vulcan-projects)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Are network-attached local scratch storage shares backed up or archived by UMIACS?",
        "answer": "No, network-attached local scratch storage is not backed up or archived by UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What CLI command shows current memory (RAM) usage and can display this information in a human-readable format?",
        "answer": "free -h."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do if they find network-attached local storage space documentation that does not state its retention policy?",
        "answer": "Contact staff."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/PrinterQueueNaming",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary function of the centralized print server used by UMIACS?",
        "answer": "To manage all of the printers in the Institute."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be used in the printer queue naming scheme if a printer is in building number 432?",
        "answer": "The name should include '432-' after the type of printer."
      },
      {
        "question": "In the naming scheme for printer queues, what letter represents color printers?",
        "answer": "'c' represents color printers."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default type of printer indicated in the naming scheme?",
        "answer": "Black & white is the default, so nothing extra is needed."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two types of printer drivers mentioned, and how do they affect naming?",
        "answer": "PostScript and PCL are the two types of printer drivers, with 'ps' for PostScript-enabled queues and 'pcl' for Printer Command Language-enabled queues."
      },
      {
        "question": "If a printer is located in room 3208 of building 432, how would its queue be named?",
        "answer": "The queue would be named 'ps432-3208' if it is black & white."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the example name for a color printer located in Atlantic building room 3261?",
        "answer": "The example name is 'cps224-3261'."
      },
      {
        "question": "Why should someone use 'ps' for PostScript if they are unsure about the printer driver options?",
        "answer": "Because PCL drivers may not always be available."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/Support",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of support does UMIACS provide for university-owned systems?",
        "answer": "UMIACS provides hardware and operating system (OS) support for university-owned systems across its various labs and centers."
      },
      {
        "question": "What services are included under Hardware Services at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The Hardware Services at UMIACS include in-warranty hardware diagnostic and replacement and Hardware Integration."
      },
      {
        "question": "List two services provided under Operating System Services by UMIACS.",
        "answer": "Two services provided under Operating System Services by UMIACS are OS Deployment and Security Updates."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the email address for contacting UMIACS Technical Support?",
        "answer": "The email address for contacting UMIACS Technical Support is staff@umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the phone number for UMIACS Technical Support?",
        "answer": "(301) 405-1775."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is the Help Desk for UMIACS located?",
        "answer": "The Help Desk for UMIACS is located at 3109 Iribe Center."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Creating_service_admin_user_on_macOS",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "Why is it critical to create a Service Admin User before taking an Apple product to the Terrapin Tech store?",
        "answer": "Technicians at the store require an admin user name and password, and if the pre-existing password is the same as your UMIACS domain login password, revealing it to the technicians would represent a security vulnerability."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must you do to create a new temporary user account with administrator privileges?",
        "answer": "Make sure you are logged in to an administrator account on your MacBook, navigate to System Preferences, select 'Users and Groups', click on the 'Add User' button, select 'Administrator' from the 'New User' dropdown menu, set the full name to 'Service Admin', and the account name to 'serviceadmin'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should the password for the new Service Admin account be?",
        "answer": "The password is up to you, so long as it's not the same as your UMIACS account password or your UMD Directory ID password."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action should you take after the service is completed?",
        "answer": "Once the service is completed, the account can be deleted."
      },
      {
        "question": "What credentials should you provide to the technician when prompted by the Terrapin Tech store?",
        "answer": "You should give this account's credentials to the technician, not your UMIACS account credentials."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Torch",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What versions of Cuda are required when compiling Torch?",
        "answer": "You have to use Cuda 8 or Cuda 7.5 when compiling Torch."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if you encounter issues while compiling Torch?",
        "answer": "You should contact staff if you have issues, as there are some local packages that are required and could cause the install to fail."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which software should be loaded into the environment using GNU Modules before compiling Torch?",
        "answer": "The software to load includes cuda/8.0.61, cudnn, zeromq, nodejs, sox, and GraphicsMagick."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to create and activate a Python environment assuming the use of the bash shell?",
        "answer": "The commands are 'virtualenv env' followed by 'source env/bin/activate'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What two dependencies are installed after upgrading the python pip package manager?",
        "answer": "The two dependencies are pyzmq and ipython."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the command to clone the Torch repository with all its sub-dependencies?",
        "answer": "The command is 'git clone https://github.com/torch/distro.git torch --recursive'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is run to build Torch after changing the directory to the torch folder?",
        "answer": "The command is './install.sh'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is provided as an example to activate the Torch environment?",
        "answer": "The command is 'source install/bin/torch-activate'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the content of the file 'torch_test.th' used to test the installation of Torch?",
        "answer": "The contents are: a = torch.Tensor(5,3); a = torch.rand(5,3); b = torch.rand(3,4); c = torch.Tensor(5,4); c:mm(a,b); print(c); require 'cutorch'; a = a:cuda(); b = b:cuda(); c = c:cuda(); c:mm(a,b); print(c)."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Nexus/Accounts",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is required for all accounts in the Nexus and UMIACS accounts?",
        "answer": "All accounts in the Nexus (and UMIACS accounts in general) are required to be sponsored."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can new accounts be requested according to the text?",
        "answer": "New accounts can be requested via the Requests application."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who can use the Requests application to request new accounts for themselves?",
        "answer": "UMIACS and CSD faculty members can use the Requests application to request new accounts for themselves."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who should be listed as the Principal Investigator when faculty members are filling out the Requests application?",
        "answer": "The username of the current Director of Computing Facilities at UMIACS, who is currently derek, should be listed as the Principal Investigator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the time frame for account installation after approval from the Director of Computing Facilities?",
        "answer": "The account will be installed within 24 business hours (9am-5pm M-F)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must students do when requesting an account as directed by a faculty member?",
        "answer": "Students or collaborators must use the UMIACS account username of the UMIACS or CSD faculty member as the Principal Investigator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if a faculty sponsor leaves UMIACS/CSD or revokes sponsorship of an account?",
        "answer": "You will be given 30 days to find a new account sponsor, and if this 30 days lapse, your account will be archived and removed."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Duo",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What does Duo provide for UMD centralized information technology resources and UMIACS local resources?",
        "answer": "Duo is the multi-factor authentication (MFA) solution for both UMD centralized information technology resources (DivIT) and UMIACS local resources."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two components that multi-factor solutions ensure for authentication?",
        "answer": "Something you know (i.e. your password) and something you have (phone/tablet/token)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must users do individually for UMD and UMIACS regarding Duo enrollment?",
        "answer": "Enrollment is discrete and must be done for both UMD (if you have a UMD appointment) and UMIACS individually."
      },
      {
        "question": "Can the same hardware token be used for both UMD and UMIACS services?",
        "answer": "No, the same hardware token cannot be used; you can enroll the same phone for both services but not the same hardware token."
      },
      {
        "question": "What actions may be taken if a Duo authentication factor is shared with another UMIACS user?",
        "answer": "Action may be taken against your account if you share a registered Duo authentication factor with any other UMIACS user."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which devices are suggested for seamless enrollment with Duo?",
        "answer": "Users are encouraged to enroll with their smartphone as it provides the most seamless experience."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do before disposing of a currently registered phone or tablet?",
        "answer": "You should consider enrolling your new device before getting rid of your old device."
      },
      {
        "question": "What options are available for generating one-time codes when phone data or calls are not available?",
        "answer": "You may use the Duo App on your phone or tablet to generate one-time codes or use YubiKey hardware tokens."
      },
      {
        "question": "What services are secured with the Duo MFA solution?",
        "answer": "The following UMIACS services are secured with Duo: GitLab, Jira, Object Storage, VPN, Directory, Requests, MediaWiki log ins, and SSH (when coming in from off-campus)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users create to work around issues cloning HTTPS Git repositories in GitLab due to Duo's requirements?",
        "answer": "Users should set up an SSH key instead of using UMIACS credentials directly for accessing HTTPS Git repositories."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SLURM/JobStatus",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command shows job status in the queue?",
        "answer": "The squeue command shows job status in the queue."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which flag would you use with the squeue command to show only your jobs?",
        "answer": "-u username to show only your jobs."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the --start flag do in the squeue command?",
        "answer": "--start estimates start time for a job that has not yet started and the reason why it is waiting."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is displayed if you do not specify a job step when using the sstat command?",
        "answer": "If you don't specify a job step, the lowest job step is displayed."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of information does the sacct command provide?",
        "answer": "The sacct command shows metrics from past jobs."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is indicated by the 'PD' status when checking running jobs?",
        "answer": "'PD' indicates that the job is in Pending status."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you determine the reason why a job is in a Pending state?",
        "answer": "You can determine the reason by looking at the NODELIST parameter or by using the scontrol show job <jobid> command."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'Resources' reason indicate when a job is in the PD state?",
        "answer": "It indicates that the cluster does not currently have the resources to fit your job in your selected partition."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command would you use to check the current reservations in SLURM?",
        "answer": "You would use the scontrol show reservation command to check the current reservations."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if your requested TimeLimit conflicts with a maintenance reservation?",
        "answer": "You can lower your TimeLimit so that the job will complete before the reservation begins, or leave your job to wait until the reservation completes."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ConferenceRooms/Zoom",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What should you do if the conference room PC is already signed into the desktop?",
        "answer": "Sign out of the desktop and then sign in again to ensure a clean slate."
      },
      {
        "question": "How long will it take for the conference room PC to automatically sign out due to inactivity?",
        "answer": "It will automatically sign out after 8 hours of inactivity."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which account should be selected when logging into the conference room PC?",
        "answer": "Select the Conference account."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps are required to log into Zoom using UMD credentials?",
        "answer": "Click on 'Sign in with SSO', type in 'umd' under company domain, and click 'Continue'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What information is required to join an existing Zoom meeting?",
        "answer": "A meeting ID (usually a 10-11 digit number) or a personal link."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you invite others to your Zoom meeting?",
        "answer": "Click on 'participants' at the bottom, then click the 'invite' button, and finally click the 'Copy Invitation' button."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action must be taken to connect Zoom audio using the lectern microphone?",
        "answer": "Unmute the mic and unmute yourself on Zoom."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you adjust in Zoom settings to display video from a personal laptop?",
        "answer": "Select 'laptop', then route it to shared video and/or projector or monitor."
      },
      {
        "question": "What to do after the Zoom meeting regarding the Conference account?",
        "answer": "Sign out of the Conference account and shut down the A/V system."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Screen",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is GNU Screen and what functionality does it provide?",
        "answer": "GNU Screen, or 'screen', is a window management program that allows multiplexing of a single terminal between multiple virtual consoles and can separate programs from the shell to keep them running even if the connection to the host is lost."
      },
      {
        "question": "When is it typically advantageous to use Screen?",
        "answer": "Screen is typically used when a network connection is unstable and the process must remain running even if an SSH connection has dropped, or when a process is slow and other processes need to be running."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you start editing a file named program.c using Screen in the vi editor?",
        "answer": "You can start editing the file program.c in vi by using the command '# screen vi program.c'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command would you use to detach from the current screen session?",
        "answer": "You would use the command '# screen -d' to detach from the current screen session."
      },
      {
        "question": "What would the output of '# screen -ls' look like if there are two detached sessions?",
        "answer": "The output would be similar to: '# There are screens on:#  26598.screenTest1 (Detached)#  18457.pts-0.tron02 (Detached)# 2 Sockets in /var/run/screen/S-username.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the function of the Ctrl-A + k command in Screen?",
        "answer": "The Ctrl-A + k command is used to kill the current window in Screen."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to a screen session when a program running in a single window exits?",
        "answer": "When a program running in a screen session that has only one window exits, the screen session will terminate as well."
      },
      {
        "question": "What customization can be done using the .screenrc file in a user's home directory?",
        "answer": "The .screenrc file can be used to customize a screen session's startup behavior by executing commands upon starting screen, such as displaying the window number and name or altering key sequences for screen commands."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Ctrl-A + ' command in Screen?",
        "answer": "The Ctrl-A + ' command presents a selection of screen windows from which to choose."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you find a full list of Ctrl-A commands?",
        "answer": "A full list of Ctrl-A commands can be found in the documentation available at the GNU Screen manual link."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Podman",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is Podman and how does it differ from Docker in terms of user namespaces?",
        "answer": "Podman is a daemonless container engine alternative to Docker, and it has the ability to run containers in user namespaces, allowing processes within a namespace to map to a new uid/gid range, unlike Docker which grants trivial administrative control over the host."
      },
      {
        "question": "What issues arise when using Podman with home directories available over NFS?",
        "answer": "When using Podman with home directories available over NFS, there is an issue that due to user name space mapping, users will not be able to access their home directory while building layers."
      },
      {
        "question": "In the context of Podman, what command should a user run if they encounter an error about no subuid ranges on their workstation?",
        "answer": "A user should contact staff with the error message and the host that they are using if they receive an error like 'cannot find mappings for user username: No subuid ranges found for user \"username\" in /etc/subuid'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default location for storing container image layers in Podman, and where should it be updated if using NFS?",
        "answer": "The default location for storing container image layers in Podman is specified in the graphroot setting of ~/.config/containers/storage.conf, which should be updated to a local directory on the host if using NFS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional configuration steps are needed to run Podman with local Nvidia GPUs?",
        "answer": "To run Podman with local Nvidia GPUs, staff must ensure the nvidia-container-runtime package is installed on any individual workstation or standalone (non-cluster) server."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user build their own image starting from an example repository using Podman?",
        "answer": "A user can build their own image by cloning the example repository, changing the directory to the cloned repository, and then running the command 'podman build -t gpudocker .'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command allows users to run a test script with Podman to verify GPU functionality?",
        "answer": "The command to run a test script with Podman to verify GPU functionality is '$ podman run --volume `pwd`/test:/mnt --hooks-dir=/usr/share/containers/oci/hooks.d gpudocker python3 /mnt/test_torch.py'."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/WindowsServicing",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are 'feature updates' designed to do for Windows machines?",
        "answer": "Feature updates are designed to bring a large set of new features to all machines that can run Windows."
      },
      {
        "question": "How frequently does Microsoft typically release feature updates for Windows?",
        "answer": "Feature updates are typically released annually by Microsoft."
      },
      {
        "question": "When did UMIACS deploy the current Windows 10 feature release?",
        "answer": "The current Windows 10 feature release was deployed on March 15th, 2023."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the end of support date for Windows 10?",
        "answer": "Windows 10 reaches end of support on October 14th, 2025."
      },
      {
        "question": "What OS versions are currently being feature released at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The current feature releases at UMIACS are Windows 10 version 22H2 and Windows 11 version 23H2."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of supplemental updates that follow feature updates?",
        "answer": "Supplemental updates are security patches that must be installed after the feature update itself."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does the Windows Patch Management handle the installation of feature updates?",
        "answer": "The Windows Patch Management automatically installs feature updates when released to supported systems, and users receive notifications to install them."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional steps may be required after installing a feature update?",
        "answer": "Additional reboots may be required while installing the supplemental updates thereafter, in addition to the reboot issued as part of the feature update install process."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does UMIACS ensure compatibility of feature updates?",
        "answer": "UMIACS releases feature updates to be installed several months after Microsoft releases them to the general public to ensure compatibility with all software that is run, such as their VPN."
      },
      {
        "question": "What documentation would one refer to for a comprehensive list of what is new in the feature updates?",
        "answer": "For a comprehensive list of what is new in these feature updates, one can see Microsoft's documentation."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/ConferenceRooms/View",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of accounts are necessary to view the room schedules?",
        "answer": "Only UMD accounts can view rooms."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which URL must be navigated to in order to view room schedules?",
        "answer": "https://calendar.google.com"
      },
      {
        "question": "What information will Google prompt you for when adding a UMD account?",
        "answer": "Your email/phone, which is your UMD username appended with @umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action must a user take if they do not have a current session open?",
        "answer": "They will be redirected to the UMD CAS login page."
      },
      {
        "question": "What button does a user need to click to access the settings menu on Google Calendar?",
        "answer": "The cog in the top right."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user addIribe conference rooms to their Google Calendar view?",
        "answer": "By expanding Add Calendar on the left pane and selecting Browse resources, then ticking the checkbox for each room they want to add."
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you need to do to temporarily hide one or more calendars you subscribed to?",
        "answer": "Untick individual calendars on the left pane."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens when a user switches to Day view in Google Calendar?",
        "answer": "It will show one column per room."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MBRC",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What does MBRC stand for?",
        "answer": "MBRC stands for the Maryland Blended Research Center."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is the MBRC located?",
        "answer": "The MBRC is located at the University of Maryland."
      },
      {
        "question": "Within which institute is the MBRC situated?",
        "answer": "The MBRC is situated within the Institute for Advanced Computer Studies."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of computational resources does the MBRC have?",
        "answer": "The MBRC has a cluster of computational (CPU/GPU) resources."
      },
      {
        "question": "Are the computational resources at the MBRC available for scheduling?",
        "answer": "Yes, the computational resources at the MBRC are available to be scheduled."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can details on the MBRC cluster be found?",
        "answer": "Details on the MBRC cluster can be found on their official website."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MacOSDisplayModes",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to start changing display settings on MacOS?",
        "answer": "Open your System Preferences from the Dock or Applications folder."
      },
      {
        "question": "After opening System Preferences, which option should be clicked to access display settings?",
        "answer": "Click Displays."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which tab must be accessed to change the display mode?",
        "answer": "Go to the Arrangement tab."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default mode for displays on MacOS according to the text?",
        "answer": "The displays are used in extended mode."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action must be taken to switch from extended mode to mirror mode?",
        "answer": "Select the mirror checkbox."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Nexus/CML",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "When did the CML cluster's compute nodes fold into Nexus?",
        "answer": "The compute nodes from CML's previous standalone cluster have folded into Nexus as of the scheduled maintenance window for August 2023 (Thursday 08/17/2023, 5-8pm)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command do you use to log in to a submission host on Nexus?",
        "answer": "You can SSH to nexuscml.umiacs.umd.edu to log in to a submission host."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is prepended to all of the values that were present in the standalone CML cluster after integration with Nexus?",
        "answer": "The prefix cml- is prepended to all of the values that were present in the standalone CML cluster."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum submission limit of jobs per user in the cml-dpart partition?",
        "answer": "The cml-dpart partition has a max submission limit of 500 jobs per user simultaneously."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which CML partition allows jobs longer run times and more resources, but is preemptable?",
        "answer": "The cml-scavenger partition allows jobs longer run times and more resources, but is preemptable."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the total amount of home directory storage available to users?",
        "answer": "You have 30GB of home directory storage available at /nfshomes/<username>."
      },
      {
        "question": "What approvals are required for project-based allocations between 3TB and 6TB?",
        "answer": "Allocations above 3TB (up to 6TB) require approval from both a CML faculty member and the director of CML."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the storage limit for the network scratch directory?",
        "answer": "You have 200GB of scratch storage available at /cmlscratch/<username>."
      },
      {
        "question": "How often does the tmpwatch job delete unaccessed data from local scratch directories?",
        "answer": "The tmpwatch job will delete unaccessed data after 90 days, scheduled via maintenance jobs to run once a month during our monthly maintenance windows."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to check the total number of Track-able Resources (TRES) allowed for each account?",
        "answer": "$ sacctmgr show assoc account=cml format=user,account,qos,grptres"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/UserReport",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is required for an account to be established in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "All accounts in UMIACS are sponsored by a faculty member."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of reports does UMIACS provide to faculty members?",
        "answer": "UMIACS provides reports to give faculty members information on the status of the account(s) they have sponsored."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'username' field in a UMIACS user report?",
        "answer": "The 'username' field represents the UMIACS username for the account."
      },
      {
        "question": "What information does the 'uidnumber' field contain?",
        "answer": "The 'uidnumber' field contains a numeric identifier for the UMIACS username."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'gidnumber' represent in the user report?",
        "answer": "The 'gidnumber' is a numeric identifier for the account's UMIACS default group."
      },
      {
        "question": "How is the 'name' field in the user report determined?",
        "answer": "'name' is the display name if set, or the full name if the display name is not set."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'sponsors' field list?",
        "answer": "The 'sponsors' field lists UMIACS usernames for account sponsors, separated by semicolons."
      },
      {
        "question": "What information is found in the 'groups' field?",
        "answer": "The 'groups' field lists UMIACS unix groups the user is a member of, separated by semicolons."
      },
      {
        "question": "What do the 'secgroups' represent in the user report?",
        "answer": "The 'secgroups' represent UMIACS security groups the user is a member of, separated by semicolons."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'crs' field denote?",
        "answer": "The 'crs' field lists the Computational Resources the user is allowed to access in UMIACS, separated by semicolons."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does UMIACS handle user email addresses according to the 'emailtype' field?",
        "answer": "The 'emailtype' field indicates how UMIACS handles their username@umiacs.umd.edu email."
      },
      {
        "question": "What information does the 'installed' field represent?",
        "answer": "The 'installed' field represents the date and time when the account was first installed in UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'lastlogon' field indicate?",
        "answer": "The 'lastlogon' field indicates the date and time when the account was last authenticated with a password."
      },
      {
        "question": "Why may the 'lastlogon' date and time not be completely accurate?",
        "answer": "Due to active directory technical design, it may not be completely accurate in the last 5-14 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'recoverysms' field signify?",
        "answer": "The 'recoverysms' field indicates whether the user has a recovery SMS number on file for automated password resets."
      }
    ],
    "total": 15
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/WindowsPython",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What must be unchecked during the installation of Python via the .exe installer to avoid installation failure?",
        "answer": "The 'Install launcher for all users' box must be unchecked."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to install Python using an MSI installer?",
        "answer": "Download the Python windows MSI installer from https://www.python.org/download/."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user access Python from the command line after installing via the MSI installer?",
        "answer": "The user must add the python folder to their path."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which file must be edited to configure Python to work with Visual Studio when using easy_install?",
        "answer": "The file msvc9compiler.py must be edited."
      },
      {
        "question": "What commands should be used to replace specific lines in the msvc9compiler.py file?",
        "answer": "The line containing toolskey = 'VS%0.f0COMNTOOLS' % version should be replaced with toolskey = 'vs110COMNTOOLS', and mfinfo = self.manifest_get_embed_info(target_desc, Id_args) should be replaced with mfinfo = None."
      },
      {
        "question": "What directory contains the installed files after using easy_install graphical installer?",
        "answer": "The installed files should be located in C:\\Path\\To\\Python\\Folder\\..\\Scripts."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command-line tool is used to install Python modules after adding the directory to the path?",
        "answer": "The command 'python setup.py install' is used to install Python modules."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can numPy be installed from according to the document?",
        "answer": "NumPy can be installed with the installer found at https://pypi.python.org/pypi/numpy/."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps are suggested to add the Python folder to the system path on Windows?",
        "answer": "Navigate to Control Panel -> System and Security -> System, select Advanced system settings, then in the Advanced tab, click the Environment Variables button, check if a Variable called Path exists, and if so, add the python directory to the end. If it does not exist, create a new variable 'Path' and set the value to the path of the Python directory."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ActiveDirectory",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What standard authentication is Windows Authentication based on?",
        "answer": "Kerberos"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are three places where ActiveDirectory authentication is used to log in?",
        "answer": "UMIACS-supported computers, UMIACS-supported web services, UMIACS VPN"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two alternate ways an account might be shown depending on the application used?",
        "answer": "UMIACS\\username and username@ad.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of extensions does Windows Authentication have in relation to Kerberos?",
        "answer": "Some extensions"
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Jekyll",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of site generator is Jekyll described as?",
        "answer": "Jekyll is a blog-aware, static site generator."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does Jekyll differ from many CMS solutions in terms of dependencies?",
        "answer": "Jekyll does not rely on a serverside scripting language and a database."
      },
      {
        "question": "What files can Jekyll sites be deployed to?",
        "answer": "Jekyll sites can be deployed to any web tree that can serve static files."
      },
      {
        "question": "What three web development technologies does Jekyll allow users to design their site with?",
        "answer": "HTML, CSS, and Javascript."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does Jekyll do when ready to update the content?",
        "answer": "Jekyll compiles your templates and content files into full HTML."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is an example of a Jekyll-generated site mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "The UMIACS Intranet page."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which guide are the instructions for getting started with Jekyll taken from?",
        "answer": "The official Jekyll quickstart guide."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the command to install Jekyll and bundler gems?",
        "answer": "gem install jekyll bundler."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to create a new Jekyll site?",
        "answer": "jekyll new mysite."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command do you use to build the site and make it available on a local server?",
        "answer": "bundle exec jekyll serve."
      },
      {
        "question": "What URL should you browse to in order to access your newly created Jekyll site on the local server?",
        "answer": "http://localhost:4000."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you find instructions to publish a Jekyll site to the Object Store?",
        "answer": "On the GitLab page for Jekyll Builder."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can the Jekyll site be configured to publish updates?",
        "answer": "To publish automatically every time you push updates to GitLab."
      }
    ],
    "total": 13
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Mpich1.csh",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What environment variable is set to the path of MPICH in the provided script?",
        "answer": "MPI_ROOT"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the command used to set the MPI_LIB environment variable?",
        "answer": "setenv MPI_LIB  $MPI_ROOT/lib"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which directory is added to the path for MPICH commands like mpirun and mpicc?",
        "answer": "$MPI_BIN"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to modify the MANPATH environment variable in the script?",
        "answer": "setenv MANPATH"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the MPICH commands that get added to the path according to the script?",
        "answer": "mpirun and mpicc"
      },
      {
        "question": "What action is taken if the MANPATH variable is already defined in the script?",
        "answer": "The script appends $MPI_ROOT/man to the existing MANPATH."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the base directory for MPI includes as defined in the script?",
        "answer": "$MPI_ROOT/includes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which shell command is used to set the path in the script?",
        "answer": "set path=($MPI_BIN $path)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default value assigned to the MPI_INC variable in the script?",
        "answer": "$MPI_ROOT/include"
      },
      {
        "question": "What version of MPICH is mentioned in the provided script?",
        "answer": "gm-1.2.7p1-20"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/BashForWindows",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What partnership led to the creation of the Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL)?",
        "answer": "Microsoft has partnered with Canonical, the makers of Ubuntu."
      },
      {
        "question": "List three Linux command line tools mentioned that can be used through Bash on Windows.",
        "answer": "grep, sed, git."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the minimum required version of Windows to install Bash/WSL?",
        "answer": "A 64-bit version of Windows 10 version 1607 or later."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user check if their Windows version is compatible with Bash/WSL?",
        "answer": "In Windows, open the Settings app > System > About."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be done first to install Bash/WSL on Windows?",
        "answer": "Turn on Developer Mode."
      },
      {
        "question": "Describe the GUI method to enable the Windows Subsystem for Linux.",
        "answer": "Go to Control Panel > Programs and Features > Turn Windows features on or off, check the box for Windows Subsystem on Linux (this will require local administrator privileges)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used in PowerShell to enable the Windows Subsystem for Linux?",
        "answer": "Enable-WindowsOptionalFeature -Online -FeatureName Microsoft-Windows-Subsystem-Linux."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens after the user accepts the license during the installation of Bash?",
        "answer": "The Ubuntu user mode image will be installed."
      },
      {
        "question": "What prompt appears the first time Bash is installed on Windows?",
        "answer": "A prompt will appear to create a Unix user."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does the Unix user account created during Bash installation relate to the Windows user account?",
        "answer": "The Unix user account is completely separate from the Windows user account."
      },
      {
        "question": "What permissions does the Unix user account have on WSL?",
        "answer": "The Unix user account has sudo permissions."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is the Linux installation located on Windows?",
        "answer": "%localappdata%\\lxss\\."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should not be done with the files in the Linux installation directory?",
        "answer": "Do not use Windows tools to edit the files or sub-files within this directory as corruption of the Linux files could occur."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can Windows storage and files be accessed from within WSL?",
        "answer": "Windows storage and files can be accessed from /mnt/..., such as /mnt/c/Users/myAccount."
      }
    ],
    "total": 15
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/FTP/Windows/Explorer",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "How can users open Windows Explorer on their desktop?",
        "answer": "Users can open Windows Explorer by clicking the folder icon on the taskbar on the bottom of their desktop."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the address to access a user's public FTP folder using Windows Explorer?",
        "answer": "\\\\umiacs-webftp\\ftp-umiacs\\pub\\<username>"
      },
      {
        "question": "What can external collaborators do with the files in a user's public folder?",
        "answer": "External collaborators can only download files published by the owner."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should be taken to access a user's public folder through a web browser?",
        "answer": "Open a web browser and type in the address: ftp://ftp.umiacs.umd.edu/pub/<username>/ to access users' public folders."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action must collaborators take to download a published file from a public folder?",
        "answer": "Collaborators can click on the file title to download a published file."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can the owner of a public folder manage its contents?",
        "answer": "The owner of the public folder can publish and modify files from a supported Windows machine."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the alternative method for opening Windows Explorer in Windows 10?",
        "answer": "In Windows 10, users can alternatively click on the Start menu and type in 'File Explorer' in the search box."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/OpenCVVersions",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to install OpenCV according to the instructions?",
        "answer": "Download the desired version of OpenCV from here (https://opencv.org/releases/)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do after double clicking the downloaded OpenCV executable?",
        "answer": "Select run at the prompt."
      },
      {
        "question": "What folder path should be referred to as {OPENCV}?",
        "answer": "The path to the folder you extracted."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you find the option to edit environment variables on a Windows system?",
        "answer": "Control Panel -> System and Security -> System"
      },
      {
        "question": "If a Variable called Path exists in the list of user variables, what should you do next?",
        "answer": "Click edit to edit the variable, and add a semicolon, then the following to the end of the Path value {OPENCV}\\build\\x64\\vc10\\bin."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you add to Additional Include Directories in Visual Studio Project Properties?",
        "answer": "'{OPENCV}\\build\\include;'"
      },
      {
        "question": "How should you set up the Library Directories in Visual Studio?",
        "answer": "Add '{OPENCV}\\build\\x64\\vc10\\lib;{OPENCV}\\build\\x64\\vc10\\staticlib;'"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the document provide for using OpenCV with Visual Studio?",
        "answer": "A link to the relevant tutorial at http://docs.opencv.org/doc/tutorials/introduction/windows_install/windows_install.html#windows-installation"
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional resource does the document suggest for using OpenCV with CUDA?",
        "answer": "A link to http://blog.cuvilib.com/2011/03/22/how-to-build-opencv-2-2-with-gpu-cuda-on-windows-7/"
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/S3Clients",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the required server address for accessing the UMIACS Object Store using graphical clients?",
        "answer": "obj.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which features are not supported by the S3 desktop clients in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Permissions"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the website link for downloading Cyberduck?",
        "answer": "https://cyberduck.io/"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of application is WinSCP and what specific drop-down menu choice is used to access the UMIACS Object Store?",
        "answer": "WinSCP is a free Windows file transfer application; it uses the 'Amazon S3' drop down menu choice under File protocol."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary function of the s3cmd tool mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "Accessing S3-like services via command line."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command line client can be added via a software module on supported UMIACS systems?",
        "answer": "MinIO Client (mc)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What information is saved in the ~/.s3cfg file for using the s3cmd client?",
        "answer": "ACCESS_KEY and SECRET_KEY"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is a unique feature of the Transmit application in handling Obj buckets?",
        "answer": "It allows you to mount your Obj buckets as local disks for easy drag-and-drop of files."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the URL to the full documentation for the MinIO Client?",
        "answer": "https://min.io/docs/minio/linux/reference/minio-mc.html"
      },
      {
        "question": "In using mc, which command would you use to list the contents of a bucket?",
        "answer": "$ mc ls obj/iso"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ServiceDeskMigration",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What system is UMIACS upgrading to based on Jira Software?",
        "answer": "UMIACS is upgrading to a new system based on Jira Service Desk."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the upgrade to Jira Service Desk?",
        "answer": "The upgrade will allow UMIACS to standardize on a more stable platform for future important bug and security patches."
      },
      {
        "question": "Will email requests to staff@umiacs.umd.edu continue to be received normally?",
        "answer": "Yes, email to staff@umiacs.umd.edu will continue to be received by staff as normal."
      },
      {
        "question": "How will the JIRA login information change for internal users?",
        "answer": "For internal users, the JIRA login will now be their UMIACS username instead of their email address."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will happen to external requests that come from email addresses not ending in @umiacs.umd.edu?",
        "answer": "External requests will no longer have accounts in Jira but can still communicate with Staff via email."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where should all order updates be sent or received after the migration?",
        "answer": "All order updates will now be sent/received through orders@umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "How should new orders be initiated after the migration?",
        "answer": "New orders should be started by emailing orders@umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "Can UMIACS Staff convert orders sent to staff@umiacs.umd.edu after the migration?",
        "answer": "Yes, UMIACS Staff is happy to convert orders sent to staff@umiacs.umd.edu as usual."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/UMobj",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of access does the UMobj suite of utilities provide?",
        "answer": "Command-line access to the UMIACS Object Store."
      },
      {
        "question": "On which type of machines is UMobj preinstalled?",
        "answer": "All UMIACS-supported RHEL8 machines."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is recommended when using UMobj for convenience?",
        "answer": "Setting a few environmental variables containing your credentials."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do to find your credentials for the Object Store?",
        "answer": "Log into the Object Store web interface and find them on the user page."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command would you use in the bash shell to set the OBJ_SERVER variable?",
        "answer": "export OBJ_SERVER=\"obj.umiacs.umd.edu\"."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is another option recommended for users not on UMIACS-supported hosts instead of UMobj?",
        "answer": "Using one of the many third-party command line clients that exist."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the recommended use case for UMobj regarding file size?",
        "answer": "Uploading large files (files greater than 4GB in size)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you find complete usage information for UMobj?",
        "answer": "On the GitLab page for umobj."
      },
      {
        "question": "What environmental variable would you set for your access key in tcsh?",
        "answer": "setenv OBJ_ACCESS_KEY_ID \"<ACCESS_KEY>\"."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the format of the URL where the Object Store user credentials can be found?",
        "answer": "https://obj.umiacs.umd.edu/obj/user/."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/WindowsDisplayModes",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to start changing display modes on a Windows system according to the provided text?",
        "answer": "Open Settings through your start menu by searching for it or clicking the gear icon."
      },
      {
        "question": "After opening Settings, which option should be clicked to adjust display settings?",
        "answer": "Click System."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default mode in which displays are used as mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "Extended mode."
      },
      {
        "question": "What option should be selected to switch to mirror mode?",
        "answer": "Select the Duplicate these displays option."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens when the 'Show only on 1' option is selected?",
        "answer": "It will only use the screen that you normally use for your computer, leaving the TV blank."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will occur if the 'Show only on 2' option is chosen?",
        "answer": "It will only use the TV as the screen, leaving the screen that you normally use blank."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Email/Barracuda",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary function of the Barracuda spam firewalls?",
        "answer": "The Barracuda spam firewalls manage all inbound and outbound email traffic to provide additional virus and spam filtering capabilities."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can users manage in their spam quarantine as a common task?",
        "answer": "Users can manage their spam quarantine."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of lists can users manage with Barracuda?",
        "answer": "Users can manage their Allow list and Block lists."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which filtering mechanism is mentioned as part of the common tasks for Barracuda?",
        "answer": "Bayesian filtering."
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Mathematica",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command do you use to add the default version of Mathematica to your Environment on UMIACS-supported Linux hosts?",
        "answer": "module add mathematica"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user see the versions of Mathematica available on UMIACS-supported Linux hosts?",
        "answer": "Use the command module avail mathematica."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the command to add a specific version of Mathematica, such as version 12.0, to a user's Environment?",
        "answer": "module add mathematica/12.0"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do to activate Mathematica on a computer that is not automated across the UMIACS domain?",
        "answer": "The computer has to be registered once against the hosted license server."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps must a user follow to activate Mathematica after being prompted?",
        "answer": "Click 'Other ways to activate', then click 'Connect to a network license server', enter 'licserv.umiacs.umd.edu' as the license server, click 'Activate', accept the terms, and click ok."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will happen to the Mathematica activation on a computer if the computer is reinstalled?",
        "answer": "The activation will not persist indefinitely if the computer is reinstalled."
      },
      {
        "question": "For UMIACS-supported Windows machines or other self-supported University-owned equipment, whom should users contact for access to Mathematica?",
        "answer": "Users should contact staff."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/CoreServices",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What user accounts are mentioned for authentication within UMIACS?",
        "answer": "UMIACS accounts and collaborator accounts."
      },
      {
        "question": "What resource is provided for backup personal devices at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Google Drive."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which resource provides a guide for printing across different operating systems at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Printing guide."
      },
      {
        "question": "What service does UMIACS offer related to web hosting?",
        "answer": "Hosting a personal website."
      },
      {
        "question": "Name one type of storage option available at UMIACS.",
        "answer": "Local scratch."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the SLURM resource scheduler at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "To manage high performance computing clusters."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the UMIACS Object Store utilize for user access?",
        "answer": "Buckets and keys."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which system is used for managing version control at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "GitLab."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is described as a method of securely destroying data?",
        "answer": "Make a request to securely destroy data."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the VPN service provided by UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Pulse Secure VPN."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/NFShomes",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "How much home directory storage space is available to each user?",
        "answer": "30GB"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of home directories in the context of UMIACS NFShomes?",
        "answer": "Home directories are intended to store personal or configuration files only."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is discouraged regarding data sharing in home directories?",
        "answer": "It is encouraged not to share any data in your home directory."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which infrastructure is recommended for hosting code repositories?",
        "answer": "GitLab infrastructure"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should be used to check the quota on the NFShomes directory?",
        "answer": "df -h ~"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should not be done with the nfshomes directory due to security reasons?",
        "answer": "You should never chmod your nfshomes directory to be world-writable."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the CIFS path format to access the NFShomes file system from Windows?",
        "answer": "\\\\isilondata.umiacs.umd.edu\\nfshomes\\<username>"
      },
      {
        "question": "From where is CIFS access limited?",
        "answer": "CIFS access is limited to machines in the domain."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be used to access NFShomes from outside the UMIACS networks?",
        "answer": "VPN"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of files are stored in the nfshomes directory that necessitate security precautions?",
        "answer": "SSH keys and other authentication related files"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MailingLists",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the two types of mailing lists mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "The two types of mailing lists are simple mailing lists in LDAP (also known as mailaliases) and Mailman mailing lists."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should one do if they would like to have a mailing list created?",
        "answer": "One should contact the HelpDesk if they would like either of these types of mailing lists created."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary function of mailaliases?",
        "answer": "Mailaliases are simple email redirects that allow for <listnamehere>@umiacs.umd.edu to be forwarded to a set list of email addresses."
      },
      {
        "question": "In what situation are mailaliases ideal?",
        "answer": "Mailaliases are ideal for situations where there is a set number of addresses in mind (i.e. no membership changes) and there is no need for moderation on the list."
      },
      {
        "question": "What features do Mailman mailing lists have?",
        "answer": "Mailman mailing lists have a robust set of administrative tools."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/PrintingDoubleSidedUSB",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of file must be saved to the flash drive in order to print from a USB?",
        "answer": "The desired file must be a PDF."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which side of the printer should the flash drive be inserted into?",
        "answer": "The flash drive should be inserted into the USB port on the left side of the printer."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first action to take after inserting the flash drive into the printer?",
        "answer": "Select 'Print'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What option should be selected after choosing to print from a USB drive?",
        "answer": "Choose your USB drive."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user navigate to the file they want to print from their flash drive?",
        "answer": "The user can see a list of the files on their flash drive and can click to select the desired file."
      },
      {
        "question": "What option must be selected to print double-sided pages during the printing process?",
        "answer": "In the 'Output Sides' option, select '2-sided'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if the '2-sided' option is not visible while printing?",
        "answer": "The default settings should already be set to double-sided."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the final step to complete the printing process after configuring settings?",
        "answer": "Click 'Print' on the right side of the screen."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ContentManagement",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What system does UMIACS support for faculty members?",
        "answer": "UMIACS supports a web content management system that allows faculty members to add modify their user profile on the UMIACS website."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can faculty members log into the content management system?",
        "answer": "Faculty members can log into the content management system at https://www.umiacs.umd.edu/user."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user begin editing their profile after logging in?",
        "answer": "A user can begin editing their profile by clicking the 'Edit' tab."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do to modify the information displayed for their profile?",
        "answer": "To modify the information displayed for their profile, a user should click the 'UMIACS staff' link at the top-right of the page."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of information can be edited in a profile?",
        "answer": "A user may edit their name, Academic Title, Research Focus, Education field, biography, home page location, mailing address, telephone, or fax."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be noted about changes made without clicking 'UMIACS Staff'?",
        "answer": "Changes made to the default profile, without clicking 'UMIACS Staff', will not be properly displayed on the site."
      },
      {
        "question": "Why might changes not be visible immediately after they are made?",
        "answer": "Changes may not be visible for up to five minutes due to the use of caching to increase performance and reliability."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can users add bibliography entries after logging in?",
        "answer": "Users can add bibliography entries by clicking on 'Biblio/Publication' at the right edge of the screen."
      },
      {
        "question": "What options do users have when entering a bibliography item?",
        "answer": "Users may enter a bibliography item with a Digital Object Identifier (DOI), a Bibtex record, a RIS record, or manually by selecting a 'Publication Type' from the drop down box."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be noted about changes made to bibliography entries?",
        "answer": "Changes made to bibliography entries may not be visible for up to five minutes due to the use of caching to increase performance and reliability."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/Compute",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are Computational Resources described as within UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Computational Resources are physical and virtual machines within UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two categories of compute resources listed in the Current Offerings section?",
        "answer": "High Performance Computing (HPC) Lab and User-Supported Compute Resources."
      },
      {
        "question": "What service is included under the virtualization category?",
        "answer": "Virtualization."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Snapshots",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of snapshots in a file system?",
        "answer": "Snapshots allow for a file system to quickly take a point-in-time copy of the file system and provide access to the data through a .snapshot directory."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do snapshots help in data recovery compared to tape backups?",
        "answer": "Snapshots provide a fast, user-accessible way to recover data that has been accidentally deleted or corrupted within a recent time window, rather than having to retrieve the data from comparatively slow tape backups."
      },
      {
        "question": "On which filers are snapshots provided according to the text?",
        "answer": "Snapshots are provided on Isilon, ZFS, VAST, and Qumulo filers."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the retention length for hourly snapshots in the core file systems?",
        "answer": "Hourly snapshots have a retention length of 24-32 hours."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the schedule for daily snapshots based on the provided retention policy?",
        "answer": "Daily snapshots are taken every day at 8pm or 12am and are retained for 2 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which directory names are used for accessing snapshots in Isilon, VAST, and Qumulo filers?",
        "answer": "The directory name used for accessing snapshots in Isilon, VAST, and Qumulo filers is .snapshot."
      },
      {
        "question": "What might occur to hourly snapshots when daily snapshots are taken?",
        "answer": "Hourly snapshots may be superseded by daily snapshots."
      },
      {
        "question": "If a user needs to recover a deleted file, how can they access the snapshots directory?",
        "answer": "The snapshots directory can be accessed by navigating to .snapshot for the Isilon, VAST, or Qumulo filers, or zfs/snapshot for the ZFS filer."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to list the contents of the snapshots directory for the Isilon filesystem?",
        "answer": "The command used is 'ls'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the structure of the ZFS snapshots' directory include according to the example given?",
        "answer": "The ZFS snapshots' directory includes entries like zfs-auto-snap_daily and zfs-auto-snap_hourly, each followed by a date and time."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Orders",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What must you do if the KFS account you plan on charging is owned by the Computer Science Department?",
        "answer": "Consult their FAQ for ordering the equipment you want."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should ticket descriptions contain when making an order?",
        "answer": "A list of specific items being ordered, preferably with direct links, unless you're attaching an official quote."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the connectivity requirements to access the web form for placing an order?",
        "answer": "You need to be connected to either the wired campus network, campus WiFi, the campus VPN, or the UMIACS VPN."
      },
      {
        "question": "When sending an email to staff directly for an order, what must be included if the account requires committee approval?",
        "answer": "You must CC the PI or include the email confirmation for any accounts that require committee approval."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the suggested format for the summary field when logging an order in Jira?",
        "answer": "The format should be 'Vendor | Brief Description'. If the order must be placed today, it should be 'PRIORITY TODAY | Vendor | Brief Description'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What information should be provided in the description field for an order through Jira?",
        "answer": "A description of what you want to buy, providing a link to the item when possible, and stating the specific vendor that is providing the item when purchasing through sites like Amazon."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens after staff receives the order as long as the PI is CC'd and all needed information is present?",
        "answer": "The order will be processed, and you will receive an email to pick up the order(s) when it arrives."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if someone other than yourself or the PI is sent to pick up the items?",
        "answer": "You should let the staff know who that person is prior to having them arrive for pickup."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be included in an order if quotes are used to specify items?",
        "answer": "Quotes must include any applicable shipping costs."
      },
      {
        "question": "When ordering from numerous vendors, what is the protocol for sending emails?",
        "answer": "Send one email per vendor."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Network/VPN/macOS",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the minimum macOS version required to use the Ivanti Connect Secure Client?",
        "answer": "macOS 13.x or higher"
      },
      {
        "question": "What must a device be enrolled with for multi-factor authentication in the UMIACS VPN setup?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Duo"
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens when the Ivanti Connect Secure Client is started for the first time?",
        "answer": "It may ask to upgrade the client."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be entered in the 'Server URL' field when creating a new VPN connection?",
        "answer": "vpn.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "What action should be taken in the secondary password box if a user wants to push a notification for MFA?",
        "answer": "Type the word 'push'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must a user do if they wish to register a YubiKey for use with the VPN?",
        "answer": "Contact UMIACS Tech Staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does a green arrow in the status icon indicate?",
        "answer": "You are connected."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can the Pulse Secure application be found if the status icon is not in the status bar?",
        "answer": "In the Applications folder."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which menu must a user navigate through to allow the extension from 'Pulse Secure LLC' if it was blocked?",
        "answer": "System Settings > Privacy & Security."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do after clicking 'Next' to a message about blocked software from 'Pulse Secure LLC'?",
        "answer": "Click 'Allow' to enable the extension."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Rclone",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary function of Rclone?",
        "answer": "Rclone is a command line program useful for syncing files and directories."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does Rclone's functionality compare to rsync?",
        "answer": "Its functionality is similar to rsync, but has additional capabilities that support cloud storage services."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is needed to load the Rclone module on a UMIACS host?",
        "answer": "The command is 'module load rclone'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should be run to find the location of the Rclone configuration file?",
        "answer": "The command is 'rclone config file'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What output can you expect when you run the command 'rclone config file'?",
        "answer": "$ rclone config file\nConfiguration file is stored at:/home/user/.rclone.conf"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command do you execute to authorize Rclone on a headless machine?",
        "answer": "Run the command 'rclone authorize \"amazon cloud drive\"'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if your browser does not open automatically during the Rclone authorization process?",
        "answer": "Go to the link: http://127.0.0.1:53682/auth."
      },
      {
        "question": "What token do you need to paste into the remote machine when setting up authorization?",
        "answer": "The token is labeled 'SECRET_TOKEN'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command do you use to create a new remote in Rclone?",
        "answer": "Run the command 'rclone config'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What storage type should you input when creating a remote for Google Drive in Rclone?",
        "answer": "Input 'drive' for Google Drive."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which scope is suggested for full operation when requesting access from Google Drive?",
        "answer": "The suggested value for full operation is 1."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command allows you to list directories in the top level of your Google Drive using Rclone?",
        "answer": "The command is 'rclone lsd <REMOTENAME>:'."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you create a cronjob for an Rclone command?",
        "answer": "Use the command 'crontab -e' to edit your crontab and input your Rclone command."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the example of an Rclone cronjob that would occur every hour on the hour?",
        "answer": "0 * * * * /opt/common/rclone-v1.53.4-linux-amd64/rclone copy /<PATHTOBEBACKEDUP>/ <REMOTENAME>:<BACKUPNAME>"
      },
      {
        "question": "When setting up a new Dropbox remote in Rclone, what should you do when prompted for your Dropbox App Key and Secret?",
        "answer": "It is okay to leave those blank."
      }
    ],
    "total": 15
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/Mailroom",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the room number where the mailroom is located?",
        "answer": "Room 5109."
      },
      {
        "question": "How are UMIACS staff notified when packages are ready for pickup?",
        "answer": "UMIACS staff is automatically notified by the mailroom."
      },
      {
        "question": "To which location will the mailroom bring items for processing?",
        "answer": "The UMIACS HelpDesk."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will happen after the UMIACS HelpDesk processes the items?",
        "answer": "They will contact you when items are ready for pickup."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the full address to which items can be ordered?",
        "answer": "5109 Brendan Iribe Center for Computer Science and Engineering, 8125 Paint Branch Drive, College Park, MD 20742."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the mailroom do after items are shipped to the specified address?",
        "answer": "The mailroom will then contact you when items are ready for pickup."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/Collaboration",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of tools are defined as collaboration tools in the provided text?",
        "answer": "Collaboration tools are designed to improve the ease of sharing and modifying data with a group of people."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is GitLab according to the information provided?",
        "answer": "GitLab is a web-based git repository manager with wiki and issue tracking features."
      },
      {
        "question": "What storage solution is mentioned in the Current Offerings section?",
        "answer": "Object Storage is the mentioned storage solution."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Tmux",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is tmux and what is its primary function?",
        "answer": "tmux is a terminal multiplexer for Unix-like operating systems that allows multiple terminal sessions to be accessed simultaneously in a single window."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user create a new tmux session with a specific name?",
        "answer": "A user can create a new tmux session with a specific name by using the command '# tmux new -s mysession'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to detach a tmux session from the terminal?",
        "answer": "To detach a tmux session from the terminal, the command used is '# Ctrl-b + d'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will the output of the command '# tmux ls' look like if multiple sessions are running?",
        "answer": "The output will be similar to this: '# mysession: 1 windows (created Thu Oct 22 10:11:44 2020) # session2: 1 windows (created Thu Oct 22 10:11:52 2020) # session3: 1 windows (created Thu Oct 22 10:11:58 2020)'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the command to rename the current window in tmux?",
        "answer": "The command to rename the current window in tmux is '# Ctrl-b ,'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What keystroke is used to enter Copy Mode in tmux?",
        "answer": "To enter Copy Mode in tmux, the keystroke used is '# Ctrl-b ['."
      },
      {
        "question": "What commands do you use to navigate to the top and bottom of a page while in Copy Mode?",
        "answer": "To navigate to the top of the page, type '# g', and to go to the bottom of the page, type '# G'."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user change the prefix keystroke from Ctrl-b to Ctrl-a?",
        "answer": "A user can change the prefix keystroke from Ctrl-b to Ctrl-a by adding the following to their ~/.tmux.conf: '# remap prefix from 'C-b' to 'C-a' unbind C-b set-option -g prefix C-a bind-key C-a send-prefix'."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Publishing_Data",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the recommended account type for publishing data at UMIACS to ensure permanence?",
        "answer": "Any/all data should be published via a faculty member's account or a Labgroup, not a student's."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be done to any papers that contain UMIACS URLs?",
        "answer": "UMIACS should be credited on any papers that contain UMIACS URLs."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are LabGroups at UMIACS used for?",
        "answer": "LabGroups allow for multiple users to upload data to a central shared location, which is especially useful for projects with multiple contributors."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the preferred method for publishing websites and data at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The preferred method for publishing websites, data, and related info is through the UMIACS Object Storage (OBJ)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is a 'bucket' in the context of OBJ?",
        "answer": "A 'bucket' is essentially a folder that stores files in the UMIACS Object Storage."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must you do to make a file publicly available in OBJ?",
        "answer": "Click the settings cog on the right side of the file, scroll down, and click 'Make Key Public'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What two main files does UMIACS recommend including when publishing websites?",
        "answer": "UMIACS recommends including an index.html file and a 404 error file when publishing websites."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must you configure in the bucket settings to publish a website?",
        "answer": "Under the 'Website Hosting' section, you need to put the name of your index file and the name of your 404 page."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is advised to do with sensitive data when using buckets to publish websites?",
        "answer": "It is recommended to keep any sensitive/access controlled data in a separate bucket."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should be taken to make a website non-public after it has been published?",
        "answer": "Click 'Remove Website Configuration' and then 'Make Private'."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/RHEL7",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What kernel version is RHEL7 based on?",
        "answer": "RHEL7 is based on the Linux 3.10.0-957 kernel."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default file system used in RHEL7?",
        "answer": "The default file system in RHEL7 is XFS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum filesystem size supported by XFS in RHEL7?",
        "answer": "XFS supports filesystem sizes of up to 500 TB in RHEL7."
      },
      {
        "question": "What module does RHEL7 include to enhance its security architecture?",
        "answer": "RHEL7 includes Security-Enhanced Linux (SELinux) as a module to enhance its security architecture."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum standalone filesystem size for ext4 filesystems in RHEL7?",
        "answer": "The maximum standalone filesystem size for ext4 filesystems in RHEL7 is 50 TB."
      },
      {
        "question": "What process management system has replaced the initial process in RHEL7?",
        "answer": "The initial process in RHEL7 has been changed to systemd."
      },
      {
        "question": "What virtualization technology is built into RHEL7 for running virtual machines?",
        "answer": "RHEL7 includes the built-in Kernel-based Virtual Machine (KVM) for running virtual machines."
      },
      {
        "question": "What file system is categorized as an 'unsupported Technology Preview' in RHEL7?",
        "answer": "Btrfs is categorized as an 'unsupported Technology Preview' in RHEL7."
      },
      {
        "question": "What mechanism does XFS use to minimize data loss during a system crash?",
        "answer": "XFS supports journaling to minimize data loss in the event of a system crash."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the role of SELinux in RHEL7?",
        "answer": "SELinux implements a mandatory access control model in RHEL7."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Java",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the two main flavors of Java supported according to the document?",
        "answer": "Oracle Java and OpenJDK."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is usually sufficient for running programs and applets written in Java if one does not do programming in Java?",
        "answer": "Java Runtime Environment (JRE)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be run on any RHEL/Ubuntu machine to check the version of Java?",
        "answer": "bash-4.2$ java -version."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can alternative JDK and JRE options be found on the machine?",
        "answer": "/usr/lib/jvm."
      },
      {
        "question": "Is JRE included in JDK, and is there a need to install both?",
        "answer": "Yes, JRE is included in JDK, so there is no need to install both."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to JRE on all supported workstations?",
        "answer": "It is installed by default and auto-updated to the latest version periodically."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if your machine does not have Java installed?",
        "answer": "Send a request to staff to have JRE or JDK installed on your machine."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Windows/LaptopSupport",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the base hardware requirements for university-owned laptops to qualify for UMIACS support?",
        "answer": "Business or professional model line from a tier one manufacturer (e.g. Dell, HP, Microsoft), 3+ years OEM warranty/support (i.e. no refurbished equipment or third-party vendor warranties), readily available manufacturer diagnostic tools, and readily available hardware drivers."
      },
      {
        "question": "Under which conditions can UMIACS hardware support be given to dual-boot laptops?",
        "answer": "Dual-boot laptops are only eligible for UMIACS Hardware Support. If you later set up or attempt to set up dual-boot on a system that UMIACS staff previously configured with either Enterprise or Base level support, UMIACS cannot offer help if you run into issues with the dual-booting process or either operating system thereafter."
      },
      {
        "question": "What kind of support does UMIACS Enterprise Laptop Support offer?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Enterprise laptop support provides a secure computing platform with automated backups and security updates, installation of an Enterprise version of Microsoft Windows, F-Secure Client Security, Ivanti Security Scan, Microsoft Office, and MATLAB, along with encryption of the hard drive using BitLocker."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary responsibility of the user under UMIACS Base Laptop Support?",
        "answer": "The user is responsible for the maintenance and upkeep of the Operating System and any data stored on the laptop."
      },
      {
        "question": "What services are provided under UMIACS Hardware Support?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Hardware support provides basic hardware diagnostics and warranty repairs, while allowing you to have full control over the software and data stored on your laptop."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to the device data when it is returned to UMIACS under both Enterprise and Base support?",
        "answer": "Data archival upon return of the device to UMIACS is provided."
      },
      {
        "question": "If a user does not have access to Terpware for downloadable software, what should they do?",
        "answer": "They should contact the HelpDesk."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which software suites are installed under UMIACS Base Laptop Support?",
        "answer": "The software suites include F-Secure Client Security, Microsoft Office, and MATLAB."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/ConferenceRooms/List",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the occupancy of the conference room IRB-1127?",
        "answer": "12"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which conference rooms have an AutoAccept type classification?",
        "answer": "IRB-1119, IRB-2119, IRB-2143, IRB-4119, IRB-5107, IRB-5111, IRB-5119, IRB-5161"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many total rooms listed are categorized as Moderated?",
        "answer": "8"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the occupancy of the largest Moderated conference room mentioned?",
        "answer": "48"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which conference room has the smallest occupancy capacity?",
        "answer": "6, with rooms IRB-1119, IRB-2119, IRB-2143, IRB-4119, IRB-5111, IRB-5119, and IRB-5161 all having this occupancy."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the occupancy of IRB-3137?",
        "answer": "24"
      },
      {
        "question": "List all conference rooms with an occupancy of 20.",
        "answer": "IRB-4107, IRB-4109"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the total number of conference rooms listed?",
        "answer": "16"
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Network/VPN/Troubleshooting",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if they experience an authentication failure after changing their password in the Ivanti Secure Access client?",
        "answer": "The user should open the Ivanti Secure Access client, right-click on the desired connection, and click on Forget Saved Settings. Afterwards, they need to re-enter their new credentials and reconnect."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should a macOS user follow to fix an authentication failure in the Ivanti Secure Access client?",
        "answer": "The macOS user should open the Ivanti Secure Access client, click on the 3 lines on the top left corner (if using the New-UX client), select Forget Settings, and then re-enter their new credentials and reconnect."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the suggested action if a user encounters an upgrade failure with the VPN client?",
        "answer": "The user should delete and reinstall the VPN client if the upgrade process is stuck."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do if they receive the error code 1300 when connecting from the Ivanti Secure Access client?",
        "answer": "Users should Forget Saved Settings and retry, or remove and re-add the VPN connection on the client."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who should users contact if they continue to experience issues following a VPN client auto upgrade?",
        "answer": "Users should contact staff@umiacs.umd.edu if they continue to have issues."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/NightlyBackups",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of the backups conducted by UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The primary purpose of the backups conducted by UMIACS is to provide accidental deletion coverage."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many days of coverage does UMIACS aim to provide through its nightly backups?",
        "answer": "UMIACS aims to provide 90 days of coverage through its nightly backups."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the frequency of the backups conducted by UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The frequency of the backups conducted by UMIACS is one backup per night."
      },
      {
        "question": "Why might the backup coverage not be perfect?",
        "answer": "The backup coverage may not be perfect because the backups are very coarse, and depending on the size of the change and size of the file, backups may be periodically missed."
      },
      {
        "question": "What challenges are mentioned regarding files that change often in relation to nightly backups?",
        "answer": "Files that change often may not have all versions backed up to 90 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is indicated about files that are created very recently in relation to nightly backups?",
        "answer": "Files that were created very recently may not be backed up."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action should a person take if they need something from the nightly backups?",
        "answer": "A person should contact staff with the full path to the directory(s) which they would like to have restored."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ConferenceRooms",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "In which location does UMIACS maintain conference rooms?",
        "answer": "UMIACS maintains conference rooms in the Brendan Iribe Center and a few in the Atlantic building."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the names of the two different conference room locations mentioned?",
        "answer": "The two different conference room locations mentioned are the Brendan Iribe Center and the Atlantic building."
      }
    ],
    "total": 2
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ConferenceRooms/TouchPanel",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What happens when you touch the panel to start it up after the room was in a 'shut down' state?",
        "answer": "It will turn on the display(s) for the room and lower the projector screens if any are present."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the three common source options available on the touch panels?",
        "answer": "\"Solstice\", \"Laptop Device\" (just \"Laptop\" on some panels), and \"Room PC\" (the third option only in non-huddle rooms)."
      },
      {
        "question": "In moderated rooms, where can you find the volume control for the sources?",
        "answer": "The volume control is on the Device Control menu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What special option is available at the top of the source/destination menu in moderated rooms?",
        "answer": "\"Device Control\" option."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do when you are done using the room PC?",
        "answer": "Log off to ensure the account is fully wiped, so the next group does not have access to anything you may have signed into."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you connect a device to display it in the room using the Laptop Device option?",
        "answer": "Connect your device to either the HDMI cable or VGA/aux cables coming out of the middle of the desk in the room."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'Shutdown A/V System' button?",
        "answer": "To save energy and give the next group using the room a clean slate by turning off the display(s) and raising the projector screens if any are present."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which rooms have the capability to display an external device's screen wirelessly using Solstice?",
        "answer": "Auto-Accept Rooms and Huddle Rooms."
      },
      {
        "question": "What specific controls can be managed through the Device Control option in moderated rooms?",
        "answer": "Volume, and in some rooms, lighting, microphones, and settings for other integrated devices such as the room's Blu-ray player, TV tuner, or room cameras."
      },
      {
        "question": "What instructions will you see when you select the Solstice option on the touch panel?",
        "answer": "Instructions on how to display your device(s) to the room's display wirelessly."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/JavaDevelEnvironment",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the recommended choice of development environment for Java according to the text?",
        "answer": "The recommended choice of development environment for Java is the Sun ONE Development Studio."
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the former name of the Sun ONE Development Studio?",
        "answer": "The former name of the Sun ONE Development Studio is Forte for Java."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who created the Java programming language?",
        "answer": "Java was created by Sun."
      },
      {
        "question": "Is the Sun ONE Development Studio available for free?",
        "answer": "Yes, the Sun ONE Development Studio is freely available."
      },
      {
        "question": "On which operating systems can the Sun ONE Development Studio run?",
        "answer": "The Sun ONE Development Studio can run on any OS and platform for which JDK is available, including Unix, Linux, Windows, and Mac."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of software is the Sun ONE Development Studio written in?",
        "answer": "The Sun ONE Development Studio is written entirely in Java."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the feedback status regarding Borland's JBuilder as mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "The text states that there has been negative feedback on Borland's JBuilder from users in the past."
      },
      {
        "question": "Why is Microsoft's Visual J++ not recommended?",
        "answer": "Microsoft's Visual J++ is not recommended because it is not compatible with the new language specifications."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which versions of Microsoft's Visual J++ are mentioned in the text as being problematic?",
        "answer": "Version 6 and the .NET version of Microsoft's Visual J++ are mentioned."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Network/VPN/Mobile",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the prerequisites for using the VPN Client mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "A full UMIACS account, device enrolled with UMIACS Duo for multi-factor authentication, and an established network connection (mobile data or wireless)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which platforms can the Pulse Secure Client be downloaded from?",
        "answer": "The app can be downloaded for free from the App Store for iOS and Google Play for Android."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the initial step when launching the Pulse Secure Client?",
        "answer": "When the client is first launched, it will prompt you to accept its license agreement."
      },
      {
        "question": "What URL should be entered when prompted for a Corporate E-mail address or URL in the client configuration?",
        "answer": "vpn.umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What basic information is required when adding a connection in the Pulse Secure Client?",
        "answer": "Connection Name: UMIACS VPN and Username: <your UMIACS username>."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'Connect' button in the Pulse Secure Client?",
        "answer": "The 'Connect' button is used to start the VPN Connection after the client has been configured."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user verify their connection status after connecting to the VPN?",
        "answer": "The connection status is verified by the VPN symbol in the top status bar."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must a user do to stop the VPN tunnel once connected?",
        "answer": "To stop the VPN tunnel, the user must click 'Disconnect'."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/EmailMigration/SelfMigration",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What email services did UMIACS wind down as of June 30th, 2020?",
        "answer": "UMIACS wound down its Exchange and IMAP mailbox email services."
      },
      {
        "question": "What email subject line was sent to users covered by the migration on May 1st, 2020?",
        "answer": "The email subject line sent was 'UMIACS Email Migration'."
      },
      {
        "question": "If a user did not receive the email sent on May 1st, 2020, what action were they directed to take?",
        "answer": "They were directed to update their email preference in the Directory app before June 2nd, 2020 at 9am."
      },
      {
        "question": "What would happen to a user's email forwarding if they did not update their preferences by June 2nd, 2020 at 9am?",
        "answer": "The UMIACS Technical Staff would update their email forward to be their corresponding @umd.edu email address or the last known email address on record."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can users update their email forwarding address if they do not have a @umd.edu address?",
        "answer": "Users can log into the Directory app, change the listed address under 'Email', and click Submit at the bottom of the page."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps must a user follow to import email from their previous provider into their UMD mailbox?",
        "answer": "Users must follow the steps detailed for importing email, since UMIACS staff have no administrative access to UMD mailboxes."
      },
      {
        "question": "What format will the archive of the UMIACS mailbox be provided in for Exchange users?",
        "answer": "The archive will be a single file in PST file format."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is necessary to import email from PST files into a UMD mailbox?",
        "answer": "Users must download and install G Suite Migration for Microsoft Outlook and follow DivIT's instructions."
      },
      {
        "question": "How will the archive for IMAP users be provided?",
        "answer": "The archive will consist of several files in MBOX format, compressed into a tarball."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the ImportExportTools NG add-on for Mozilla Thunderbird?",
        "answer": "The ImportExportTools NG add-on is used to import email from MBOX files into Mozilla Thunderbird."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do if they have issues during the email import process?",
        "answer": "Users should contact the Division of IT for assistance."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can users find instructions for forwarding email from their previous provider?",
        "answer": "Users should search for instructions from their previous provider."
      },
      {
        "question": "Can users import email in file formats other than PST or MBOX according to the text?",
        "answer": "No, the text specifies that users need to export email in either PST or MBOX format to follow the corresponding import steps."
      }
    ],
    "total": 13
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Remote_Desktop",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What protocol is used to connect to Windows hosts remotely at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must users ensure before attempting to use RDP to connect to a Windows host?",
        "answer": "Users must be on the UMIACS physical network or VPN and be authorized to access and remotely control the host."
      },
      {
        "question": "If a remote session is active, what will happen if another user attempts to log onto the console in-person?",
        "answer": "It is not possible for another user to log onto the console in-person."
      },
      {
        "question": "What format must the username be in when entering UMIACS credentials for RDP access?",
        "answer": "The username must be in the format UMIACS\\username, where username is replaced by the UMIACS username."
      },
      {
        "question": "What feature does Audio Redirection provide in the context of Remote Desktop?",
        "answer": "Audio Redirection allows the remote desktop to access the audio capture and playback devices on the user's desktop."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should be followed to redirect folders on a Mac when connecting to a remote desktop?",
        "answer": "Right click over the PC connection, select 'Edit', go to the 'Folders' tab, check 'Redirect folders', and add the desired folders."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which application is recommended for connecting to Windows clients over RDP on macOS?",
        "answer": "Microsoft Remote Desktop application."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should be used to access a Windows host via RDP on an Ubuntu machine using rdesktop?",
        "answer": "rdesktop -r clipboard:CLIPBOARD -g <GEOMETRY> -d UMIACS -u <USERNAME> <HOSTNAME>."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the xfreerdp command require in order for a user to connect to a remote host?",
        "answer": "xfreerdp -d UMIACS -u <USERNAME> --plugin cliprdr -g <GEOMETRY> <HOSTNAME>."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is indicated if a warning message appears about an identity verification failure when connecting to UMIACS machines?",
        "answer": "For UMIACS machines, you can ignore this warning and proceed by checking the box and selecting 'Yes'."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/Web",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of webspace is offered for individual users?",
        "answer": "Individual user webspace."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who should be contacted for more details regarding lab-specific webspace?",
        "answer": "Staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is mentioned as upcoming for MediaWiki?",
        "answer": "Documentation coming soon."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/UNIXPrinting",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command is used to submit a postscript file named 'filename.ps' to a printer queue named 'printername'?",
        "answer": "lpr -Pprintername filename.ps"
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if no printer name is specified when using the 'lpr' command?",
        "answer": "The job is discarded by the print server."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command is used to remove jobs from a specific printer queue?",
        "answer": "lprm -Pprintername"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you check the status of a printer queue named 'printername'?",
        "answer": "By using the command 'lpq -Pprintername'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional information does the '-l' argument provide when using the 'lpq' command?",
        "answer": "It specifies the id, queue rank, the total size of the job in bytes, and any errors encountered in processing the job."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'textps' command?",
        "answer": "It is used to generate postscript from an existing text file."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to view the contents of a postscript file before printing?",
        "answer": "ghostview file.ps"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to check all print queues available?",
        "answer": "lpq -a"
      },
      {
        "question": "If you want to remove a specific job with job id 198 from the queue, what command would you use?",
        "answer": "lprm -Pps432-3208 198"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command allows you to monitor the job sent to the printer?",
        "answer": "lpq -Pps432-3208"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/CMake",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is required for installing CMake as of version 3.4, even when selecting one's home directory?",
        "answer": "Administrative privilege is required to install CMake."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a non-admin user do if they want to install CMake on a UMIACS-supported system?",
        "answer": "They should send mail to staff to schedule a time where staff can provide admin credentials."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can the appropriate binary for CMake be retrieved from?",
        "answer": "The appropriate binary can be retrieved from https://www.cmake.org/download."
      },
      {
        "question": "What option does the installer provide regarding the PATH variable?",
        "answer": "The installer provides the option to automatically modify the PATH variable."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two options available for using CMake after installation?",
        "answer": "The two options are to use CMake from the command line if it has been added to your path, or to use the CMake GUI located in the bin directory within the install directory."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should be followed to configure the compiler using the CMake GUI?",
        "answer": "Click configure and choose the compiler which has been installed on the system, such as some version of Visual Studio."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can the right compiler be passed in when using CMake from the command line?",
        "answer": "The right compiler can be passed in using the -G option."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will typing 'cmake' without any options display?",
        "answer": "It will display basic help."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Windows_Patch_Management",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What software has UMIACS staff deployed to manage third-party security vulnerabilities on Windows machines?",
        "answer": "Ivanti Endpoint Manager."
      },
      {
        "question": "On what day of the month are patches always released according to the defined schedule?",
        "answer": "On the Wednesday that falls between the 9th and the 15th of every month."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if a user remains active on their system during the nightly update scan time?",
        "answer": "They will see a popup with the scan beginning and a prompt from Ivanti asking to begin installing patches once the patches are downloaded."
      },
      {
        "question": "How often do laptops scan for updates provided they are powered on?",
        "answer": "At least once every day."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the automatic installation time for patches on desktops if a user does not respond to the prompt?",
        "answer": "24 hours."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the maximum time a user can defer a reboot after installation finishes on a desktop?",
        "answer": "6 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "If a user interrupts the installation process, what may Ivanti request the next time the user installs patches?",
        "answer": "Ivanti may ask to reboot before continuing to install the remaining patches."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the consequence of trying to manually scan for patches while Ivanti is running an invisible scan?",
        "answer": "The scan may fail on the 'Checking for other running scanners' step."
      },
      {
        "question": "After installing all patches, what options does a user have if they do not want to reboot immediately?",
        "answer": "They can click on the 'Remind me in:' drop down menu, choose 'More options...', then select 'Remind me on' and choose a date and time before the deadline."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if a patch is continually failing after a reboot?",
        "answer": "Contact staff."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Snapshots:Example",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command is used to check the current working directory before removing the Python file?",
        "answer": "pwd"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the file size of virtualenv.py as shown after running ls -lah?",
        "answer": "98K"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to remove the virtualenv.py file?",
        "answer": "rm virtualenv.py"
      },
      {
        "question": "After removing virtualenv.py, what command is run to verify its removal?",
        "answer": "ls"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the most recent weekly snapshot the user changes directory into?",
        "answer": "Weekly_nfshomes_2024-06-23_00:00"
      },
      {
        "question": "In which directory is the Weekly_nfshomes_2024-06-23_00:00 snapshot located?",
        "answer": "/nfshomes/username/.snapshot"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to copy the virtualenv.py file back to the original directory?",
        "answer": "cp virtualenv.py /nfshomes/username/virtualenv/"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is executed to confirm that the virtualenv.py file has been successfully restored?",
        "answer": "ls"
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/OBJ",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is an object store, and what are its primary focuses?",
        "answer": "An object store is a web-based storage solution focused on reliability, scalability, and security."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are buckets and keys in the context of S3-like storage?",
        "answer": "Keys are analogous to files, and a bucket is simply a container for a set of keys."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does the UMIACS Object Store ensure data protection from machine failure?",
        "answer": "Data is protected from individual machine failure via replication within the cluster."
      },
      {
        "question": "What storage is allocated to UMIACS users and faculty?",
        "answer": "UMIACS users are allocated 50GB of storage, while faculty are allocated 10TB."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if a user deletes a key or bucket in the Object Store?",
        "answer": "If a user deletes a key or bucket in the Object Store, there is no way to restore that information."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of Access Control Lists (ACLs) in the UMIACS Object Store?",
        "answer": "ACLs allow users to specify who has what types of access to their buckets at both the bucket level and the individual key level."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can users access the UMIACS Object Store from their desktops?",
        "answer": "Users can access the UMIACS Object Store using the command line UMobj utilities, third-party graphical clients, or programmatically using popular programming languages."
      },
      {
        "question": "What role do LabGroup managers play in managing access to buckets?",
        "answer": "LabGroup managers can grant granular access (read, write, full control, manager) to buckets owned by the LabGroup."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do to maintain the confidentiality of their Secret Key?",
        "answer": "Users should treat their Secret Key(s) the same as a password and not plaintext it over email or share it with others."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the implications of bucket names in the UMIACS Object Store?",
        "answer": "Bucket names must be unique, and a notification will be issued if the name is already taken when creating a bucket."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/UMIACS:General_disclaimer",
    "Q/A": [],
    "total": 0
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Fixing_Stuck_Standing_Desk",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to take when the electric adjustable standing desk is stuck?",
        "answer": "Disconnect the table from outlet / power source."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which cable should be disconnected from the power box during the troubleshooting process?",
        "answer": "Disconnect the controller cable (blue end) from the power box."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where are the M1 and M2 connectors located?",
        "answer": "The M1 and M2 connectors are located underneath the desktop or to the desk frame."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the correct procedure for connecting the table leg cables to the M1 and M2 connectors?",
        "answer": "Connect the cable from the table leg on the same side as the up / down controls to the M1 connector first, then connect the cable from the second leg to the M2 connector."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be done after reconnecting the controller cable and powering the desk on?",
        "answer": "Press and hold the down button for 5 seconds."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be felt after holding the down button for 5 seconds?",
        "answer": "A very slight movement."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be done if the desk moves in the opposite direction of the button pressed?",
        "answer": "Repeat the steps listed above but switch which legs go to the M1 and M2 connectors."
      },
      {
        "question": "When switching legs to M1 and M2 connectors, which leg should be connected to the M1 connector first?",
        "answer": "The leg on the OPPOSITE side of the up/down controls."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is important to ensure when connecting cables to the M1 and M2 connectors?",
        "answer": "You must connect a cable to the M1 connector BEFORE connecting anything to the M2 connector."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/EuclidCluster",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What has happened to the Euclid cluster?",
        "answer": "The Euclid cluster has been deprecated."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who should be contacted if there are questions regarding the Euclid cluster?",
        "answer": "Staff should be contacted with any questions."
      }
    ],
    "total": 2
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ComputationalResource",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of Computational Resources (CRs) as described in the text?",
        "answer": "The primary purpose of Computational Resources (CRs) is to provide access control to login shells and GUIs for a set of computers."
      },
      {
        "question": "Can users customize their Shell using Computational Resources?",
        "answer": "Yes, a user can customize their Shell."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can staff provide to users depending on the resource?",
        "answer": "Staff can provide users different home directories depending on the resource."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Nexus/Tron",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the Tron partition a subset of?",
        "answer": "The Tron partition is a subset of resources available in the Nexus."
      },
      {
        "question": "How was the Tron partition funded?",
        "answer": "It was purchased using college-level funding for UMIACS and CSD faculty."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the total quantity of nodes in the full configuration of Tron?",
        "answer": "The total quantity of nodes in the full configuration of Tron is 70."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of GPU node has 6 units and 256 GB of memory per node?",
        "answer": "The A6000 GPU Node has 6 units and 256 GB of memory per node."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many CPU cores are present per A4000 GPU Node?",
        "answer": "There are 16 CPU cores per A4000 GPU Node."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the total amount of memory across all nodes listed for Tron?",
        "answer": "The total amount of memory across all nodes listed for Tron is 1,840 GB."
      },
      {
        "question": "How many GPUs are there per RTX 2080 Ti GPU Node?",
        "answer": "There are 4 GPUs per RTX 2080 Ti GPU Node."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the total number of GPUs in the full configuration of Tron?",
        "answer": "The total number of GPUs in the full configuration of Tron is 396."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which GPU Node type has the least amount of memory per node?",
        "answer": "The A4000 GPU Node has the least amount of memory per node, with 128 GB."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the specification of the total for all nodes grouped together?",
        "answer": "The total for all nodes grouped together consists of 69 nodes, 1,840 CPU cores, and 396 GPUs."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/BarracudaSpamFirewall/SearchingQuarantine",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What email address format should you use to log in to the spam quarantine system?",
        "answer": "username@umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two URLs provided for accessing the spam quarantine system?",
        "answer": "bubs.umiacs.umd.edu and pompom.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the three different filters available for searching emails in the quarantine?",
        "answer": "'from', 'subject', and 'message'"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the 'from' filter allow you to search for?",
        "answer": "It allows you to search the emails based on who sent them."
      },
      {
        "question": "If you select the 'subject' filter and choose 'contains' while searching for 'binary', what will you see?",
        "answer": "You will see emails with 'binary' in the subject."
      },
      {
        "question": "What outcome results from selecting the 'message' filter?",
        "answer": "It allows you to search in the body of the email."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does selecting 'doesn't contain' under the subject filter signify?",
        "answer": "It indicates that all emails that don't have 'binary' in the subject will be shown."
      }
    ],
    "total": 7
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/RHELDisplayModes",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "How do you start to change the display settings in RHEL?",
        "answer": "Open Settings by clicking on Applications -> System Tools -> Settings."
      },
      {
        "question": "After opening Settings, which section should be clicked to adjust display settings?",
        "answer": "Click Devices."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default display mode used in RHEL?",
        "answer": "The default display mode is extended mode, called Join Displays in RHEL."
      },
      {
        "question": "What option should be selected to switch to mirror mode in RHEL?",
        "answer": "Select the Mirror option."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will happen if the Single Display option is selected?",
        "answer": "Selecting the Single Display option will only show the display selected below."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/R",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to retrieve the latest version of R for Windows according to the installation instructions?",
        "answer": "Select 'Download R for Windows' from the top of the screen."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do after clicking 'Install R for the first time' on the download page?",
        "answer": "Click 'Download R<version number> for Windows' to begin the installation."
      },
      {
        "question": "What warning message is displayed when starting the installer for R?",
        "answer": "There will be a warning that says the full installation requires administrative privileges."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default folder name suggested for the start menu during the customized options setup?",
        "answer": "The default 'R' is acceptable for this."
      },
      {
        "question": "What options are provided for the interface selection during the customized startup environment setup?",
        "answer": "MDI (one main window for all R programs) or SDI (separate windows for each R program)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What formats can the help display be chosen from during the customized startup environment setup?",
        "answer": "Plain text format or HTML formatted."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can users open an R script with RScript?",
        "answer": "Users can run Rscript path\\to\\file\\test.R from within the \\bin\\x64 folder at the location that you installed R to."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action should be taken if a user is unsure about customizing the options for the startup environment?",
        "answer": "Select 'No' (can still be changed later)."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Backups",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What types of laptops are mentioned for backups in the text?",
        "answer": "Windows or macOS laptops"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the frequency of the backups mentioned for laptops?",
        "answer": "Nightly backups"
      },
      {
        "question": "Through which system are the nightly backups executed?",
        "answer": "TSM"
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/UbuntuPrinting",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What network must you be connected to in order to print from a personal Ubuntu laptop or desktop at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "You must be on the UMIACS internal network, either via a wired proxy drop or an SSH tunnel."
      },
      {
        "question": "What initial action must be taken within the system settings to begin the printer connection process?",
        "answer": "You must open your system settings and search for the 'Printers' dialog box."
      },
      {
        "question": "After opening the 'Printers' dialog box, what options must you select to start adding a new printer?",
        "answer": "Click 'Additional Settings' and 'Add' in the new box that pops up."
      },
      {
        "question": "What URL must you navigate to in order to find the name of the printer you wish to connect to?",
        "answer": "You need to navigate to http://print.umiacs.umd.edu/printers."
      },
      {
        "question": "How should you format the 'Device URI' for adding a printer?",
        "answer": "Enter ipp://print.umiacs.umd.edu:631/printers/ followed by the name of the printer."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is an example of a 'Device URI' for connecting to a printer named 'cps432-3208'?",
        "answer": "The Device URI would be ipp://print.umiacs.umd.edu:631/printers/cps432-3208."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do after entering the 'Device URI' and clicking 'Forward'?",
        "answer": "You will see a list of printer models, from which you should select the brand of the printer."
      },
      {
        "question": "What needs to be done after selecting the brand of the printer?",
        "answer": "Select the specific model of the printer and then click 'Forward'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional options can you select during the printer setup process?",
        "answer": "You can select any additional features available for the printer, such as duplexing or trays."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do to verify that the printer has been properly configured?",
        "answer": "Print a test page to verify the configuration."
      },
      {
        "question": "What result indicates that the printer is not properly configured?",
        "answer": "If you just get a page with a string of text instead of the default Ubuntu test page."
      }
    ],
    "total": 11
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Special:SpecialPages",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of reports can be found under the section labeled 'Maintenance reports'?",
        "answer": "Broken redirects, dead-end pages, double redirects, long pages, oldest pages, orphaned pages, pages with the fewest revisions, pages without language links, protected pages, protected titles, short pages, uncategorized categories, uncategorized files, uncategorized pages, uncategorized templates, unused categories, unused files, unused templates, wanted categories, wanted files, wanted pages, and wanted templates."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which sections contain lists of pages?",
        "answer": "The 'Lists of pages' section contains 'All pages', 'All pages with prefix', 'Categories', 'External links search', 'List of redirects', 'Pages with a page property', and 'Tracking categories'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can be found under the 'Users and rights' section?",
        "answer": "Active users list, autoblocks, blocked users, bot passwords, grants, link accounts, password policies, preferences, reset tokens, unlink accounts, user contributions, user group rights, user list, and user rights."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of changes are logged under the 'Recent changes and logs' section?",
        "answer": "Gallery of new files, logs, new pages, recent changes, related changes, and valid change tags."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which functionalities are included in the 'Media reports and uploads' section?",
        "answer": "File list, list of files with duplicates, MIME search, and media statistics."
      },
      {
        "question": "What special pages are involved in redirecting actions?",
        "answer": "Delete a page, differences, edit a page, new section, page history, page info, permanent link, protect a page, purge, random page, random page in category, random redirect, and redirect by file, user, page, revision, or log ID."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are considered 'High use pages' according to the text?",
        "answer": "Most linked-to categories, most linked-to files, most linked-to pages, most transcluded pages, pages with the most categories, pages with the most interwikis, and pages with the most revisions."
      },
      {
        "question": "What tools can be found in the 'Page tools' section?",
        "answer": "Compare pages, export pages, get data, and what links here."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Ubuntu",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of Ubuntu releases does UMIACS support?",
        "answer": "UMIACS provides support for Ubuntu LTS (long-term support) releases."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the duration of support for previous Ubuntu LTS releases on the desktop and server?",
        "answer": "Previous Ubuntu LTS releases are supported for 3 years on the desktop and 5 years on the server."
      },
      {
        "question": "Starting with which version of Ubuntu LTS are both desktop and server releases supported for 5 years?",
        "answer": "Starting with Ubuntu 12.04 LTS, LTS releases will be supported for 5 years on both the desktop and the server."
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the end of life date for Ubuntu 16.04 LTS (Xenial)?",
        "answer": "The end of life date for Ubuntu 16.04 LTS (Xenial) was April 2021."
      },
      {
        "question": "What abilities do users have regarding software installation in Ubuntu according to UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Users have the ability to install software from blessed repositories without staff intervention."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does the desktop software experience of Ubuntu compare to RHEL offerings?",
        "answer": "Ubuntu provides a more bleeding edge desktop software experience than the RHEL offerings."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can the software that is commonly provided with Ubuntu LTS releases be found?",
        "answer": "The software is found in /opt/common."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of software are included in the binary software common tree for Ubuntu LTS releases?",
        "answer": "The software includes Matlab, Mathematica, Compilers, etc."
      },
      {
        "question": "What functionality was introduced starting with Ubuntu 14.04 LTS regarding software paths and libraries?",
        "answer": "Starting with Ubuntu 14.04 LTS, you can use Modules to easily load these paths and relevant libraries into your environment."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/NautilusThumbnails",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What step should be taken in the file browser window to access the preferences?",
        "answer": "In the top bar click 'File -> Preferences'."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which tab must be navigated to in order to adjust the thumbnail settings?",
        "answer": "Navigate to the 'Search & Preview' tab."
      },
      {
        "question": "What option must be selected under the thumbnails section to disable thumbnail generation?",
        "answer": "Under the thumbnails section select 'Never'."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where are the thumbnails stored on the system?",
        "answer": "Thumbnails are stored in the directory ~/.cache/thumbnails/."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to check the current disk space utilization of the thumbnails?",
        "answer": "The command is 'du -sh ~/.cache/thumbnails/'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the result of removing the directory ~/.cache/thumbnails/?",
        "answer": "Removing that directory will clean up the thumbnails."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Email",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the format of the email address provided to a UMIACS account?",
        "answer": "A UMIACS account includes a username@umiacs.umd.edu e-mail address."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required for University of Maryland employees concerning their UMIACS email address?",
        "answer": "If you are a University of Maryland employee, this address is required to forward to your directoryid@umd.edu e-mail address."
      },
      {
        "question": "What options do non-University of Maryland employees have regarding their UMIACS email address forwarding?",
        "answer": "If you are not a University of Maryland employee, you can forward this address to an external email provider."
      },
      {
        "question": "For how long can email forwarding be provided if a UMIACS account was closed?",
        "answer": "If your UMIACS account was closed within the last year, we can provide forwarding for this address up until one year from the date that the account was closed upon request only."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do to set up forwarding for a closed UMIACS account?",
        "answer": "Please contact staff and let us know the address to forward to."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can users with a previous UMIACS Exchange or IMAP mailbox request after the email migration in June 2020?",
        "answer": "If you would like a copy of the archive of your mailbox we made, please contact staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can users verify their current email preference?",
        "answer": "You can verify your current E-mail preference through the Directory Profile Tool."
      },
      {
        "question": "What has UMIACS deployed into their mail infrastructure to enhance email security?",
        "answer": "UMIACS has deployed spam firewalls into our mail infrastructure to provide additional virus and spam filtering capabilities."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can users find more information about interacting with their spam quarantine?",
        "answer": "Please see the Spam firewall page."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Vtune",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of the Intel VTune Amplifier XE Suite?",
        "answer": "The Intel VTune Amplifier XE Suite is a profiler and performance analyzer for Intel chips."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of license does UMIACS have for the Intel VTune Amplifier XE Suite?",
        "answer": "UMIACS has a single floating license that can be checked out for RHEL."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command is used to load the VTune Modules in the shell?",
        "answer": "The command to load the VTune Modules in the shell is 'module load vtune'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two interfaces available for using the Intel VTune Amplifier XE Suite?",
        "answer": "The two interfaces available are amplxe-cl for the command line and amplxe-gui for the graphical user interface."
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SLURM",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary function of SLURM as a workload manager?",
        "answer": "It allocates exclusive or non-exclusive access to resources (computer nodes) to users for some duration of time so they can perform work."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to run a parallel job on a cluster managed by SLURM?",
        "answer": "srun"
      },
      {
        "question": "How does the salloc command function after successfully obtaining a job allocation?",
        "answer": "It runs the command specified by the user and relinquishes the job allocation when the command is complete."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to check the status of jobs managed by SLURM?",
        "answer": "squeue"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the sacct command display?",
        "answer": "Job accounting data stored in the job accounting log file or SLURM database, including information on jobs, job steps, status, and exit codes."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be done before starting a Jupyter Notebook on a compute node?",
        "answer": "Create and activate a Python virtual environment on the compute node and install Jupyter using pip."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required to tunnel a Jupyter Notebook port from a compute node to a local machine?",
        "answer": "Run the command 'ssh -N -f -L localhost:8888:<NODENAME>:8889 <USERNAME>@<SUBMISSIONNODE>.umiacs.umd.edu' with the appropriate replacements."
      },
      {
        "question": "If a Jupyter Notebook has token authentication enabled, what part of the URL must be included to connect?",
        "answer": "/?token=XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the previous workload manager used at UMIACS before adopting SLURM?",
        "answer": "PBS/TORQUE"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which SLURM command corresponds to the PBS command 'qdel'?",
        "answer": "scancel"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SecureShell/MFA",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the multi-factor authentication (MFA) requirements implemented by UMIACS for SSH connections?",
        "answer": "To provide better account and data security."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must a user do if they want to use SSH without needing to additionally multi-factor authenticate?",
        "answer": "Connect to the VPN first."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which two authentication methods are currently supported for SSH connections on internal hosts?",
        "answer": "Interactive password authentication and public key authentication."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of authentication does the multi-factor authentication-enabled SSH on public-facing hosts support?",
        "answer": "Only interactive password authentication."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which hardware tokens are not supported for SSH login specifically according to the UMIACS guidelines?",
        "answer": "U2F hardware tokens registered with Duo."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will happen if a user tries to SSH into another public-facing host after successfully logging in without a VPN?",
        "answer": "Subsequent SSH attempts will not require multi-factor authentication."
      },
      {
        "question": "What prompt appears after entering a password for SSH login with multi-factor authentication enabled?",
        "answer": "Duo two-factor login for username. Enter a passcode or select one of the following options."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does choosing the option 'Phone call to XXX-XXX-XXXX' do during the authentication process?",
        "answer": "It calls the registered phone and asks the user to press any key on their phone to proceed."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the function of the code shown in the Duo app or on a hardware token during the authentication process?",
        "answer": "The code is used to authenticate the user."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if they want to minimize repeated multi-factor authentication steps while using SSH?",
        "answer": "First establish a connection over the VPN or use a terminal multiplexer like Screen or Tmux."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SLURM/Preemption",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What should a user ensure when submitting a job to a partition that is eligible for preemption?",
        "answer": "The user is responsible for making sure that their job can be interrupted/restarted gracefully."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two fields of note set in the output of 'scontrol --json show job $SLURM_JOBID' when a job is cancelled?",
        "answer": "job_state = ['CANCELLED', 'COMPLETING']"
      },
      {
        "question": "What signal does the Slurm controller send to the nodes when a job is cancelled?",
        "answer": "An internal cancel signal."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to a job once it is stopped due to preemption?",
        "answer": "It enters the PENDING state for two minutes, and then is eligible to be run again."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be checked to determine if a job needs to behave differently after preemption?",
        "answer": "The environment variable SLURM_RESTART_COUNT."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command can be used to manually cancel a job?",
        "answer": "scancel <job id>"
      },
      {
        "question": "What environment variable is defined when a job runs again after being preempted?",
        "answer": "SLURM_RESTART_COUNT"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does SIGKILL do if processes don't stop within a certain amount of time after being cancelled or preempted?",
        "answer": "SIGKILL will be sent to forcibly terminate the processes."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command should a user run within their script to check the job state after a SIGTERM signal?",
        "answer": "scontrol --json show job $SLURM_JOBID"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the equivalent REST API endpoint for the output of 'scontrol --json show job $SLURM_JOBID'?",
        "answer": "GET /slurm/v0.0.40/job/{job_id}"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Setting_File_Permissions_in_Windows",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to change file permissions in Windows according to the provided text?",
        "answer": "Right-click the file or directory you would like to change permissions for and click on 'Properties.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the folder whose permissions are being changed in the example?",
        "answer": "\"ExampleFolder\""
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the owner of the folder \"ExampleFolder\"?",
        "answer": "\"GenericUser\""
      },
      {
        "question": "Which user has been granted permissions to the folder in the example?",
        "answer": "\"Example\""
      },
      {
        "question": "After opening the properties menu, which tab needs to be selected to change permissions?",
        "answer": "'Security'"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which button must be clicked to access advanced settings for permission changes?",
        "answer": "'Advanced'"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of selecting 'Show Advanced permissions'?",
        "answer": "To view more granular permissions."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do after selecting the permissions for the user?",
        "answer": "Apply all changes by clicking the 'OK' or 'Apply' button at the bottom of each menu as necessary."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/RevisionControl",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What version control system should users utilize according to the text?",
        "answer": "Users should use GitLab."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of projects does GitLab support as mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "GitLab supports personal projects and collaboration with UMIACS users and Offsite users."
      },
      {
        "question": "What features does GitLab provide according to the information from the text?",
        "answer": "GitLab provides a multitude of revision control features."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Gurobi",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is Gurobi Optimizer used for?",
        "answer": "Gurobi Optimizer is a suite of solvers for mathematical programming."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can Gurobi be accessed through the module tree?",
        "answer": "Gurobi can be accessed through the module tree with the command module add gurobi."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can more information about Gurobi be found?",
        "answer": "More information can be found on the Modules page."
      },
      {
        "question": "What error message will Gurobi display if it is run on the Nexus submission nodes?",
        "answer": "Gurobi will give the error message 'Error 10009: Server must be on the same subnet'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if you encounter the error message 'Error 10009' while using Gurobi?",
        "answer": "If you encounter this error, try running the command in a SLURM job."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if issues with Gurobi persist after trying SLURM jobs?",
        "answer": "If you're still having issues, please contact the HelpDesk."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Stow",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary subject of the wiki page titled 'Stow'?",
        "answer": "GNU Stow"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the URL provided in the text for GNU Stow?",
        "answer": "http://www.gnu.org/software/stow/"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of content retrieval is mentioned in the information provided?",
        "answer": "Retrieved from 'https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php?title=Stow&oldid=3966'"
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Windows_Activation",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the time frame in which the installs must verify activation for UMD-licensed Windows installations?",
        "answer": "The installs will have to verify activation every 180 days."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is necessary for laptops or home machines to perform renewal activation automatically?",
        "answer": "As long as the laptop or home machine is periodically on the campus wireless or connects to the UMIACS or campus VPN, renewal activation will be performed automatically."
      },
      {
        "question": "What network connections are required to activate Windows according to the instructions?",
        "answer": "You need to be connected to either the wired campus network, campus WiFi, the campus VPN, or the UMIACS VPN to activate."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be done to ensure the time is set correctly for activation to work?",
        "answer": "Your time must be correct (i.e., set via the Internet) and set to the US Eastern timezone."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is suggested to run before executing the activation commands in case of failure?",
        "answer": "You can try running w32tm /resync on the command line before running the other commands."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the correct sequence of commands to run in the Command Prompt for activating Windows 10/11?",
        "answer": "The sequence is: cscript c:\\windows\\system32\\slmgr.vbs -skms kms.umd.edu:1688, cscript c:\\windows\\system32\\slmgr.vbs -ipk NPPR9-FWDCX-D2C8J-H872K-2YT43, cscript c:\\windows\\system32\\slmgr.vbs -ato."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command allows you to see when the current activation expires?",
        "answer": "You can run: cscript c:\\windows\\system32\\slmgr.vbs -xpr to see when the current activation expires."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who should you contact if you are unable to activate and the computer is owned by the Institute for Advanced Computer Studies?",
        "answer": "You should contact UMIACS staff with information about your problem."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where should you contact if the computer you are attempting to activate is not owned by the Institute for Advanced Computer Studies?",
        "answer": "You should contact the Division of IT."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MonthlyMaintenanceWindow",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the monthly maintenance window conducted by UMIACS staff?",
        "answer": "The purpose is to patch and reboot all UMIACS-supported hosts and services to ensure security updates are installed and activated."
      },
      {
        "question": "How is the date of the maintenance window determined?",
        "answer": "The date is calculated by adding 9 days to Microsoft's Patch Tuesday, resulting in a window that is on the Thursday between the 17th and the 23rd of each month."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the operational hours of the maintenance window?",
        "answer": "The maintenance window lasts from 5pm to 8pm."
      },
      {
        "question": "What reservation does Nexus have in place during the maintenance window?",
        "answer": "Nexus has a reservation from 4:45pm to 8pm on the day of the upcoming window to prevent jobs from being scheduled on compute nodes."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to jobs submitted before the reservation begins if they run into the reservation time?",
        "answer": "Any job submitted before the reservation that has a time limit running into the reservation will be held until at least the end of the reservation at 8pm."
      },
      {
        "question": "When is the next maintenance window scheduled as stated in the document?",
        "answer": "The next maintenance window is scheduled for October 17th, 2024."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which vendors' patches are included in the maintenance window preparations?",
        "answer": "Patches released by Microsoft, Red Hat, Apple, and other OS and application vendors are included."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the adjusted time for the maintenance window that began on April 23rd, 2020?",
        "answer": "The adjusted time for that window was from 5pm to 7pm."
      },
      {
        "question": "How long generally does UMIACS maintain the schedule of monthly maintenance windows?",
        "answer": "The maintenance windows are scheduled to occur consistently on Thursdays between the 17th and 23rd of each month."
      },
      {
        "question": "What occurrence might lead to an adjusted date for the maintenance window?",
        "answer": "An example provided is an adjusted date for an AVW power outage."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/WindowsPrinting",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What must you do if you are off the UMIACS network before adding a printer queue?",
        "answer": "You must first connect to the VPN on Windows."
      },
      {
        "question": "What user prefix must be added to your username when authenticating to add a printer queue?",
        "answer": "'UMIACS\\' must be prefixed to your username."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should you follow if you receive an error when attempting to add a printer queue due to security configurations?",
        "answer": "You should click on the Start menu, type 'cmd', right-click and select 'Run as Administrator', then run the specified commands to adjust registry settings and restart the spooler."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to remove a printer queue from a Windows machine?",
        "answer": "Open the Start menu and search for and go to Control Panel."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must you do in order to set duplex printing as the default for a printer?",
        "answer": "Right-click on the installed printer queue, select 'Printing preferences', go to the 'Printing Shortcuts' tab, select 'EcoSMART Settings', and click OK."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of PIN-protected jobs when printing at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "PIN-protected jobs ensure that print jobs are not printed until the user is ready to pick them up, which is useful for sensitive documents."
      },
      {
        "question": "When creating a stored job, what should you select under Job Storage Mode?",
        "answer": "You should select 'Personal Job'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to a print job after it is printed from the printer's control panel?",
        "answer": "The print job is deleted from memory after it prints."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Google_Drive",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is Google Drive?",
        "answer": "Google Drive is a file storage and synchronization service developed by Google."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who has access to unlimited Google Drive storage at UMD?",
        "answer": "All current faculty, staff, and students at UMD have unlimited Google Drive storage when using their UMD-provided account."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can the overarching documentation for Google Drive be found?",
        "answer": "The overarching documentation for Google Drive can be found at https://support.google.com/drive/"
      },
      {
        "question": "What application does Google currently offer for Drive interaction?",
        "answer": "Google currently offers a single unified app called Google Drive for Desktop, which can be downloaded."
      },
      {
        "question": "Is there a migration step for users who used Google Drive Backup and Sync?",
        "answer": "Yes, if users previously used Google Drive Backup and Sync, they should follow migration steps provided."
      },
      {
        "question": "What platforms does Google Drive for Desktop support?",
        "answer": "Google Drive for Desktop supports Windows and macOS."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Mattermost",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What messaging features does Mattermost support?",
        "answer": "Mattermost supports direct one to one messaging, teams with public and private channels, extensive search capabilities, and file sharing."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where is the Mattermost platform hosted?",
        "answer": "The Mattermost platform is hosted in one of the physical on-premise data centers."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required for logging into Mattermost?",
        "answer": "Logging into Mattermost requires integration with the GitLab authentication system and its MFA requirement."
      },
      {
        "question": "What options do users have when signing into Mattermost?",
        "answer": "Users are prompted to use GitLab to login and then log in with the UMIACS Single Sign On. They can also select which Teams they would like to join by default, including the option to select the UMIACS Team."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can faculty, labs, and centers acquire a private Team on Mattermost?",
        "answer": "Faculty, labs, and centers can request a private Team for their research groups, labs, or centers by contacting staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of documentation does Mattermost maintain?",
        "answer": "Mattermost maintains extensive documentation about using the service, including information about Teams, Channels, and Direct Messages."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of messaging formatting does Mattermost support?",
        "answer": "Mattermost supports rich text messaging formatting, including using markdown and other simple techniques."
      },
      {
        "question": "What applications are available for using Mattermost?",
        "answer": "There are desktop and mobile applications that can be downloaded for using Mattermost."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must users enter when using the desktop and mobile applications for Mattermost?",
        "answer": "Users need to enter the URL for the service, https://mattermost.umiacs.umd.edu, to sign in and use the service."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to teams after 6 months of inactivity?",
        "answer": "Teams will be archived if there is no activity for 6 months within the team channels."
      },
      {
        "question": "When will user account data be archived?",
        "answer": "User account data will be archived when their UMIACS accounts are archived."
      }
    ],
    "total": 11
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/BarracudaSpamFirewall/QuarantinePassthrough",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Quarantine Passthrough feature in Barracuda?",
        "answer": "The Quarantine Passthrough feature allows mail that would ordinarily be quarantined by Barracuda to be delivered to your mailbox instead."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the process to configure the Quarantine Passthrough using the Barracuda web interface?",
        "answer": "To configure Quarantine Passthrough, log in to the Barracuda web interface with your UMIACS email address and password, click the Preferences tab, select Quarantine Settings, change the Quarantine Enable/Disable option to 'No', and then click Save Changes."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will happen to the mail that would have been captured by the Barracuda quarantine filter if the setting is changed to 'No'?",
        "answer": "If the setting is changed to 'No', all mail that would be captured by the Barracuda quarantine filter will instead be delivered to your mailbox with the tag [QUAR] prepended to the subject line."
      },
      {
        "question": "After disabling the quarantine filter, what action may a user decide to take regarding emails?",
        "answer": "After disabling the quarantine filter, the user may wish to set up a filter to redirect the messages that are now delivered to their inbox to an appropriate folder."
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SecureShell",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What command is used to connect a client computer to the UMIACS Nexus under Linux and macOS?",
        "answer": "# ssh username@nexusgroup00.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be installed on a macOS client machine to use X11 Forwarding?",
        "answer": "xQuartz"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which command is used to enable X11 Forwarding for a connection to the UMIACS Nexus?",
        "answer": "# ssh -Y username@nexusgroup00.umiacs.umd.edu"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required on Windows to forward X sessions when connecting via SSH?",
        "answer": "VcXsrv or another X11 application"
      },
      {
        "question": "What security measure does UMIACS require when connecting from the public internet?",
        "answer": "multi-factor authentication"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does SSH utilize for authenticating and authorizing users to enhance security?",
        "answer": "public key encryption"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if prompted about the authenticity of a host's SSH key on a first-time connection?",
        "answer": "Verify the key fingerprint with the actual key of the host."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to determine the fingerprint of an RSA key type on a remote host?",
        "answer": "$ ssh-keyscan -t rsa nexusgroup00.umiacs.umd.edu > key"
      },
      {
        "question": "What option must be enabled in PuTTY to use X Forwarding?",
        "answer": "Connection > SSH > X11"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of using a screen session for long-running processes on a remote host?",
        "answer": "To allow the process to continue running even if the connection is dropped."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MFA",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is multi-factor authentication (MFA)?",
        "answer": "Multi-factor authentication (MFA) is a method of confirming a user's claimed identity in which a user is granted access only after successfully presenting 2 or more pieces of evidence (or factors) to an authentication mechanism."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the three valid factors used in multi-factor authentication?",
        "answer": "The three valid factors are: knowledge (something they and only they know), possession (something they and only they have), and inherence (something they and only they are)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which security platform does UMIACS utilize for MFA?",
        "answer": "UMIACS utilizes the Duo security platform to allow mobile devices to serve as a second factor."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Nexus/CLIP",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What happened to the previous standalone cluster for CLIP as of late 2022?",
        "answer": "The previous standalone cluster for CLIP's compute nodes have folded into Nexus."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can you access by connecting to the submission hosts nexusclip00.umiacs.umd.edu or nexusclip01.umiacs.umd.edu?",
        "answer": "You can log in to a submission host."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the names of the actual submission hosts for the Nexus cluster?",
        "answer": "The actual submission hosts are nexusclip00.umiacs.umd.edu and nexusclip01.umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What specific job QoS is available for longer jobs using higher overall resources in the CLIP partition?",
        "answer": "The additional job QoS for the CLIP partition specifically is 'huge-long'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must you specify in order to submit jobs to the CLIP partition?",
        "answer": "You need to specify --partition=clip and --account=clip."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the GrpTRES limit for jobs in the CLIP partition?",
        "answer": "The GrpTRES limit is 100% of the available cores/RAM on the partition-specific nodes in aggregate plus 50% of the available cores/RAM on legacy## nodes in aggregate."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if they store something in a local directory on a submission host?",
        "answer": "The user will need to connect to that same submission host to access it later."
      },
      {
        "question": "What details are provided regarding a job submission example in terms of resources and state?",
        "answer": "The job showed that it was queued and waiting for resources, and later allocated with the job state being RUNNING."
      },
      {
        "question": "What specific command is indicated for running a job in the submission example?",
        "answer": "The command indicated is 'srun --pty --ntasks=4 --mem=8G --qos=default --partition=clip --account=clip --time 1-00:00:00 bash'."
      },
      {
        "question": "Are all data filesystems that were available in the standalone CLIP cluster also available in Nexus?",
        "answer": "Yes, all data filesystems that were available in the standalone CLIP cluster are also available in Nexus."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Automounter",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What automounter is utilized in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The automounter utilized in UMIACS is autofs."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary method used to mount almost all file systems in UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Almost all file systems are mounted with NFS."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you utilize the automounter according to the text?",
        "answer": "You can utilize the automounter by just changing directory into the target or into a directory underneath the target."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the most common file system mounted with the automounter?",
        "answer": "/nfshomes/fs/nexus-scratch"
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/BarracudaSpamFirewall/Scoring",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What scoring range allows the message to pass through to the Inbox?",
        "answer": "0.0 to 3.4"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the score range for messages that are tagged?",
        "answer": "3.5 to 8.9"
      },
      {
        "question": "At what score are messages quarantined?",
        "answer": "9.0 and above"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the X-Barracuda-Spam-Status header indicate for allowed messages?",
        "answer": "No, SCORE=0.00"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the TAG_LEVEL for the tagged message example provided?",
        "answer": "3.5"
      },
      {
        "question": "How can the domain default scoring thresholds and actions be changed?",
        "answer": "By logging into the Barracudas, going to Preferences -> Spam Settings, changing Use Domain Defaults from Yes to No, clicking Save, and customizing the score thresholds for each action."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the score of the quarantined message example?",
        "answer": "10.11"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which header can be filtered to route messages tagged by the Barracuda to another folder?",
        "answer": "X-Barracuda-Spam-Status: Yes or X-Barracuda-Spam-Flag: YES"
      },
      {
        "question": "What action is not performed for messages scored at 10.0 and above under domain default settings?",
        "answer": "Blocking of messages"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the X-Barracuda-Spam-Flag header indicate for a tagged message?",
        "answer": "YES"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/CML",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "Where is the Center for Machine Learning (CML) located?",
        "answer": "The Center for Machine Learning (CML) is located at the University of Maryland within the Institute for Advanced Computer Studies."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of computational resources does the CML have?",
        "answer": "The CML has a cluster of computational (CPU/GPU) resources."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required to use the computational resources at CML?",
        "answer": "The computational resources are available to be scheduled."
      },
      {
        "question": "What significant change occurred during the August 2023 maintenance window for CML's compute nodes?",
        "answer": "As of the August 2023 maintenance window, all compute nodes have moved into the Nexus cluster."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can one find more details about the Nexus and CML?",
        "answer": "More details can be found in Nexus/CML."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Printing",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What must be done before printing from a wireless network or non-UMIACS network?",
        "answer": "You will need to first connect to the UMIACS VPN."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which operating system printing guides are mentioned in the provided text?",
        "answer": "Windows Printing Guide, macOS Printing Guide, Linux Printing Guide (RHEL and Ubuntu), Self-supported Ubuntu Printing Guide."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two types of printing guides specifically mentioned for Linux?",
        "answer": "Linux Printing Guide (RHEL and Ubuntu) and Self-supported Ubuntu Printing Guide."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one of the topics included in the 'Section: Other Printing Pages'?",
        "answer": "Selecting A Print Queue (Color/Driver)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which types of printers does the text refer to under 'UMIACS Public Printers'?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Public Printers."
      },
      {
        "question": "What troubleshooting resource is mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "Printer troubleshooting."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/Logistics",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is required to place an order within UMIACS?",
        "answer": "An account within UMIACS to charge and approval of the account's Principal Investigator."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be included in the email sent to orders@umiacs.umd.edu for purchasing?",
        "answer": "An itemized list of the items you wish to purchase, as well as which account they should be charged to."
      }
    ],
    "total": 2
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SetGID",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What happens when a file with the setgid bit is executed?",
        "answer": "When a file with the setgid bit is executed, it sets the group's ID to the GID of the binary instead of the user running it."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the effect of the setgid bit on files that are not executable?",
        "answer": "The setgid bit has no effect on files that are not executable."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the security concerns associated with the use of the setgid bit for files?",
        "answer": "The use of the setgid bit for files can lead to security issues if the group has files that can be read or written when otherwise not permitted."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do setgid directories affect file creation within them?",
        "answer": "Setgid directories cause all filesystem creations under that directory to inherit the group from the directory."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is UMIACS policy regarding users' default UID and GID?",
        "answer": "UMIACS policy is to keep users' default UID and GID."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two appropriate umask settings mentioned for effective use of the setgid bit?",
        "answer": "The appropriate umask settings mentioned are 002 or 007."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to change the group of a directory to umadmin in the example?",
        "answer": "The command used is 'chgrp umadmin .'"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the permissions set for the directory after applying setgid in the example?",
        "answer": "The permissions set for the directory are rwxrwsr-x."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to create a new file named 'test' in the example?",
        "answer": "The command used to create the new file is 'touch test'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can be deduced about the group ownership of the created test directory and file?",
        "answer": "Both the test directory and the test file are owned by the umadmin group as indicated by the group ownership shown in the ls output."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/LDAP",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the Lightweight Directory Access Protocol used for at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "UMIACS uses the Lightweight Directory Access Protocol for a variety of system information, and for most users, it is the source of authentication and can be used to lookup users, offices, and email addresses of UMIACS users."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the server address for the LDAP at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The server address for the LDAP at UMIACS is ldap://ldap.umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the BaseDN (Base Distinguished Name) used in the LDAP at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The BaseDN used in the LDAP at UMIACS is dc=umiacs,dc=umd,dc=edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where are the people entries located in the LDAP structure at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The people entries are located at ou=people,dc=umiacs,dc=umd,dc=edu."
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/CUDA",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is CUDA and who invented it?",
        "answer": "CUDA is a parallel computing platform and programming model invented by NVIDIA."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the primary advantage of using CUDA?",
        "answer": "The primary advantage of using CUDA is the dramatic increases in computing performance by harnessing the power of the graphics processing unit (GPU)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the prerequisites needed to use CUDA?",
        "answer": "The prerequisites needed to use CUDA include an NVIDIA GPU device and an NVIDIA Driver."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can one check if their device is CUDA capable?",
        "answer": "If you are unsure if your device is CUDA capable, please contact staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to load the CUDA environmental variables via GNU Modules?",
        "answer": "The command used to load the CUDA environmental variables is 'module load cuda'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the process to obtain a copy of the CUDA samples?",
        "answer": "The process to obtain a copy of the CUDA samples is to use the command 'rsync -a /opt/common/cuda/<CUDA Version>/samples/ ~/cuda_samples'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps should be taken to build and run the device query sample?",
        "answer": "To build and run the device query sample, you need to change directory to '~/cuda_samples/1_Utilities/deviceQuery/', then run 'make' and './deviceQuery'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you expect to see if the deviceQuery compilation completed without error?",
        "answer": "If the deviceQuery compilation completed without error, you should see output listing the details of the GPUs in your system."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can additional CUDA samples be compiled?",
        "answer": "Additional CUDA samples can be compiled by switching to their respective directory and running 'make'."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Data_Storage",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the landing page for 'Data Storage' at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The purpose of the landing page for 'Data Storage' at UMIACS is to serve as a central resource for all topics related to data storage available at UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What section discusses where data can be stored according to the UMIACS page?",
        "answer": "The section that discusses where data can be stored is titled 'Where can I store my data?'"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which section addresses the methods for transferring data?",
        "answer": "The section that addresses methods for transferring data is titled 'How can I transfer my data?'"
      },
      {
        "question": "What best practices are outlined in the context of data storage on the UMIACS page?",
        "answer": "The best practices for data storage are outlined in the section titled 'What are some data storage best practices?'"
      },
      {
        "question": "What topic is covered under the section titled 'How is my data retained?'",
        "answer": "The topic covered under the section titled 'How is my data retained?' addresses data retention."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are some data transfer methods mentioned in the UMIACS page?",
        "answer": "The data transfer methods mentioned include Rclone, SCP, and FTP."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of data management strategies are referenced on the page regarding data backups?",
        "answer": "The strategies referenced regarding data backups include 'Snapshots', 'Nightly Backups', and 'Archives'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the nature of the content on the 'Data Storage' landing page at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "The content on the 'Data Storage' landing page at UMIACS is described as being under active development."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/MacOSPrinting",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What macOS version must be used to print from UMIACS network?",
        "answer": "macOS 13.x or later"
      },
      {
        "question": "What button must be clicked on the Printers & Scanners page to create a new local printer?",
        "answer": "Add Printer, Scanner, or Fax..."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which protocol should be set in the IP tab when adding a printer?",
        "answer": "Internet Printing Protocol - IPP"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the required format for setting the queue when adding a printer?",
        "answer": "printers/queue"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if you need access to more advanced features of a printer?",
        "answer": "Follow extra steps in the Advanced section at the bottom of the page."
      },
      {
        "question": "When prompted about duplex printing, what should you do if you are unsure whether the printer has the option?",
        "answer": "Just leave it disabled; you can enable it after the queue is added."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if you installed the printer with generic drivers and need to use advanced printing features?",
        "answer": "Highlight the printer and click - before attempting to add it again."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can the make and model of your printer be found when enabling advanced printing features?",
        "answer": "http://print.umiacs.umd.edu/printers/"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be selected in the dropdown list under 'Copies & Pages' when configuring a stored job?",
        "answer": "Job Storage"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default name of the folder where stored jobs are saved?",
        "answer": "Your username"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/FTP/macOS/Finder",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the first step to open macOS Finder?",
        "answer": "Click on the macOS Finder icon on the dock at the bottom of your desktop."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can an owner of the public folder modify files?",
        "answer": "The owner of the public folder can publish and modify files from a supported machine."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the keyboard shortcut to bring up the address bar in macOS Finder?",
        "answer": "Press Command + Shift + G."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you type into the address bar to access your public folder as an owner?",
        "answer": "/fs/ftp/pub/<username> - where <username> should be replaced with your username."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do external collaborators access the public folders?",
        "answer": "External collaborators can access the public folders through the Finder's 'Connect to Server' feature."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the keyboard shortcut to open the 'Connect to Server' window in Finder?",
        "answer": "Press Command + K on your keyboard."
      },
      {
        "question": "What address should collaborators enter in the server address bar to connect?",
        "answer": "ftp://ftp.umiacs.umd.edu/pub/<username> - where <username> should be replaced with the desired collaborator's username."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you select when prompted to connect as a collaborator?",
        "answer": "Choose to connect as a guest."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Programming",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "Which programming languages are specifically mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "C/C++, Java, Python, R"
      },
      {
        "question": "What information does the section provide about C/C++?",
        "answer": "It mentions C/C++ Compilers and C/C++ Debuggers."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which development environment is noted for Java in the text?",
        "answer": "Java Development Environment"
      },
      {
        "question": "What specific Python-related topics are mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "Python, Python Virtual Environment, Windows, Python OpenCV, and OpenCV Versions."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the title of the section from which this information is derived?",
        "answer": "Programming"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which software is mentioned in relation to R in the text?",
        "answer": "RStudio for Windows"
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/ConferenceRooms/Recording",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What software is recommended by UMIACS for video recording and live streaming?",
        "answer": "Open Broadcaster Software (OBS)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the 'Shared Media' option on the Crestron control panel?",
        "answer": "It routes the selected source through the A/V Bridge to the conference room computer."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user do if the output appears blurry or fuzzy while using OBS?",
        "answer": "They should set the Resolution/FPS Type to Custom and change it from Device Default to the highest available resolution."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a user ensure that audio settings are correct in OBS?",
        "answer": "They should check that the default microphone is set as Mic/Aux under the Mixer pane and can change it by clicking on the cog -> Properties if they want to use an alternate microphone."
      },
      {
        "question": "What do users need to do if they do not want desktop audio recorded during a conference?",
        "answer": "They should click the megaphone icon under Desktop Audio to mute it."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can a user find their stream key for YouTube?",
        "answer": "At the YouTube live dashboard, which can be accessed through the link: https://www.youtube.com/live_dashboard."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the recommended recording path setting if recording in a conference room?",
        "answer": "It should be set to an external SSD or the internal drive."
      },
      {
        "question": "What issue might arise from using external HDDs for recording?",
        "answer": "Using external HDDs may introduce dropped frames due to encoding lag because of I/O bottlenecks."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Google_Drive/Drive_for_Desktop",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the operating systems for which Drive for Desktop is available?",
        "answer": "Drive for Desktop is available for Windows and macOS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What functionality does Drive for Desktop provide regarding local files?",
        "answer": "Drive for Desktop automatically syncs local files and directories of your choosing to your Google Drive in the background."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps must a user follow to install Drive for Desktop on Windows?",
        "answer": "Once downloaded, open the downloaded file to bring up the installation window, select preferences for application and desktop shortcuts, then select install. After that, sign in with your <DIRECTORYID>@umd.edu email address and follow the prompts to complete installation."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first action required after downloading Drive for Desktop on a Mac?",
        "answer": "The first action required is to open the downloaded file and install Drive for Desktop."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can users add folders to back up to their Google Drive using Drive for Desktop?",
        "answer": "Users can add folders by going to the 'Preferences' page, selecting 'Add Folder', and then choosing any local folder they wish to back up."
      },
      {
        "question": "What option is available for backing up photos instead of files in Google Drive?",
        "answer": "Users have the option to back up their photos to Google Photos instead of their Google Drive."
      },
      {
        "question": "What confirmation does the user see before signing into Drive for Desktop after downloading it?",
        "answer": "The user is prompted with 'Make sure that you downloaded this app from Google' before signing in."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can users customize the appearance of their Google Drive files on their machine?",
        "answer": "Users can customize how files stored on Google Drive appear by selecting the 'Google Drive' option in the preferences window under their computer name."
      },
      {
        "question": "What alternative method for backing up files to Google Drive is suggested for Linux users?",
        "answer": "Linux users can set up Rclone with a cronjob to copy files to their Google Drive periodically."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional step need to be taken after installing Drive for Desktop regarding folder selection on both Windows and Mac?",
        "answer": "Users need to go to the 'Preferences' page to select the folders they would like to have backed up."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/ConferenceRooms",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What must be accepted by designated moderator(s) for reserving a moderated room?",
        "answer": "Reservations must be accepted by the designated moderator(s) for the room."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the capacity range for auto-accept rooms?",
        "answer": "Auto-accept rooms can accommodate 6-12 persons."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can huddle rooms be reserved?",
        "answer": "Huddle rooms can only be reserved at the touch panel."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is indicated by a red status on the touch panel outside the conference room?",
        "answer": "A red status indicates that the room is reserved right now."
      },
      {
        "question": "What system is used to view conference room availability?",
        "answer": "UMD’s Google Calendar system is used to view conference room availability."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the minimum AV capability available in all conference rooms?",
        "answer": "You should be able to either plug in your laptop to display to the projector and screen(s), or use the Solstice Mersive Pod to display wirelessly."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can be done if a non-moderated room is unoccupied within the next 12 hours?",
        "answer": "You can walk up to the panel and reserve the room if it is unoccupied within the next 12 hours."
      },
      {
        "question": "In what context can moderators approve room requests?",
        "answer": "Moderators can approve room requests when they are reserving a room."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/PrinterTroubleshooting",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What steps should be taken if there is trouble printing a PDF?",
        "answer": "Choose File >>> Print, and then click Advanced. Select the Print As Image check box, and click Ok. Then click print."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can one find more information about fixing PDF printing issues?",
        "answer": "More information can be found at Adobe quick fix."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is suggested for users experiencing other printing errors on Windows?",
        "answer": "Try using a pcl queue for MS/Office applications and a ps queue for Adobe applications."
      },
      {
        "question": "What alternative solutions are proposed if users encounter printing issues?",
        "answer": "Try using a different printer model and try using a different print queue."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the text say about adding new print queues?",
        "answer": "New print queues can be added with directions for respective operating systems on the printing page."
      }
    ],
    "total": 5
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/WebSensitiveInformation",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of information does UMIACS not store on their web servers to maintain maximum security?",
        "answer": "Sensitive information."
      },
      {
        "question": "How is sensitive information handled upon receipt at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "It is encrypted in memory and sent to a designated email address."
      },
      {
        "question": "What software is recommended for email encryption/decryption at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "WinPT (Windows Privacy Tray)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required to use WinPT software?",
        "answer": "GnuPG 1.4.11 or higher must be installed on the computer."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the first step when running the WinPT program for the first time?",
        "answer": "You will be asked to generate your 'keypair'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does a keypair contain in the context of WinPT?",
        "answer": "A public key, which is used for encryption, and a private key, which is used for decryption."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can users send encrypted messages to others using WinPT?",
        "answer": "They must export their public key and send it to the other party."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should never be distributed to others when using WinPT?",
        "answer": "The private key."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be done to accept sensitive information online, such as credit card information at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "It is mandatory to use encrypted messages."
      },
      {
        "question": "To whom should the public key be sent when accepting sensitive information online via UMIACS?",
        "answer": "It should be sent to webmaster@umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional resource is suggested for an in-depth guide on WinPT?",
        "answer": "Consult the over-simplified WinPT Tutorial at http://sebsauvage.net/winpt_en.html."
      }
    ],
    "total": 11
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/BitLocker",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is BitLocker Drive Encryption and what threats does it address?",
        "answer": "BitLocker Drive Encryption is a data protection feature available in all modern versions of Windows. It addresses the threats of data theft or exposure from lost, stolen, or inappropriately decommissioned computers."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does BitLocker help mitigate unauthorized access to data?",
        "answer": "BitLocker helps mitigate unauthorized data access by enhancing file and system protections."
      },
      {
        "question": "What circumstances may cause BitLocker to detect changes to the system boot information?",
        "answer": "Circumstances that may lead to BitLocker detecting changes include BIOS or firmware updates, DVDs or USB drives inserted during boot, and malware on the system."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be done if a recovery prompt appears after booting the computer?",
        "answer": "The first step should always be to disconnect any external devices and then power the machine off and back on."
      },
      {
        "question": "What actions are recommended if one anticipates making changes that affect BitLocker?",
        "answer": "If you know you will be making a change that affects BitLocker, you should search for BitLocker in the Start menu, click on 'Manage BitLocker', and then click 'Suspend protection' on the Operating system drive."
      },
      {
        "question": "What must be done after performing an operation that triggers BitLocker recovery?",
        "answer": "After booting back into Windows, click 'Resume protection' to ensure BitLocker will resume and commit the current boot configuration."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which machines will have BitLocker enabled according to UMIACS?",
        "answer": "All supported personal office workstations and all enterprise or base-supported laptops and home machines will have BitLocker enabled by UMIACS staff."
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can official Microsoft documentation about BitLocker be found?",
        "answer": "Official Microsoft documentation can be found at https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/device-security/bitlocker/bitlocker-overview."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Jira",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is Jira used for by UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Jira is a request and bug tracker that UMIACS uses to provide their HelpDesk functionality to users."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can a UMIACS account holder log in to Jira?",
        "answer": "A UMIACS account holder can log in to Jira using the UMIACS Single Sign On service."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if a user emails Jira without having a UMIACS account?",
        "answer": "When a non-UMIACS account holder emails Jira, a ticket is created, and the email address used is added as a participant to the ticket."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will a user receive the first time they use a new email address to submit a ticket in Jira?",
        "answer": "The user will receive an automated email containing a link to set a password for the newly-created Jira account."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the steps to log in using a non-UMIACS email address?",
        "answer": "A user must log in to Jira using the non-UMIACS email address and the password they set after receiving the automated email."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can a user do if they no longer have the automated email to set their password?",
        "answer": "The user can go to the external user page, click 'Forgot your password?', and enter their email address as the username to set it."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Kerberos",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary purpose of Kerberos as mentioned in the introduction?",
        "answer": "Kerberos provides a toolkit for reducing the risks associated with insecure networks."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does Kerberos manage strong passwords?",
        "answer": "It provides a unified password space in which we can manage strong passwords easily."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to the user's credentials after one week at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Credentials expire after one week at UMIACS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to list current Kerberos credentials?",
        "answer": "klist"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does 'Default principal' signify in the context of Kerberos credentials?",
        "answer": "'Default principal' indicates the Kerberos identity of the current process."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the output of 'klist' indicate if the credentials are not set up correctly?",
        "answer": "klist will report: klist: No credentials cache found."
      },
      {
        "question": "What advantage does Kerberos offer for IMAP and SMTP services?",
        "answer": "Kerberos authenticated IMAP and SMTP provide secure and convenient methods for sending and reading mail."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the responsibility of the user regarding password security in Kerberos?",
        "answer": "It is still your responsibility to secure your password."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/GitLab",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is GitLab used for?",
        "answer": "GitLab is source code collaboration software based on Git that allows users to create their own repositories and share them with other users/groups or publicly."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the storage limit for projects created by non-class account UMIACS users?",
        "answer": "All non-class account UMIACS users are given 10 projects with a hard limit of 800Mb per project."
      },
      {
        "question": "What kind of support does UMIACS Staff provide regarding GitLab?",
        "answer": "UMIACS Staff can help create Lab groups and delegate authority to manage the group to one or more faculty members."
      },
      {
        "question": "What URL should be navigated to in order to log in to GitLab?",
        "answer": "To log in to GitLab, navigate to https://gitlab.umiacs.umd.edu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the two methods by which users can clone git repositories in GitLab?",
        "answer": "Users can clone git repositories over either SSH or HTTPS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the recommendation regarding the use of SSH compared to HTTPS for cloning repositories?",
        "answer": "SSH is recommended because it is more convenient for most users."
      },
      {
        "question": "What utility must be accessed to create offsite collaborator accounts for UMIACS users?",
        "answer": "The utility can be found in the Requests application under UMIACS Collaborators."
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you need to do in order to use SSH for GitLab?",
        "answer": "You need to add an SSH key to your GitLab account."
      },
      {
        "question": "Under what conditions can projects be made public in GitLab?",
        "answer": "Projects can only be made public by the owner."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps must be followed to make a GitLab project public?",
        "answer": "1. Go to your project page. 2. Click on Settings. 3. Scroll down to Project Visibility and choose Public. 4. Scroll down and click on Save Changes. 5. Scroll down to Repository under Project Visibility and select Everyone with access. 6. Click on Save Changes."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Services/Data",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of storage is described under 'Object Storage'?",
        "answer": "Block storage"
      },
      {
        "question": "What services are included in the 'Data Archiving' section?",
        "answer": "Long term storage of data (DEPRECATED)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What service is offered for transferring files in the 'Data Distribution' category?",
        "answer": "FTP service"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are home directories and lab fileshares included in the current offerings?",
        "answer": "Yes"
      }
    ],
    "total": 4
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/VS_Code",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "Who developed Visual Studio Code?",
        "answer": "Microsoft."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of editor is Visual Studio Code?",
        "answer": "A multi-platform source-code editor."
      },
      {
        "question": "Can the basic functionality of Visual Studio Code be extended, and if so, how?",
        "answer": "Yes, it can be extended through extensions available via its marketplace."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one key reason why users are advised to use VS Code only as a code editor on submission nodes?",
        "answer": "Using it for file management operations can cause load spikes that slow down other processes."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should users do instead of opening large files in VS Code on submission nodes?",
        "answer": "Use a lighter-weight command-line based text editor such as vim, or transfer the files to a less-used remote machine or local machine before opening them."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens to files opened in VS Code on a remote machine through the Remote - SSH extension?",
        "answer": "They are loaded entirely into RAM on the remote machine."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if you are done using VS Code for an extended period of time?",
        "answer": "Consider manually killing your server session on the submission node when exiting."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to kill the VS Code Server on a host?",
        "answer": "Open the Command Palette with Ctrl+Shift+P and search for 'Kill VS Code Server on Host...'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What troubleshooting step should you take if you are unable to SSH into a submission node using VS Code?",
        "answer": "Check if your home directory is full."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you check if your home directory is full?",
        "answer": "By navigating to your home directory and running the command 'df -h.'"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Lamsub.sh.e127",
    "Q/A": [],
    "total": 0
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/SLURM/JobSubmission",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the srun command in the SLURM job submission system?",
        "answer": "The srun command is used to run a process on the compute nodes in the cluster by submitting a job to run a shell command/script on a compute node."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command would you use to request 2 gigabytes of memory for your job using sbatch?",
        "answer": "$ sbatch --qos=default --mem=2g --time=1:00:00 helloWorld.sh"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you use if you want to run processes interactively for debugging on a compute node?",
        "answer": "You should use srun with the --pty argument to invoke a shell."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does one request to run a job on a specific node using srun?",
        "answer": "You can request to run your job on a specific node by using the --nodelist=<NODENAME> option in the srun command."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command can be used to cancel an active job allocation?",
        "answer": "The scancel command can be used to cancel job allocations."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command provides details about the available GPUs and other resources on nodes?",
        "answer": "The show_available_nodes command provides details about the available GPUs and other resources on nodes."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default behavior of srun regarding process input and output?",
        "answer": "By default, input to srun is broadcast to all compute nodes running the process, and output from the compute nodes is redirected to srun."
      },
      {
        "question": "In the sbatch script example provided, what does the line '#SBATCH --error=helloWorld.out.%j' specify?",
        "answer": "This line specifies a file to redirect STDERR to, where '%j' is replaced with the job ID."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the --exclusive option do when included in a job request?",
        "answer": "The --exclusive option requests that your job be the only one running on the node(s) it is assigned to."
      },
      {
        "question": "When using the salloc command, what happens when you exit the subshell?",
        "answer": "When you exit the subshell, your job allocation will be relinquished."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Datasets",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the faculty approvers for the CML, GAMMA, and Vulcan dataset directories?",
        "answer": "The faculty approver for CML is Tom Goldstein, for GAMMA is Dinesh Manocha, and for Vulcan is Abhinav Shrivastava."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required in order to request a new dataset if the uncompressed/final dataset size is over 100GB?",
        "answer": "If the uncompressed/final dataset size is over 100GB, staff will first contact the faculty approver for the cluster to ensure they approve of using the storage space."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should a user specify when requesting a dataset from the Nexus directory?",
        "answer": "A user must let staff know which faculty member's research they are working on that requires the use of the dataset they are requesting."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens if the uncompressed/final dataset size requested from the Nexus directory is over 50GB?",
        "answer": "If the size is over 50GB, the Director of Computing Facilities must first approve of using the storage space."
      },
      {
        "question": "What types of links are not allowed when requesting a new dataset?",
        "answer": "Mirrors and torrents/other peer-to-peer re-hosting are not allowed unless sanctioned by the dataset owners."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps are taken by staff after a new dataset is requested and there are no terms and conditions?",
        "answer": "Staff will download/extract the dataset, copy it to the appropriate location depending on what cluster you are requesting it for, and let you know when it is available for use on that cluster."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required if the dataset's terms and conditions exceed well-defined Creative Commons licenses?",
        "answer": "The dataset's terms and conditions must be approved by UMD's Office of Research Administration before the dataset can be hosted."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the policy regarding the storage of intermediate data generated from a dataset?",
        "answer": "Any intermediate data generated from a dataset will need to be stored in a location other than the shared filesystem hosting the dataset."
      },
      {
        "question": "Under what conditions might exceptions be granted for storing intermediate data generated from a dataset?",
        "answer": "Exceptions may be granted if there is a set of intermediate data generated from a dataset that is believed to be useful to a subset of a cluster's users."
      }
    ],
    "total": 9
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Subversion",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "When was the Subversion service at UMIACS fully deprecated?",
        "answer": "June 21, 2024"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is required to have a Subversion repository created at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "You need to email staff and provide the name of your repository and how much initial space you think you will need."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will you receive after requesting a Subversion repository?",
        "answer": "You will receive a URL back with the server in it."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the default configuration for all repositories created at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "They will be private and require authentication for both reading and writing."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which authentication method is used for Subversion at UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Authentication is done against LDAP using SecGroups."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to check out a repository from UMIACS?",
        "answer": "svn co https://subversion.umiacs.umd.edu/my_url"
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to add files that are not under revision control yet?",
        "answer": "svn add"
      },
      {
        "question": "Where can you find the defacto book on Subversion?",
        "answer": "In HTML at http://svnbook.red-bean.com/en/1.4/svn-book.html or in PDF at http://svnbook.red-bean.com/en/1.4/svn-book.pdf"
      },
      {
        "question": "What should be added to the subversion configuration file to disable password caching completely on Linux?",
        "answer": "\"store-passwords = no\""
      },
      {
        "question": "What fingerprint should be verified when connecting to the UMIACS Subversion server on macOS?",
        "answer": "cb:4f:c6:74:3e:1a:27:d3:55:e7:4b:5a:89:af:e4:c4:95:ce:fe:32"
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/UMIACS_Public_Printers",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "How many locations in the Iribe Center have publicly accessible printers?",
        "answer": "Four locations."
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of printer is located in room 3208?",
        "answer": "One color printer (HP Color LaserJet Enterprise M653) and one black/white printer (HP LaserJet Enterprise Flow MFP M633)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What additional capability does the black/white printer in room 4208 have?",
        "answer": "Faxing capability."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which printer is available in room 4149 for color printing?",
        "answer": "HP Color LaserJet Enterprise M653."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the model of the black/white printer located in room 5208?",
        "answer": "HP LaserJet Enterprise Flow MFP M633."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if you are unsure of how to connect to the printers?",
        "answer": "See the other articles on printing in UMIACS."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Windows_Account_Migration_March_2018",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of consolidating authentication into the new Active Directory domain UMIACS?",
        "answer": "To simplify the user experience so that users will be able to use a single password for all UMIACS services."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the new format for Windows accounts after the migration is completed?",
        "answer": "The new format will change from PC\\username to UMIACS\\username."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will happen to users' passwords during the migration?",
        "answer": "Your password will NOT change."
      },
      {
        "question": "When does the migration begin, and what is the specific time frame for it?",
        "answer": "The migration starts on Saturday, March 24th, 2018 from 8am to 11:59pm."
      },
      {
        "question": "What actions must users take regarding their Windows workstation before the migration begins?",
        "answer": "Users need to log off their Windows workstation prior to 8am on Saturday, March 24th."
      },
      {
        "question": "During the migration window, what is the status of the Pulse Secure VPN authentication?",
        "answer": "Authentication to the Pulse Secure VPN will not be available during the migration window."
      },
      {
        "question": "What will happen to Exchange email access during the migration?",
        "answer": "Exchange email access will be interrupted during the migration window, and while email will be delivered, it will not be accessible from phones, Outlook, or Outlook Web Access until after the migration has concluded."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the plan for existing VPN sessions during the migration?",
        "answer": "Existing sessions will not be terminated, allowing users to continue using the VPN through the migration."
      },
      {
        "question": "How will UMIACS notify users after the migration has completed?",
        "answer": "An announcement will be posted on https://intranet.umiacs.umd.edu and a follow-up email will be sent."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which services will require the new username format UMIACS\\username?",
        "answer": "The services that will require this new format are Outlook Web Access for Exchange email users, phone email setup for Exchange email users, Remote Desktop workstation access, and saved network drive credentials."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Working_with_External_Collaborators",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of accounts does UMIACS provide to facilitate collaboration with non-UMIACS Faculty, Staff, and Employees?",
        "answer": "Collaborator accounts."
      },
      {
        "question": "What resources can Collaborator accounts access?",
        "answer": "Collaborator accounts can access resources such as GitLab, UMobjstore, Wikis, and other web-based applications."
      },
      {
        "question": "Do Collaborator accounts have storage and access to UMIACS workstations?",
        "answer": "No, Collaborator accounts do not have storage and access to UMIACS workstations."
      },
      {
        "question": "Who has to sponsor the creation of a Collaborator Account?",
        "answer": "A UMIACS Account holder has to sponsor the Collaborator Account."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the UMIACS Requests Application in relation to Collaborator Accounts?",
        "answer": "The UMIACS Requests Application is used to sponsor the Collaborator Account and send an email to the Collaborator to set their details."
      },
      {
        "question": "What happens after a Collaborator has created their account?",
        "answer": "An email will be sent to both the account sponsor and the Collaborator that the account is ready to use."
      },
      {
        "question": "What built-in features does GitLab support for project collaboration?",
        "answer": "GitLab supports built-in project wikis, code review, and issue tracking for each project."
      },
      {
        "question": "Can Collaborators create their own projects in GitLab?",
        "answer": "No, although Collaborators can modify any of the repos they are added to, they do not get an allocation to create projects of their own."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the function of UMobjstore?",
        "answer": "UMobjstore is the web application component complementing UMobj, used to interact with the Object Store."
      },
      {
        "question": "What do SecGroups allow PIs to manage?",
        "answer": "SecGroups allow PIs to manage which users should have access to different applications they manage."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can one view which Security Groups they can grant access to?",
        "answer": "One can view which Security Groups they can grant access to through the directory app."
      }
    ],
    "total": 11
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Network/Troubleshooting/DNS",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the primary issue that has been experienced with home internet providers regarding UMIACS?",
        "answer": "Home internet providers not correctly handling DNS resolution for UMIACS hostnames."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the IP addresses provided for Google DNS?",
        "answer": "8.8.8.8 and 8.8.4.4."
      },
      {
        "question": "List the IP addresses associated with OpenDNS.",
        "answer": "208.67.222.222, 208.67.220.220, 208.67.222.220, and 208.67.220.222."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps are outlined to change default DNS servers on Windows?",
        "answer": "Go to Control Panel -> Network and Internet -> Network and Sharing Center. Click 'Change adapter settings' on the left. Right click on the network adapter you're using, choose 'Properties'. Select 'Internet Protocol Version 4 (TCP/IPv4)' and click on 'Properties'. If not selected, choose 'Use the following DNS server addresses:' and enter the public DNS addresses you desire to use. Click OK, and close the remaining windows."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can DNS servers be changed on macOS?",
        "answer": "Go to System Settings > Network > Wi-Fi/Ethernet > Details > DNS."
      },
      {
        "question": "What file needs to be edited on Linux to change DNS servers, and what specific action must be taken?",
        "answer": "Edit your /etc/resolv.conf file and change the IP addresses after 'nameserver' to any of those listed above."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the command to use the UMIACS name servers for a manual lookup of a host name?",
        "answer": "nslookup somehost.umiacs.umd.edu 128.8.120.19."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the UMIACS name servers listed for manual lookup?",
        "answer": "128.8.120.19, 128.8.120.50, and 128.8.132.75."
      }
    ],
    "total": 8
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/PerlDevelEnvironment",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the Integrated Development Environments (IDEs) for Perl mentioned in the text?",
        "answer": "ActiveState, emacs, Komodo, and VisualPerl."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which IDE for Perl is described as a plugin for MS Visual Studio .NET?",
        "answer": "VisualPerl from ActiveState."
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the previous pricing model for Komodo from ActiveState?",
        "answer": "It used to be free but not any more."
      },
      {
        "question": "According to the text, what are the suggested text editors for UNIX/Linux that support syntax highlighting?",
        "answer": "Emacs or any text editor that does syntax highlighting."
      },
      {
        "question": "If a user is familiar with VB and VC development, which Perl IDE is recommended as the best tool?",
        "answer": "VisualPerl from ActiveState."
      },
      {
        "question": "Is Komodo from ActiveState available for Windows?",
        "answer": "Yes, it is available for Windows too."
      }
    ],
    "total": 6
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Iribe/OfficeTV",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What are the two ways to connect a device to the office TVs?",
        "answer": "VGA cable or HDMI cable."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the main difference between HDMI and VGA concerning sound?",
        "answer": "HDMI transfers sound natively, while with VGA you need to connect an additional 3.5mm audio cable."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if your device does not automatically appear on the TV?",
        "answer": "You may need to turn on the TV or adjust the input of the TV using the remote."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you adjust the input of the TV?",
        "answer": "By clicking the source button on the remote, located between the volume and channel buttons, and selecting the proper input named HDMI 1."
      },
      {
        "question": "What two basic display modes are available for connection to the office TVs?",
        "answer": "Mirror and Extend."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the function of the Mirror display mode?",
        "answer": "It displays the same screen on both your computer and the TV."
      },
      {
        "question": "What steps must you follow to display images or a slideshow on the TV?",
        "answer": "Upload the pictures onto a flash drive, plug the flash drive into the USB port on the TV, click the source button on the remote, navigate to the MagicInfo S option, and select the USB from the dropdown menu."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do if you do not see 'Player' in the top left of the screen after navigating to MagicInfo S?",
        "answer": "Click on the player option in the menu or click the return button on your remote."
      },
      {
        "question": "How do you change the USB setting to display your pictures on the TV?",
        "answer": "Navigate to the dropdown menu that says Internal Memory and change it to the name of your USB using the remote's navigation buttons."
      },
      {
        "question": "What capabilities does the remote control provide when viewing a slideshow?",
        "answer": "You can click the play and pause buttons on the remote to toggle the slideshow behavior."
      },
      {
        "question": "What options can be changed regarding the slideshow playing on the TV?",
        "answer": "The slideshow speed, orientation, and transition effects."
      },
      {
        "question": "How much space is available for uploading files from a USB to the TVs?",
        "answer": "~4.5 GB."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the process to store images onto the TV from a USB?",
        "answer": "Navigate to the options menu, select the Send option, choose all the images you want to store, click the Send button, and select Internal Memory from the dropdown."
      },
      {
        "question": "What should you do after the image upload process completes?",
        "answer": "Navigate back to the internal memory to see all the pictures you selected, and you can then remove the USB."
      }
    ],
    "total": 14
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Security",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What type of security threats are mentioned in the section?",
        "answer": "Phishing and Malware/virus removal."
      },
      {
        "question": "What action is suggested regarding Java in the context of security?",
        "answer": "Disable Java."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is one of the practices related to browser security mentioned?",
        "answer": "Disable Browser."
      }
    ],
    "total": 3
  },
  {
    "url": "https://wiki.umiacs.umd.edu/umiacs/index.php/Python",
    "Q/A": [
      {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the PYTHONPATH variable in Python?",
        "answer": "The PYTHONPATH variable tells the Python interpreter where to look to find modules."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can you view your Python path in a Unix/Linux environment?",
        "answer": "You can view your Python path by executing the command: bash:~$ python -c 'import sys; print sys.path'."
      },
      {
        "question": "What command is used to install a Python module using the user scheme?",
        "answer": "The command used is: bash:~$ python setup.py install --user."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the prefix scheme allow a user to do when installing Python modules?",
        "answer": "The prefix scheme allows a user to install a module into a location of their choice, which needs to be added to the PYTHONPATH."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is a Python Virtual Environment?",
        "answer": "A Python Virtual Environment is an isolated working copy of Python which allows you to work on a specific project without worry of affecting other projects."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the significance of the command 'python setup.py install --prefix=\"/path/to/location\"'?",
        "answer": "This command is used to install a Python module into a user-defined location using the prefix scheme."
      },
      {
        "question": "In Windows, what is the traditional location used for the prefix scheme when installing additional packages?",
        "answer": "The traditional location used is: python setup.py install --prefix=\"\\Temp\\Python\"."
      },
      {
        "question": "What advantage do modern *NIX distributions provide regarding Python versions?",
        "answer": "Most modern *NIX distributions ship with a system version of Python."
      },
      {
        "question": "What can a user do if they need a version of Python not available through GNU Modules?",
        "answer": "The user can build Python from source using the instructions provided on the Python downloads page."
      },
      {
        "question": "How can directories be added to the PYTHONPATH in Python?",
        "answer": "Directories can be added to the PYTHONPATH through the shell or in the Python code itself with the command: >>> sys.path.append('/location/to/directory')."
      }
    ],
    "total": 10
  }
]
